Chapter 751: Evolve 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few days later…

The Blood Breeds had sent people to every corner without holding back, in search of Dahm and Hochman’s whereabouts. However, there were no traces of Death Apostles.

The Holy Fist Palace was hindered by their outdated and deficient intelligence fields. They did not know the exact whereabouts of the Death Apostles and could only wait silently while secretly dispatching manpower and reinforcements. The obstructions by the Blood Breeds resulted in a great reduction of their strength.

Both sides had clashed with each other in a few cities many times. However, they had restrained themselves from creating large-scale conflicts and only confined themselves to localized standoffs.

The weather in America gradually entered spring. During this time, Ninox, who had just returned from Grano, had finally brought Raffaele and a few of her other relatives back. They entered the village residence at the foot of a mountain near Holy Fist Palace.

“This is Holy Fist Palace?” Raffaele raised her head and looked at the lofty snowy white mountain. It was impossible to see the mountain peak as large clusters of white clouds were clustered together, forming a sea of clouds that obstructed her vision while they drifted around the mountainside.

The person who was walking in front and guiding them answered frantically.

“Yes, this is the headquarters of Holy Fist Palace. It is also the Temple of the Waterbird Fist and Shooting Shadow Fist.”

All three guides were fully dressed in black robes. Ninox wore the same outfit and walked in the center before turning her head and smiling at Raffaele after hearing what she had asked.

“Master already knows that you’re here and has prepared the banquet at the mountain top already. The next mountain path will probably require a climb of at least two hours. Of course, we will be using a cable car near the top of the mountain for part of the journey to make it more relaxing.”

“Isn’t there a public road that leads up the mountain here?” Raffaele felt slightly doubtful. She had to climb the mountain alone while the rest were left in the village at the foot of the mountain.

“We had planned to construct one initially but decided against that to preserve the original appearance of the mountain. Moreover, climbing up this mountain on foot also served as a form of training for many martial arts practitioners. This training is beneficial towards both the mind and body. Therefore, no one has bothered to repair the road anymore,” replied Ninox while smiling.

The line of people continued to move forward while walking along the mountain path. Throughout their journey, they would occasionally encounter martial arts practitioners who were going down the mountain.

Most of them were young people that were being led by a specially assigned leader. They were all dressed in black robes that made them resemble religious pilgrims with pious expressions on their faces.

They could occasionally see single martial artists. These people would have determined looks on their withered faces. Moreover, their skinny bodies would be covered in torn clothes while their faces would be sunken and yellow, making them look extremely poor. They would continue inching up the mountain while facing greater heights and colder thinner air without a single sign of cowardice on their faces.

Fortunately, the mountain path was clearly broadened already. It was seven to eight meters wide and neat white steps were built there as well. A few white semi-circular stone pavilions were built within a certain distance from each other, allowing people to rest there.

Along the way, Raffaele looked as if her mind was secretly frightened.

These martial artists were all normal humans who did not have the force fields of Blood Breeds or Witches around their bodies. However, they continued to display determined expressions despite clearly being normal humans.

It was rumored that although Holy Fist Palace had only been built for a few years, incredibly sincere disciples had already appeared. One could only imagine the importance of this powerful organization in the hearts of the human martial arts practitioners.

“These are ascetics. After the recent World Fistfighting Exchange Assembly at Holy Fist Palace, Master’s reputation as the World Fistfighting Master began to spread. As the only remaining great martial arts master, many ascetic martial artists would come over to humbly seek his teachings,” Ninox explained. “According to the rules of Holy Fist Palace, ascetics who are able to hike up Holy Fist Mountain on foot and reach Holy Fist Palace without any supplies will be qualified to take a free examination to enter the palace.”

“Isn’t this actually very simple? There are only two mountainous paths that will only take a few hours to climb up. A regular person would be able to hike up the mountain on foot as long as they were slightly more robust than normal,” Raffaele was rather puzzled.

“If only it were that simple. Walk this way.” Ninox guided Raffaele to the left, away from the path of the ascetics before walking on a different road that seemed more leveled. On the road, they could see many people climbing down the mountain, making the stream of people much denser than before. Most of these people seemed to possess exuberant spirits and ample vigor. They were outfitted with various ornaments and equipment. Some of them even had the faint smell of blood wafting from their bodies.

When they saw how Ninox and the others were dressed, most of the people who were walking down the mountain gave way immediately. They saluted them faintly and waited for the group to pass as a sign of their respect before continuing their journey.

“This place is the real mountain path that leads upwards. Meanwhile, the ascetics travel forward on the road that we were using earlier,” Ninox only replied after returning the salutes of others.

“Are there any differences?” asked Raffaele in a slightly curious tone.

“Of course there are differences, big ones in fact,” Ninox smiled. “Watchmen are placed along the path of the ascetics at certain distance intervals. They are elderly disciples who are participating in voluntarily ascetic practices within Holy Fist Palace. They will test the ascetics after a specific distance. Furthermore, some of these tests are unbelievably dangerous and even life-threatening. For instance, one of the tests requires them to walk a distance of two meters along a precipice that is only the width of a palm. The slightest mistake will send them falling into an abyss. This is a test of courage and carefulness while there are others that will test one’s willpower,” a desolate but respectful look appeared on Ninox’s face.

One of the guides beside her could not help but interrupt.

“Those who are able to pass the tests and arrive at Holy Fist Palace are definitely outstanding elites. They will usually be instantly promoted as official members who are free to choose to enter any of the three great departments that consist of the combat club, Nighthawks, or the Holy Fist Palace headquarters.”

“That’s amazing, right?” Raffaele was slightly intrigued. As a Sun Witch, she had always been unconcerned about the powers of normal people. However, after seeing the proud look on the other person’s face while she was speaking currently, she was unable to control her mouth and asked the question suddenly.

“Of course!”

That person was a girl who possessed a competitive temperament.

“Only the two great marshalls and the Four Major Generals are qualified to practice the Royal Fist Technique. Its powers are completely beyond your imagination!”

Raffaele smiled but was slightly unconvinced. Although she had heard that Holy Fist Palace was indeed very powerful, those rumors were only based on the great strength of the Holy Fist. Was it really possible that he managed to cultivate subordinates that were equally strong within a few short years? She did not believe it.

However, her expression froze quickly when she saw a few familiar figures walking down the mountain.

They were the Blood Breed witnesses that she had once met at the Witches meeting. They were previously members of the Light Party and one of them was an old Middle-level Blood Breed woman. She was currently walking down the mountain with a calm expression on her face. Apparently, the other woman did not recognize her as Raffaele had initially belonged to the Lower level. The difference between them was too great and they did not have any chance to socialize at all.

As she watched the old woman stroll down the mountain slowly, the shock in Raffaele’s heart increased suddenly.

Soon, she saw more Blood Breeds that were emitting Middle and Lower level Qi while walking down the mountain. They were speaking casually and happily with a few people who looked like completely unassuming regular humans. Apparently, they were all on equal footing.

This caused her small mouth to gape open slightly.

Ninox and the others looked at her while faint feelings of pride and dignity flashed through their minds.

The line of people quickened their footsteps and climbed up the mountain hurriedly. They soon arrived at the location of the cable car. After providing the proof, they clambered into the cable cars before traveling up the mountain along the sturdy steel cords speedily.

When the steel cords passed through the sea of clouds, the entire stretch of whiteness around them made it impossible to see the edges.

An intrigued expression flashed in Raffaele’s eyes.

“How beautiful…”

“Of course,” Ninox smiled.

Time ticked by before the cable car approached the Holy Fist Palace quickly. The lofty and huge white building gradually became bigger while a large cylindrical passage spouted white gas that resembled water outwards continuously.

“What is that, the thing that is coming out?” Raffaele pointed towards the white gas and asked.

“A specialized gas. It’s a type of gas that is extracted from the insides of the mountain. Since the temperature here is too low, the difference between the temperature of the water inside is too great, forming this white gas that gushes out. In reality, it is merely a normal ventilation installation,” answered Ninox patiently.

As the steel cords approached slowly, a few other cars in front of them that traveled downwards along the steel cords had appeared.

There was a person in a thick coat who was with a few of his subordinates. There was a somewhat uncomfortable look on his face as he sat in the cable car.

Raffaele glanced at one of the people before feeling her heart jump suddenly when a brutal Qi radiated from their bodies naturally. He glanced over unexpectedly and it seemed as if a ray of white light flashed in his eyes suddenly when he looked over.

Raffaele’s mind was shocked and she lowered her head immediately. She had gained a new understanding of the strength of Holy Fist Palace.

The convoy got down from the car and entered the palace while being guided by the people in charge. They passed through various areas before entering the inner cavity of the mountain.

Half an hour later, Raffaele was finally taken into an area that was filled with little warm water fountains everywhere.

A familiar figure was standing in front of a bright stone hall there, waiting for her.

Ninox took her into the stone hall and stopped walking before leaving quietly. Once she had entered the stone hall, the stone door behind Raffaele was quietly closed, and she was alone in the room with Garen.

There was a large wall of floor-length glass on the other side of the white stone hall. It was possible to see the endless sea of white clouds there, making it seem as if one was standing up high in the clouds.

“Long time no see, Raffaele,” the figure turned around and looked at her calmly. The person was wearing a mask on his face, but Raffaele was able to recognize his voice and tone immediately as the same Garen that she’d once known.

“Yes, long time no see. How many years has it been since we last met?” Raffaele walked towards a chair beside Garen and sat down.

It looked as if he was still stuck in his old ways. He still looked like a regular person from the past. However, she understood that his current self was far from the simple identity that he’d once possessed in the beginning. Perhaps he never had never been simple from the start.

“Almost a year and two months,” answered Garen casually. “Since you’ve come all this way, you should rest properly here. There will be people who are in charge of going down the mountain to buy anything you need. You could even go to the little village at the foot of the mountain if you want.”

“Are Uncle Emmer and little sister Vivien there?” Emotions stirred inside Raffaele’s eyes slightly.

“They’re both in the little village at the bottom of the mountain,” Garen did not conceal anything.

“I’ll go and be with them then,” said Raffaele while lowering her head and biting her lip. “Frankly, I’m not in the position to say this, but the things between us ended quietly a long time ago, right?”

“Who knows?” Garen chuckled before lifting her chin gently. “Stay with my family for me. It’s inconvenient for me to accompany them constantly now, and you’re the only one who can help me.”

“Don’t do this,” anger flashed in Raffaele’s eyes before she pushed Garen’s hand away. “I don’t like actions like that. They make me feel very disrespected.”

“Alright,” Garen was slightly shocked. Only then did he remember that Raffaele had finally become one of the leaders of the Witches. “Okay, you should go and rest for a while first. I still have things to sort out.”

“Okay,” Raffaele turned around and walked out of the main door of the stone hall quickly with slightly flushed cheeks.

Suddenly, she felt her waist tighten as her waist was embraced by Garen from behind. Next, a slightly warm feeling began to creep up her neck.

“Don’t worry, I will take care of everything,” Garen’s voice echoed behind her.

Chapter 752: Evolve 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Raffaele’s entire body turned numb and her cheeks became red at once. A look of uncertainty flashed in her eyes before turning into a firm expression immediately.

“I know.”

Her voice sounded like the buzz of a mosquito when she replied and she broke free of Garen’s embrace suddenly before she pushed the door open and left.

She shut the stone door behind her.

Raffaele was led towards her own room by one of the people in charge.

Behind the young female guide, she hung her head while somewhat heavy feelings filled her mind.

“For the mission of the Witch King Mother… Lion Mother… Protected me so that I can finish this task successfully…” countless complicated ideas drifted through her mind continuously.

As she regulated and controlled her own consciousness, she slowly sank into a state of half confusion and could only follow the young woman and walk forward instinctively.

While she remained in this state, a faint voice echoed throughout her mind suddenly.

“Hong Ji, you did extremely well and without raising Garen’s suspicions.”

“Witch King Mother?!” joy stirred within Raffaele’s heart suddenly before her mind shouted out internally.

“Don’t worry, although that person is extremely powerful, he is still not an undefeatable Death Apostle. As long as he is not a Death Apostle, he will definitely have flaws. You merely need to wait for the right opportunity and be more patient… Patience…” that voice disappeared slowly.

Raffaele finally knew that the Lion Mother had left when her mind regained consciousness in a somewhat frustrated manner suddenly. She was one of the forty-five Witch Lion Mother’s daughters who had been chosen as members of this plan, and the most important member as well.

Once she thought of her mission, Hong Ji became even more determined at once.

When she thought of the possibility of having to go up against a few innocent subordinates who were merely normal people, an unbearable feeling bubbled up inside her heart. However, it was immediately suppressed forcefully.

“Holy Fist Palace is the source of all chaos and Holy Fist Garen is the origin of Holy Fist Palace. This is to ensure that the order of the world returns to conformity… Everything that I do is for order…”

When she thought of this, sacred splendor appeared in the depths of her eyes once again.

“Now all I have to do now is to observe the internal situation of Holy Fist Palace for a while, as it’s best to clarify all the divisions of strength and forces. After that, I’ll go to the foot of the mountain again…” a plan formed in her heart quickly.

*********

Inside the stone hall

Garen stood beside one of the stone pillars that was next to the fountain in the center with a calm expression on his face. A Blood Breed subordinate in black clothes was currently standing beside him and reporting the situation quietly.

“…investigated all of the related areas and searched high and low in all of the places where it could possibly exist. As of now, we have not received any information on Marshall Dahm,” the male Blood Breed covered his face, making it impossible to see his expression while he reported everything in a low voice.

“The reporting division confirmed that they lost him three days ago? What about Caesar?” Garen’s eyebrows were slightly furrowed.

“Since Sir Caesar had to arrange for follow-up tasks to wrap everything up, he was unable to return earlier. The hidden members have been arranged to escort Marshall Dahm, but no one expected that they would encounter an ambush along the way. The members have gone missing. Judging from the traces that were left on the site, it seems like this was the doing of the Blood Breeds. However, we were still unable to determine Marshall Dahm’s whereabouts despite using every method we know. I’m extremely sorry!” said the male Blood Breed with his head lowered.

“Dahm…” Garen pondered casually. “He should have a mask with him now. The probability of the Blood Breed’s actions is very likely.”

“That is indeed true. Moreover, the key point is that our strength networks are only covering the American territories. Meanwhile, the other territories are still being influenced and occupied by the forces of the Blood Breeds. This makes it impossible for us to conduct grand scale searches.”

“You can go back down first,” Garen nodded.

The male Blood Breed exited the stone hall respectfully, leaving Garen there alone.

‘The actions of the Blood Breeds are extremely arrogant…’ Black Sethe’s voice drifted over.

“Not the Blood Breeds,” Garen answered simply.

‘Oh? How do you know? If it wasn’t the Blood Breeds, who else would dare to ambush a high-level expert like Dahm?’ Black Sethe could not really understand how Garen was able to come up with such a conclusion.

“I naturally have my own ways. But I’m certain that it’s not the Blood Breeds.” Garen walked towards the front of the floor-length glass and looked out at the endless sea of white clouds. His gaze seemed to penetrate the boundless distance while looking on in an unknown direction.

****************

Within a concealed valley in America

Huff…

Huff…

Huff…

Something sounded like the heavy breathing of a wild beast. It also sounded like the violent panting of an exhausted fierce predator.

Dahm sat leaning against a little green moss-covered ravine inside the valley. He’d covered himself with large piles of broken tree branches and leaves to the best of his ability before stretching out his four limbs and body.

Both of his eyes were bloodshot and he seemed unusually thin and sallow, as though he’d been unable to rest for a long time.

Within the lush green forest around him, muffled noises and movements would echo through occasionally. These noises were enough to force him to turn his head around quickly while looking behind himself with an unusually worried expression on his face.

It was true that he’d had no chance to rest.

After obtaining the mask, he had been ambushed by people on the way back. All of his escorts had been killed and he’d used all of his strength to fight the enemy off before escaping quickly. Next, his opponent started to chase him quickly. While he was being pursued, he could feel that his opponent was clearly closing the gap between them. When he ran towards a place with more people, his opponent would follow him closely behind suddenly before clashing with him violently. They fought until he was forced to flee into more remote areas.

They were forcing him into no man’s land!

Dahm sank both of his feet inside the undergrowth and mud inside the ravine. His body was covered in bits of grass and little insects while there were countless gashes on is clothes. His entire body seemed incomparably sallow, making him look completely unlike his usual elegant Marshall’s demeanor.

After three consecutive days of being pursued and attacked, the high state of anxiety that he was currently in due to lack of proper rest caused him to become as easily startled as a bird by the slightest noise. His body had weakened as well. He was initially able to release the first star and use the Waterbird Fist’s Final Profound, Flight of the Evil Phoenix that he was unable to control all along. However, he had overused his body, and his current lack of rest made it difficult for him to heal. His bodily deficiencies were also becoming even worse.

“Don’t tell me I’m going to die here?!” unwillingness flashed in Dahm’s eyes.

At this moment, the distinct noise of footsteps could be heard faintly in the forest. The noise started off slowly and paused for a while before it detected that he was here. Suddenly, the noise quickened at once and approached him instantly.

“You can’t escape anymore!” a determined gaze flashed in Dahm’s eyes. “You may lose all chances of resisting if you keep escaping!”

He tried to relax his body as much as he could. He tried his best to accumulate all the energy in his body despite being unable to rest for a long time while waiting quietly for his enemy and pursuer to approach him quickly.

500 meters… 400 meters… 300 meters… 100 meters…

Crash!

A tree branch and leaves were torn down at once before a familiar figure appeared before Dahm’s eyes.

“Hochman!!” Dahm yelled out suddenly. “It was actually… It was actually you!!!” he gritted his teeth in anger. His body had tensed up immediately even though he had just relaxed it moments ago. Intense hatred flashed in his eyes.

Hochman’s face was calm and he’d just changed into a black suit and beautiful black leather shoes. He looked like a regular but successful man who was planning to attend a banquet. However, his attire was clearly abnormal and strange while standing in a forest in a canyon.

He glanced casually at Dahm who was in an extremely awkward position.

“How pitiful. To think that you would fall into such a state, Dahm. You’ve truly embarrassed Master now.”

“I knew it was you…!!” Dahm’s entire body trembled with rage. All this while, he would be pursued by the other person whenever he wanted to rest. Every time he thought of stopping, his opponent would approach him immediately, making it impossible for him to rest. He could never understand how someone was able to grasp his whereabouts so accurately. But in hindsight, he realized that it could only be Hochman, who was able to use the Qi connection between both of their Soul Primers to locate him.

Dahm himself was currently unimaginably weak. He was unable to do the same thing, but it was clear that Hochman had his own ways.

Both of them were practitioners of one of the two sides of the Waterbird Fist respectively. The Negative Waterbird Fist and Positive Waterbird Fist could only become the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist when it was combined. Unlike the other similar branches, the techniques that these two men were practicing were the strongest among the Waterbird Fists and were also the practicing pathways with the greatest power.

Garen had once mentioned to just the two of them that although the strength of their Fist Techniques was extremely powerful, they would naturally lose a lot as well. Strength could only be obtained by paying prices that were unimaginable to normal humans. Therefore, only one person could survive between the users of the Negative and Positive Fist Techniques. The one who survived would be able to resume the fusion of the Fist Techniques and advance it to peak levels.

As for the extent of the peak level powers, even Garen himself was unaware of what that truly meant. Since this pathway was merely a road formed by a theory that he had deduced, the true powers that it could achieve were something that he himself as the advancer of the Waterbird Fist did not know either.

“This is truly a rare opportunity… Don’t you think so, Dahm?” Hochman adjusted his glasses and walked towards Dahm slowly. “Perfecting the Waterbird Fist is the final goal that you and I should be pursuing.”

“You won’t get away with this…” said Dahm furiously.

“Who knows?” Hochman spread both of his hands while a smile appeared on his face. “Actually, I’ve always been very thankful to Master for giving us a chance to improve. He was right. The results that one wishes to accomplish can only be achieved if an equivalent contribution is made. Just look at Quentin, Xander, and the others. They’re currently still at Middle levels and can never achieve Upper levels. Moreover, they are forced to struggle bitterly whenever they face just one Upper-level Blood Breed. Why is that?”

He paused before his smile widened.

“Because their contributions towards their martial arts were not great enough!”

Dahm could only grit his teeth in response.

Hochman glanced at him casually.

“The way of our Waterbird Fist of the Holy Fist Palace is also a holy path for Fist Techniques. In reality, although other people are unaware of this, should we just remain unaware as well? The supposed holy paths are actually just demonic paths. Aren’t we just practicing demonic techniques? How would we be able to progress so quickly otherwise?”

“The demonic technique adheres to the survival of the fittest as its main principle. Dahm…” his eyes turned fierce at once. “I’m stronger than you. Therefore, you’re only destined to be my stepping stone… These things were already predestined.”

“If you kill me, you won’t meet a happy ending! Besides that, don’t you want the mask?!” although Dahm already knew that it was impossible for him to escape by sheer luck, a final ray of hope flashed in his eyes.

“I’ll form the holy path after I kill you. As for the mask, it was naturally snatched by the Blood Breeds, or perhaps already destroyed.” Hochman smiled before a dull crashing noise could be heard below his feet as he charged towards Dahm like a rocket. His arm expanded suddenly and became thicker and darker as if it was completely shrouded in countless dark blue veins.

His ferocious Qi was moved by this punch as though all the air around him had been absorbed into his fist.

The entire forest darkened slightly when it was affected by the frantic flow of air.

“Go peacefully! I will take care of your household properly!”

Boom!!!

Chapter 753: Bureau 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kasha!!

A flash of lightning streaked across the sky.

It illuminated the hall of Holy Fist Palace and it glowed as bright as snow for a second.

Garen stood in the dark hall. Unconsciously, he had already been standing here for the entire afternoon.

For an unknown reason, he was constantly disturbed by an extremely agitated feeling recently. Although he used the duration of an entire afternoon this time, he was still unable to find the root and cause of this irritation. Perhaps it was caused by practicing the Holy Phoenix Scriptures. In the end, he always felt that his emotional fluctuations were decreasing and his feelings were becoming colder. In the past, there were many things that would stir his emotions but now he only felt indifference.

Kasha!

The lightning struck again and illuminated the hall in blues and whites immediately.

Garen stood in the large hall alone while the flash of lightning caused a long shadow to form behind him instantly.

“This world…” he looked at the endless sea of clouds outside the window. “It’s rejecting me.”

‘You’ve felt it?’ Black Sethe’s weak voice could be heard occasionally. ‘You passed through the Mother Stream accidentally. Moreover, your original plan was not to come here and your arrival in this world was merely a mistake.’

“This world does not possess any form of consciousness. How did this phenomenon occur?” Garen could not understand.

‘Yes… Most worlds do not possess consciousness but each world has a different state. They resemble the various different types of plants,’ explained Black Sethe softly, ‘but the Holy Phoenix Scriptures that you practice are scriptures that are heartless and lack character. Their goal is to heighten one’s spirit to its limits which require a large number of energy sources from the outside world. This is actually equivalent to plundering the world. Any actions that absorb energy from the outside world to strengthen oneself will naturally cause chain reactions. This is due to the changes that occur when the cycle of equilibrium is destroyed.’

Garen remained silent for a moment before nodding his head faintly.

“I know what you mean. It is similar to how certain beasts of prey in a mountain forest require more food when they become stronger suddenly. When the mountain forest is unable to satisfy their needs, they are forced to widen their range which will ultimately destroy the natural cycle of equilibrium in their surroundings.”

‘To be more precise, absorbing too much energy without producing an equal amount in return. It is similar to the deformed and distorted cancer cells in the human body that rob energy that is originally used for other functions. This causes faults and the destruction of the natural cycle before serious environmental changes are finally produced. These changes have also been detected by the creatures in certain areas of this world, and they are currently taking action,’ Black Sethe explained. ‘This was also caused by the Holy Phoenix Scriptures’ overly extreme true intentions.’

“Looks like this is the source of my agitation,” Garen nodded. “My five senses and instincts have become sharper, making it possible for me to detect the threats that I am about to encounter in the future…”

‘Your powers are getting even stronger and their influence towards their surroundings will naturally become greater as well. This is unavoidable and amplified effects like these will form traces that will make it easier for others to observe and grasp. Initially, you were not like this. However, the Holy Phoenix Scriptures were too strong and their plundering techniques were too extreme. Therefore, the changes in your surroundings were intensified,’ answered Black Sethe casually.

Garen did not speak anymore and merely looked out of the window silently into the sea of white fluffy clouds below.

Kachak!!

There was a flash of lightning.

Large sheets of rain cascaded downwards and left yarn-like traces when it was stirred by the wind.

Dahm’s entire body was covered in fresh blood while the base of his back was pressed against the icy cold green mountain wall. He glared daggers at Hochman who stood on the opposite side of him not far away.

Both of them stood under the heavy rain without the intention of shielding themselves from it at all.

There were potholes everywhere on the ground. The mud inside most of these was filled with red and yellow fresh blood. It was clear that these potholes had just been formed and were quickly being filled by rainwater.

The raindrops shook the surrounding leaves, branches, and undergrowth continuously while the wind gusted and howled. It sounded like the crying noises of a human or the ghostly howls of an animal.

“Give up.”

The suit on Hochman’s back was already soaked through. However, he remained emotionless and looked quietly at Dahm who was nearby. The raindrops rolled off his cheeks continuously and wet his hair, causing the strands to stick against his forehead closely.

They had already been fighting in the valley for an extremely long and continuous period of time. To prevent Dahm from counter-attacking with all of his might, or perhaps to ensure that he would win without any injuries, Hochman did not close in on him unnecessarily at all. Instead, he would chase Dahm step-by-step and step forward to clash with him occasionally. He was constantly keeping his opponent in a panicked state to exhaust him.

The effect of this was actually very satisfying. Currently, Dahm had almost exhausted all of his energy and was unwilling to even move. To preserve his energy, he was leaning against the side of the mountain. Being unable to restore his energy for a few days had caused him to deplete his resources and fall into a troubled state much earlier on.

“You don’t even stand a chance anymore,” said Hochman lightly.

“I was ambushed by you after I completed a mission. Master… Master will not forsake me…” said Dahm furiously. “You’re ignoring the bigger picture and fighting a member of your own branch. Did you forget that the whereabouts of your cousin is still in my hands…”

“You’re too naive…” Hochman laughed suddenly. “To think that you really believed that I truly liked my cousin?” He raised his head and looked at the color of the sky. “It’s almost time.”

He removed his glasses slowly and exposed his cold, sharp and narrow long eyes.

He combed his hair backward after removing his glasses to instantly form a clean and sharp slicked-back hairstyle. An indescribably imposing manner permeated from his body faintly.

“It’s impossible for people not to have weaknesses, Dahm,” a devilishly handsome smile appeared on Hochman’s pale and chiseled face.

“End it.”

He outstretched both of his hands and crossed all ten of his fingers to form a heart shape.

Boom!!

While the heavy rain continued to pour, his figure crashed through the sheets of rain suddenly. Only martial artists could notice that a large black aura had exploded suddenly around his entire body to form the black shadow of a terrifying dragon’s head that roared as it charged towards Dahm.

“Clouded leopard!!”

Hochman let out a low growl as his entire body charged forward in the rain. He was currently stretched out like a cheetah that was dashing forward. The air and raindrops sputtered around when he tore through them. As his speed was extremely fast, he formed a long cavity in the middle of the heavy rain.

His Upper-level powers were being released all at once from the palms of both of Hochman’s palms where they were gathered.

Bang!!!

Both of his hands sank into the mountainside deeply before the entire surface collapsed with a ‘crash’ after caving inwards.

Dahm was barely able to dodge this attack. However, he was still affected by the repercussions. The raindrops that were sent flying violently hit against his body painfully like bullets, forming a few more wounds.

“Bloody Night!!”

He roared loudly and threw out his last two silk strings. However, they were completely exposed amidst the rain and he was unable to hide them at all, making it easy for Hochman to evade them.

“Does God want me to die as well?!” Dahm staggered towards the left side and tottered into the rain. Feelings of dread filled his heart. His handphone and other electronics that were on him had been destroyed at the first moment. He was unable to ask for assistance as Hochman had intentionally driven away that chance as well.

“Don’t tell me I’m really going to die here…” Behind him, Dahm could hear the sound of Hochman tearing through the air hurriedly. “Master…” the last image that floated up in his mind was the scene when Garen had first taught them the Waterbird Fist. The memories from that scene… That marked the starting point of his journey into the temple of martial arts.

“White Bear!”

A low roar echoed behind him.

Bang!!!

Dahm felt a pain in his chest. He had detected the whistling sound of tearing air behind him long ago. However, his physical body was unable to keep up with his consciousness anymore. He wanted to dodge but was struck in the middle of his back.

Pfoo…

He lowered his head and spat out a mouthful of fresh blood before kneeling into the rainy dark night with a ‘thump’.

Bang!!

Another violent jolt of pain could be felt from his back when it was hit over where his heart was located. He was hit by yet another brutal punch before the immense pain passed through his muscles and bones. It hit his heart accurately and caused it to explode suddenly.

This was Hochman’s prized hidden Waterbird strength that was able to detonate the insides of his opponent’s body anytime. It was unlike Dahm’s own exploding blood. Hochman’s explosions were formed when he gathered his strength before releasing a one-hit killing blow.

“Goodbye… Dahm.”

Hochman’s voice echoed behind him.

Dahm’s vision was blinded before darkening gradually. Everything began to darken before becoming blurry and turning black slowly until he was unable to see anything anymore. He could feel the strength in his body flowing away quickly while an empty feeling drifted in his mind.

“Am I going to die?”

He fell into darkness finally while the sound of the rain began to soften. Soon, he was unable to hear anything and his nose was unable to smell the scent of rain anymore.

Shh!!

A sensation that resembled the feeling of a deflating balloon was felt inside his body. Dahm felt as if he was losing something extremely important that was currently escaping and being removed quickly.

Gradually, his consciousness fell into complete darkness.

The roaring sound of thunder echoed in the sky.

Hochman stood beside Dahm’s corpse quietly and looked at this man whom he’d once regarded as his best friend. His blood red aura flowed out of his body continuously before converging with his black aura.

The blood red aura resembled a bloody stream. It flowed out of the wound on Dahm’s back continuously before crossing the ground and converging with the black shadow below his feet.

Strong and intense emotions flooded the depths of his body and heart endlessly.

Hochman outstretched his right hand. The flesh on his palm that was initially covered by terrifying blackened skin and muscles was currently shrouded in faint threads of blood that were crawling there. These bloody threads formed on the surface of his skin like a large red web that covered the entire surface of his body.

“Power… This kind of power… Hehehehe…”

Continuous feelings of fulfillment and power flooded Hochman’s heart endlessly.

He could feel that the Qi of the Soul Primer in the depths of his spirit was continuously being nourished by this strength. Moreover, strange changes were gradually forming there.

The Qi of the Primer there was becoming stronger and more intense.

Boom!!

A crashing noise could be heard. No one knew if it was the sound of thunder or the sound of an explosion in his heart.

Hochman’s entire body trembled suddenly. He could vaguely see a figure that was fully dressed in black muslin walking out of the rain suddenly.

“Who are you?” it was difficult to distinguish the other person’s figure in the rain and they seemed almost transparent at times, giving off a strange illusory feeling.

“My identity is unimportant,” answered the person in a soft voice. Their voice was neither masculine nor feminine, making it impossible to distinguish their sex. “The important thing is that you’re currently in an extremely important phase.”

“Oh?” Hochman kept his guard up.

Chapter 754: Bureau 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“There are abnormalities in your soul. These abnormalities bring strange changes… Let me help you.”

Before they could finish speaking, the other person’s figure disappeared abruptly. At the moment when their figure vanished, Hochman suddenly felt a pain in his own head.

Ahh!!!

He raised his head suddenly and roared furiously.

The immense pain surged through his body and caught him off guard. It felt as if a giant hammer had been suddenly smashed against his head. His five senses were completely affected by the violent burning pain all at once.

A tearing noise could be heard.

Hochman could hear the faint sound of something ripping. Next, a strange sense of freedom filled his mind.

“You’re free now…” a voice echoed in the rain.

Hochman lowered his head in a trance. He noticed that his own body had been restored to its normal state again as if everything that happened earlier was just an illusion.

Meanwhile, the strange feeling of constantly being controlled by Garen that was always hidden in the depths of his heart had disappeared completely now.

“I’m free?” he asked himself quietly.

He felt as if he had robbed something from Master. This unknown feeling was truly strange and indescribable. He was currently filled with a type of unprecedented power while the endless amounts of energy that formed a cycle inside his body made it feel as if he could crack the earth with one punch and break through any obstacle that hindered his path.

He crouched his body downwards and took the still-perfect mask from Dahm’s body quickly before keeping it close against his bosom.

“I can’t return anymore…” he murmured to himself softly before taking a final look at Dahm’s corpse. His figure flashed before he disappeared into the heavy rain instantly.

*******************

Holy Fist Palace

Garen suddenly felt a sharp pain ripping through his brain.

Woo…

He buried his face in his hands suddenly and stood in the middle of the large dark hall while being unable to suppress his cold sweat for a while.

“This is…?!”

The searing pain had arrived at a strange moment and had been unusually sudden as well.

He raised his head abruptly and looked in a direction that led to the outside of the palace.

“It’s the Soul Primer… Someone has escaped from my control! They ripped out a part of my Soul Primer and stole it!! Who was it??!!” his mind jolted with shock.

He closed his eyes and carefully detected the Qi of the Soul Primer that had flowed out of him at once.

The clusters of Qi seemed like galaxies of stars that were distributed throughout the dark and empty spaces in his mind. At this moment, out of the two largest stars that represented the Soul Primers, one of them had dimmed quickly while the other was shining brighter and even turning transparent quickly! It transmitted an unavoidable sense of separation.

“It’s Dahm and Hochman!” Garen’s mind froze at once. “Dahm is dead… Hochman absorbed the other pole of the Waterbird Fist’s aura… But how was he able to break away from the control of my Soul Primer? How could he rip through the Qi of my soul??!!”

‘Apparently, it was just as I had anticipated. You have trouble, Garen,’ said Black Sethe quietly.

Garen remained silent and did not speak. However, the waves of pain from his headaches caused the veins in his face to become even more obvious, making him look ferocious as well.

According to the principle, even though Hochman had absorbed and killed Dahm, it was still impossible for him to break free of Garen’s control. Though in hindsight, he had truly stolen a part of the Soul Primer’s Qi that belonged to him. Once he had appropriated it to himself, he was even able to successfully escape from Garen’s control of his spirit.

There were definitely external forces that were helping him!

“Who is it? Who’s helping him? Who could be able to help him?!” asked Garen quietly.

Losing this Soul Primer and its Qi would spell major trouble for him. Soul Primers instinctively had perfect characteristics. However, once part of it was ripped away, life-threatening flaws would show up in the soul. If he was unable to make up for it quickly, when an enemy of the same level used direct soul attacks against him, it was very likely that Garen would collapse completely within a short span of time in his current state.

‘You need to restore the wounds in our soul quickly! Otherwise, when Nadia appears, just one gaze of hers will be enough to kill you!!’ Black Sethe said seriously. ‘You cannot have the slightest flaw or obvious deficiency between experts. One misstep will be your downfall! This is truly fatal!’

“How could this world have measures that can counter against souls?!” Garen could feel that his headache was easing itself gradually. However, his face was still slightly uncomfortable.

‘Since this world is so huge, it would be very normal for various mystical creatures to appear. The important thing right now is that you need to find Hochman as soon as possible to get back the soul Qi that was ripped from you! For most people, perhaps this would merely be insignificant shrouds of soul Qi that would not be a great hindrance even if they lost it. However, to experts and peak level experts especially, whenever little holes appear in their imperfections, these seemingly tiny holes will be expanded endlessly,’ reminded Black Sethe in a low voice.

“I was careless…” Garen’s expression turned slightly ashen as this was the first time he had tasted such bitter regret. In this world, everything was going smoothly and he did not have any enemies at all. Even the Death Apostles were not worthy opponents in his eyes as most of them were merely cockroaches that could not be killed easily. All of his energy was directed towards Nadia as Nadia was his only true adversary. However, someone had inflicted a heavy hit upon him now!

‘Souls are extremely important towards all life forms. Even the Qi of the Soul Primer that you released could produce a military influence that causes you and your subordinates to become strong together. Not to mention that there are many other mystical properties and effects that we have yet to discover. This is definitely not an aspect that we can overlook.’

Garen remained silent. He thought of the years that he’d spent continuously separating shrouds of soul Qi. If all of this Qi was ripped by others violently… His once powerful soul would probably be suppressed into a state of everlasting weakness…

When he thought of this, Garen turned around suddenly and walked out of the main door.

He had to bring all of the parts of his Soul Primer that had been separated as soon as possible. Although this would cause a great loss throughout the strength of his subordinates, he was unable to be preoccupied with so many things now!

Dahm had died in battle while Hochman deserted him and fled! The repercussions that were caused by this incident would be very severe!

‘Are you thinking of retrieving all of your Primers back? You don’t need to do that,’ said Black Sethe. ‘Army level Primers like yours cannot simply be torn at any moment as they require specific timings. Among your subordinates, only Dahm and Hochman had the power to alter time while the others could not. Moreover, the consumption that is caused when one rips it is extremely great! This is something that was done on the soul level and could not be completed easily. Furthermore, the effects of the soul and Qi towards the physical body cannot overlap with one another. Losing one of them is equivalent to losing a hundred. Losses like these are negligible against the total strength of the soul itself. Only gaps and splits that are formed within perfect states and realms are the most troublesome.’

‘However, although it will not be affected, or perhaps the probability of the effects will be very low, I still suggest that you remove everyone from the inside of the palace and check them once over. You need to pay close attention to those who display unusual states!’ Black Sethe suggested.

“Right now, the most important thing is to capture Hochman and bring him back,” Garen pushed the main door open and walked out of the stone hall briskly. The disciples who were standing guard outside the door bowed their heads and looked at him with respectful gazes while he walked towards the student’s practice hall.

Dahm’s death and Hochman’s betrayal meant that Holy Fist Palace had lost two of its main Upper-level members at the same time. This affected Holy Fist Palace greatly, forcing him to make the necessary arrangements quickly before solving the problem of the torn souls later.

He would only be able to fully restore his lost soul and Qi by killing Hochman and remedying the flaws in his soul.

***************

Raffaele stood quietly in the doorway of the hidden room inside the palace. There was no one else in her surroundings and the sole patrol guard had just passed by to survey the cracks and gaps. There were a total of fifteen hidden rooms like this within Holy Fist Palace. She had already examined ten separate ones as her goal was to find the Sleepless Faces masks that were kept in Holy Fist Palace. There were about six of these masks that were collected in Holy Fist Palace and were definitely concealed in specific hidden places. Once she found it, she could quickly create a fake mask using the Witchcraft that Witch King Mother had prepared. This would allow her to take the real mask away quietly.

After pushing open the stone door that led to the hidden room gently, Raffaele walked inside silently and scanned the area quickly. Other than the necessary items such as the bright candlesticks, tables, chairs, and other furniture, the room was devoid of other objects.

She removed a little white ornament that was used a decoration from her own skirt quickly and shook it gently before a faint white light was released from the ornament suddenly, passing through the insides of the hidden room at once.

“The same thing again…” Raffaele’s gaze darkened slightly while she prepared herself to leave dejectedly.

Suddenly, the white ornament lit up again suddenly before shining directly on the wall on the opposite side of the door to the hidden room.

“This is?!!” Raffaele’s eyes narrowed when she realized that the magical probing tool that had been given to her by the Witch King Mother would not react for no reason.

She walked over quickly while the white light from the ornament in her hand reflected against the wall in a translucent state like glass. She could see the situation on the other side of the wall through it.

She could see a cylindrical, average-sized cavity inside the wall where a book seemed to be placed there. The book was thick and had a hard black cover.

For an unknown reason, this book gave Raffaele a strange and indescribable feeling. It felt as if she was not looking at a book but a sentient living creature instead.

“This thing… It’s definitely Garen’s most prized possession!” Raffaele gritted her teeth and turned her hand before removing a piece of thin red cardboard from the side pocket of her skirt. Clusters of strange symbols that seemed to be handwritten in blood covered its surface.

There were a total of three pieces of cardboard that were similar to this one. They were specialized magical tools that were equipped with short-term transmission functions. One of these precious magical tools could only be created with the heavy price of a sacrifice. Currently, the raw materials to create this item had depleted earlier on. They were only five pieces of this left which were all in the Lion Mother’s hands. In order to counter Garen now, the Witch King Mother, Lion Mother was willing to give her three of these items at once so that Raffaele could deliver these treasures to her from Holy Fist Palace.

“To be able to conceal it in such a hidden place…” she reached her hand out and pressed it against the wall before beginning to check for a switch there carefully. She just needed to remove the object and place it on the cardboard. Next, she would need to activate it gently so that it could be delivered instantly.

After probing for some time, she soon discovered a section of the wall that was slightly smoother and cleaner than the other areas. She outstretched her hand and dug it out gently before a little ring was removed from the wall suddenly.

She pulled it with all of her strength.

A faint buzzing noise could be heard before a large rectangular shaped stone block immediately protruded from the wall automatically. A cylindrical metallic pillar was embedded in the middle of the stone block. There was a ring that could be pulled on the pillar.

Chapter 755: Bureau 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Raffaele walked forward and checked if there were any switches around the ring carefully. When she had determined that she was correct, she prepared herself to extend her finger and grip the ring.

Woo…! Woo…!

Suddenly, the sound of an alarm could be heard clearly throughout the entire Holy Fist Palace. In only a few seconds, all of the training scholars, disciples, external trainers, and Middle and Upper-level members were all rushing towards the biggest training hall in the center of the palace.

While the sound of close footsteps echoed, groups of internal palace members in black and white uniforms passed by the hidden room frantically.

The main door of the hidden room had been resealed long ago but Raffaele had exited the hidden room without anyone noticing. She currently stood in the doorway, looking as if she had just happened to be passing by.

“What happened?” Raffaele pulled over an internal palace member disciple whom she had met earlier.

“It’s definitely a serious problem. Otherwise, Holy Fist Master would not have sounded the emergency assembly command!” the person answered frantically with a solemn look on their face. “Come with us to the training hall in the center if you want to know more.”

“Serious problem?” Raffaele’s heart stirred. She glanced at the corners and surroundings of the palace where white monitors and surveillance cameras had extended out suddenly and were beeping there. These surveillance cameras were almost the same color as the walls, making it extremely difficult to distinguish them. It was obvious that they had all of the security systems were activated immediately because of the critical state.

She congratulated herself unconsciously. If she had hesitated earlier and left slightly later, she would definitely have been detected by the monitors. At that time, it would have been impossible for her to escape as she was a member of the enemy camp.

Without much time to think, she merely nodded.

“Show me the way, we’ll go together!”

The other person nodded and pulled Raffaele along before rejoining his team in front. The footsteps of groups of people who were running echoed throughout the corridor behind him.

****************

Inside the white round arch-type stone hall

White cylindrical stone pillars stood upright throughout the area while steel chains hung from the center. Dark green chains that were thick but nimble matched the simple style of the large stone brick floors. They gave off an unsophisticated but rough look that felt barbaric yet divine.

Each of the stone bricks on the ground was actually a large brick that was more than three meters wide. Perhaps it was unfitting to call them bricks anymore, as they were more like a typical large rock.

Groups of scholars and internal palace members flowed through the area in one direction like streams that met at a lake. They gathered inside the hall here from entrances of different sizes before quickly forming three square formations with different uniform colors of white, black, and red.

Bright light cascaded inside from all four stone walls, shrinking everyone’s shadows to a position that was below their feet and shining so that there were no blind spots.

Soon, almost all of the members were present.

Garen sat on the highest seat in the stone hall. There were two empty black high-back chairs below right below the level of his arms. Below that were the seats of the Four Major Generals while rows of seats were specially set up on the right. The ones who sat there were the other high-level important diplomats who were temporarily stationed here. Besides that, there were a few other generals and high-level leaders of organizations. Rod and his older brother were currently chatting in low voices with another director and leader of an organization, who seemed as if he had just gotten into his seat.

The Four Major Generals sat down quickly while the crowd of Middle and Upper-level internal palace members and the other external members below them took their seats in the lower rows according to the ranks of their posts.

Meanwhile, a few of the higher level members of the Lightless Alliance who were constantly stationed here entered the room as well. They were arranged to be seated in the VIP seats on the right side of the hall at the same level as the Four Major Generals.

As the number of people increased, the stadium-sized hall finally quietened down gradually, displaying the members’ exceptional discipline. When most of the people there became silent, the VIPs who were whispering to each other quietened gradually as well before their gazes were focused on Garen who was seated in the highest position.

Garen was fully dressed in black clothes while his long golden hair cascaded down his shoulders. His body sat upright on the seat like a large mountain, giving off a terrifying imposing feeling. His expression was cold as if he was thinking of something troublesome.

The atmosphere was somewhat heavy for a while.

When the final member entered, the whistling alarm noises finally stopped.

The entire hall finally fell into a state of complete silence.

There was a moment of silence while Garen waited for everyone’s concentration to be focused on him before he began to open his mouth slowly.

“I am about to issue some unfortunate news here today.”

The initially heavy atmosphere suddenly became even more tense when that sentence was spoken. Everyone focused their attention on Garen unconsciously. Even the VIPs who were being absent-minded earlier had now sat up slightly straighter with stern looks on their faces.

Raffaele had also been seated in the VIP section. She glanced at Garen who was seated at a high position quietly while an abnormally powerful force spiraled around that man’s entire body. The air around his seat seemed as if it was sticky together densely. Although he was seated there alone, his force field was apparently suppressing the momentum of everyone in the hall!

It was worth mentioning that there were almost a thousand people here!

While fearful feelings were trembling in her heart, she heard Garen continuing to speak.

“One of the two great Marshalls, the Bloody Marshall Dahm was unfortunately killed in battle outside.”

At first, the entire hall fell silent at once. It was a deathly type of silence as everyone was convinced that they had misheard or that Garen was merely joking.

Moments later, the attention of the crowd of a thousand people had fully focused on Garen again.

“None of you misheard me,” said Garen casually. “I wasn’t joking either. Dahm has died in battle.”

His voice trailed off. The first person to react was Dahm’s underling in red clothes, who was also his division subordinate and a member who was born to his own clan.

The next ones who responded were the superiors from the VIP section who had the most interactions with Dahm. The others were the scholars and disciples who had learned the Royal Fist Technique from Dahm.

Boom!!

The entire hall seethed with shock and hubbub instantly.

Dahm had died in battle! An individual who possessed peak standards had actually died in battle outside?

Who could kill him? An Upper-level? Maybe a Death Apostle? Was it possible that the Blood Breeds had officially launched a full-scale ambush attack against Holy Fist Palace?

Everyone was making assumptions. For an expert who possessed an Upper-level strength to die in battle, neither Blood Breeds nor Witches would be able to endure such pain, much less a new member of Holy Fist Palace.

“I haven’t finished speaking,” Garen waited until everyone had digested the news somewhat before he opened his mouth again. “The main reason that Dahm died in battle has nothing to do with the encirclement of the Blood Breeds.”

His gaze scanned the entire hall and everyone who felt it lowered their heads unconsciously.

“He was killed by his fellow Marshall Hochman. Hochman has currently betrayed and fled Holy Fist Palace.”

Boom!!!

When he finished speaking this time, an even louder uproar exploded through the hall. Everyone looked at him with widened eyes and gaping mouths when they realized that their minds were unable to keep up with these changes.

Other than Holy Fist Garen and Tu Lan, the other two strongest Marshalls in Holy Fist Palace had disappeared completely. One of them was dead while the other had fled?! This was simply the latest piece of sensational news. If a reporter was on the scene, they would be able to sell so many copies of the newspaper at the first instant that everyone else would be green-eyed with envy.

It was worth mentioning that among the regular humans, Holy Fist Palace was currently the highest ranking force against the Blood Breeds that most people paid attention to. Furthermore, it was also the assembly point of the hope of all of humanity.

The current question was, how would they sort it out?

That was the first reaction that anyone would have when they heard the news at the first moment.

“My decision is to release commands for a counterattack on all fronts from now on. We will put up wanted signs for the Boxing Overlord Marshall Hochman and set a confirmed reward of one million euros for anyone who is able to provide information regarding his whereabouts. Those who are able to injure or kill him will be rewarded with ten million euros. Furthermore, I will personally guide them in the ways of the Fist Techniques once and increase their lifespan by two years. If someone is able to defeat him, I will personally teach them the refined meaning of the Royal Fist Technique before adding ten years to their lives.”

Garen’s voice sounded like thunder that echoed throughout the inside of the hall endlessly.

“Regardless of whichever methods you use and whatever measures you take, you must find him! Kill him!”

Murderous intentions that resembled dark clouds rose up in both of Garen’s eyes. These murderous intentions crept around the room and made it difficult for the thousands of people inside the stone hall to breathe. Everyone was secretly terrified of his wrath.

Scorching hot flames burned in the eyes of the Four Major Generals. They were the only ones who understood the severity of Garen’s words. It was obvious that Hochman had not simply killed Dahm. Instead, he had done something to anger Garen as well. Under these circumstances, if he was able to achieve his goal, his position in Master’s eyes would surely be increased by a large degree. Master Garen had spent many years helping both of these Marshals increase in ranks from earlier on. He would only need to work a little harder to find new people to fill in these new ranks.

Although they merely possessed Middle-level powers and were far from the two great Marshals, victory and defeat were not merely decided by strength many times. Otherwise, everyone would be able to discover the strongest person within the realm easily, and what need would there be for them to compete in training then?

Tu Lan stood in the shadows of the hall and exchanged gazes with Quentin and Xander of the Four Major Generals. Both of them were in charge of one information branch respectively. One of them was responsible for the strength networks in the external combat club, though both possessed networks of strong forces. During the recent period of time, as Quentin and Xander were both occupied in learning the Fantasy Fist, they had become good friends with Tu Lan and Ninox when their interactions had increased. Of course, Tu Lan would never treat herself as their senior…

Then, the few of them exchanged glances. All three of them had reasonably good relationships with one another. When they heard about Garen’s reward, all of their hearts were stirred immediately. The other rewards were good, but the prize of additional life force was an unquenchable and unattainable desire of numerous outsiders.

This was an opportunity to lengthen their lifespan and improve their bodily functions without any harmful side effects! The eyes of a few old high-level organization leaders had lit up while their minds now burned with a passion.

Money, martial arts knowledge, and life. A combination of these three things had stirred the desires of everyone in the hall as it encompassed the deepest yearnings of the majority.

This was the first time Garen had mentioned the opportunity to add ten years worth of life force. The maximum amount was only five years in the past. However, he had now increased it to ten years in one go. This was equivalent to extending one’s lifespan by ten years. Especially for older individuals, the ability to live for another decade was simply a dream that could wake them up with a smile.

When the sound of his voice trailed off after the final sentence, he was met with an enthusiastic response at once that came from the seats of the VIPs and the Four Major Generals.

“Master, we’re willing to form an alliance and cooperate with Master Tu Lan to move forward and attack!” Quentin stood up suddenly. It was obvious that she was secretly inspired by Tu Lan.

Tu Lan played a subtle role in Holy Fist Palace. She was higher than the Marshalls but lower than Garen. No one objected to the rumor that she was the second strongest person in the palace. However, the outsiders knew that she had betrayed the Blood Breeds to come over. They did not trust her very much while only a few superiors were aware that Tu Lan probably only remained respectfully because she was tired of being cowed in the beginning. However, she had truly learned to love the practice of Secret Techniques now and her fear towards Garen gradually turned into awe. After she had slaughtered Blood Breeds whom she once recognized as her own people, it did not matter that she gave her reputation away as she had already joined Holy Fist Palace fully.

With Tu Lan there to perform the task, Garen was able to relax slightly. However, Hochman had absorbed Dahm’s Primer now and no one knew which stage he had grown into. Moreover, if that external force appeared again…

“Alright, but you’ll need to inform me right away if you receive any news of his whereabouts.”

“Understood!” Quentin and Xander smiled happily and withdrew quickly. It was obvious that they were acting swiftly before going to prepare to leave and collect information immediately.

Garen narrowed both of his eyes. That external force could apparently grasp the movements of Hochman and the others accurately. It was likely that they had an extensive intelligence network. Therefore, they would definitely have a source that informed them about the movements of the troops within his Holy Fist Palace as well. Furthermore, he was unsure whether the strength of Tu Lan and the other two people were enough to suppress Hochman.

It looked like he still needed to take action personally…

Chapter 756: Bureau 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!!

On top of a snowy mountain peak somewhere in Iceland, chunks of snow exploded like bombs and scattered snow everywhere. Looking from afar, an entire right chunk of the snow peak had been blown away, looking similar to a sugarcane that was bitten off.

The top half of the mountain crashed down and fell onto a plateau below, causing the ground to tremble.

The sky was clear without a single cloud but the sunlight did not provide much warmth. The sunlight shone on the exploded part of the mountain peak. There was a dark cave there.

There was a hint of green smoke coming out of the cave. That green smoke swirled around at the entrance of the cave and before it quickly dispersed as though it was a living thing.

Cough cough cough…

A slight coughing sound came from the cave. It seemed to belong to an old man’s voice.

A moment later, an old figure with a white beard slowly walked out of the cave. He was leaning on a thick white cane and dressed in shabby clothes made from hides and skins. It seemed to be a patchwork of many different kinds of animal hides. There was a necklace made from shrunken human skulls hanging on his chest, giving off a primitive impression.

“Finally got out…” the old man groused. His face was lined with wrinkles like the bark of a tree. His hair and beard were a mess like the mane of a lion, totally unkempt.

He put his free hand by his mouth and blew.

Piiii!!!

A sharp whistle sound traveled through the cold wind.

After some time, a black dot was flying in the sky in the distance.

The black dot gradually came closer until its appearance was revealed. It was a big black hawk that had a wingspan of over four meters without a tinge of other colors. In the eyes of the black hawk was the strange old man at the bottom. It gave off a loud screech and flew down towards the old man.

A shadow flashed by and the old man was sitting on the back of the black hawk before it had even completely flown down. Then, one man and one hawk flew away from the place.

A few days later, the Lightless Alliance that was growing in numbers sent out a message. One of their three leaders, AG, had finally come out in spring and successfully made a breakthrough to a new realm. Originally, AG was an Upper Level but after the breakthrough, he could only be a Death Apostle.

The Lightless Alliance, which only had two Death Apostle class experts in the ranked one Holy Fist Palace, now had another one. The Alliance had now become more powerful, to an extent that it was comparable to the Blood Breeds and Witches.

Especially the Witches which had now become the weakest among them. AG, who represented the wizards, had had a breakthrough. Did it mean that the wizards who disappeared from history had returned once more? No one was clear.

However, the one point that everyone understood was that Lightless Alliance had become more powerful. Supernatural powers combined with the powers of ordinary people. More and more humans, under the leadership of Holy Fist Palace, were constantly training in fist techniques. Every second and every moment that passed by meant the expansion of Holy Fist Palace and Lightless Alliance.

In this situation, the Blood Breeds had no choice but to make a move.

*********************

Deep in the Blood Alliance Headquarters

In the crimson underground, a number of huge spheres similar to glass balls floated in mid-air while moving around.

All the Death Apostle Blood Breeds except for Ashen were gathered here, occupying each of the glass spheres.

Wellington, Scarlet Moon, the female death apostle, the mysterious blonde man, and the last one was the Lion Mother. The Lion Mother’s real body seemed to be elsewhere, but she had projected through the sphere what appeared to be a virtual image standing in the sphere.

The five of them opened their eyes and looked at each other in the sphere.

“The hidden piece is in. The next step should follow the plan,” Lion Mother was the first one to speak. “The world has become more and more chaotic. If it is not put back on the right track, I’m afraid there will be unpredictable severe consequences.” While she was speaking, she still had a gentle and compassionate look on her face.

“Based on my recent observation, I felt that the original plan should be slightly altered,” someone gave a different opinion. It was the only female Death Apostle. She slightly frowned and stared at Lion Mother.

“I feel that, with Garen’s personality, even if we used his parents and relatives to threaten him, the most we can achieve is to perish together with him. Besides letting him cast aside any worries, there are no other uses.”

“Why do you say that? We can use his family to exchange for the benefits we need,” Wellington said. He was now developing new family descendants so his consumption was very large. Until now, his face was still greenish, evidence of his large blood consumption.

“Though there is that kind of scenario, according to my analysis on Garen’s past, this person was, on the surface, protective of his family but deep down he was an absolutely indifferent and rational person. I expect that threatening him using his family will not yield a good enough result worth sacrificing our hidden piece which we took so much care to insert,” the female Death Apostle retorted.

“Indeed, with Garen’s personality, he will likely go straight down to fighting us to the death. Even if we kill his family, it will only fuel the fire in his heart for vengeance. In the end, it will be a war that consumes both sides with nothing to gain except damage. In comparison, the Holy Fist Palace has a huge number of humans to back them up and their speed in restoring their power and forces far outstrip us. This not worth it,” Wellington also shook his head slightly and said.

“Say, Scarlet Moon, isn’t there someone on your side that has a very good relationship with Garen’s family? Is there a chance?” he looked at Scarlet Moon and said.

“I will not use such a despicable move,” Scarlet Moon said. He looked at him indifferently and closed his eyes, refusing to say anymore.

“Stodgy!” Wellington curse at him.

“I also agree with this view. Garen’s personality is not the kind that succumbs to threats easily. The most we can get out of this is a war to the bitter end. It will only remove his last worries,” the mysterious blonde man nodded in agreement, “My suggestion is that the hidden piece refrains from taking any action for now, so as not to expose themselves. They will be able to display the largest effect at the critical time.”

“I agree,” Wellington nodded and said.

“This is fine too,” Lion Mother nodded and agreed to this method.

*****************

Swish swish swish….

In the bushes that stood as tall as a man, several figures flashed by. They were all dressed in black and almost blended into the darkness of the night, like ferocious nighthawks.

At the front, there was a scarlet figure running with all its might. The speed of the scarlet figure was not slow, but the distance with its pursuers at the back was getting shorter and shorter.

When the distance was less than three hundred meters away, the scarlet figure came to a sudden halt and turned around. The moonlight revealed a cold and handsome man’s face. It was the person who had killed Dahm and successfully escaped, Hochman.

“Found me out so soon?” Hochman murmured at the few shadows behind him expressionlessly.

After killing Dahm, he put on a mask and escaped since he was sure to become a wanted man in the Lightless Alliance. With the large network that Holy Fist Palace had and the mysterious means of the Dark Colors Witches. Even if he had a breakthrough, he was tracked down without realization.

“Hochman! Die!!”

Several shadows flashed around him at that moment, just like petals of a black flower, and withdrew four sharp knives that were stabbed towards his waist from all directions.

“Nighthawk?” Hochman narrowed both his eyes and recognized the secret technique they used. It was Nighthawk’s improved version of Shooting Shadow Secret Technique. This secret technique of the Holy Fist Palace was the most involved in their outside work as it was specialized in high speed for assassination purpose. In order to achieve victory, they would use any methods available to them. These people who dared to come out to pursue him was obviously fierce and not scared of death.

The blade was absolutely untouchable because it was hundred percent coated in poison. One touch would spell his death.

“Die!”

Flicking both his hands, Hochman sent out one transparent wind punch after another in all directions and caused the blade to bend.

Peng!

He kicked the belly of one of the dark shadows and made him shoot out like a cannonball. How many forces did Holy Fist Palace send out to kill him? He intended to leave one alive for interrogation purposes.

Just then, he looked at the eyes of the four men wearing masks. There was no desire for survival reflected in the remaining three people.

“This is bad!”

Just as this thought appeared in his mind, he heard three bursting sounds accompanied by extremely hot waves.

Boom!!!!

Around Hochman, red and white flames burst out from the three figures. These fiery flame tongues surrounded Hochman.

The flames had a diameter that was more than six meters and their colors were strange. Looking from afar, they were divided into three layers of colors. The inside was white gold, the middle was pure white and the outermost was pale red in color.

The huge shock turned into ripples and spread out. Looking from far away, the figure of Hochman and the three people could not be seen as they were completely wrapped in flames.

The surrounding grassland quickly turned yellow and withered before turning charred and then into ashes with sparkles on them. They were blown away by the shockwaves and some glued themselves to the surrounding grass, quickly starting another fire.

The flame lasted a few seconds before it slowly disappeared, leaving a huge pit behind. It was more than ten meters large and there was smoke inside.

Peng!

A dark shadow suddenly dashed out of the deep pit and flew into the distance, leaving behind afterimages.

Hochman felt his body boiling and his clothes were almost completely burned. There were large patches of burns on his body. The original handsome face had become unrecognizable and more than half of his hair had burned away.

This was the combined power of the modern science and secret techniques. Three death soldiers with special explosives blew up themselves together. The power it brought was such that even a Death Apostle class like Hochman would receive grievous injurious in a moment of carelessness. After all, he did not have the kind of terrifying physique like Garen.

Even then, the charred skin on Hochman was rapidly healing with a speed that was visible to the naked eyes.

“Such ruthlessness!” Hochman endured the pain and sped away. Even if he was a Death Apostle class, the Holy Fist Palace was not an ordinary force. There was still a real Death Apostle, Tu Lan, there. Not only that, apart from their life force that was close to immortal, the actual gap in strength between the upper level and them was not that large. He was not a secret technique expert that was specialized in speed, hence if he was surrounded with a range of technology to delay and interfere with him, not even he could escape.

“Surrender quietly, Hochman!” a voice came from far away. It seemed to be one of the top Nighthawk members. He could not remember clearly but it was not important right now. What was important was the shrill sound on top of his head.

Swish!!

A dark shadow suddenly flew over his head and Hochman felt a sudden threat from the sky. Looking up quickly, two torpedo-like white missiles flew at him with a shrill sound.

Chapter 757: Conspiracy 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!

The missiles exploded with a large shockwave and Hochman was blown away, rolling around on the ground.

Soon, there were shrill sounds once again and a few missiles raced down from the sky like meteors.

After a few mechanical sounds, the second wave of missiles automatically burst into more than ten warheads. They aimed for Hochman, including all of the possible places he could dodge.

Peng peng peng peng!!…

Amidst a series of explosions, Hochman kept dodging at a very high speed. The sparks from the explosion of missiles stuck to his body and kept burning. The fact that he could not even extinguish them spoke of his current disheveled condition. He quickly took off his cloak and hid from the warheads in the sky using the surrounding bushes.

“Lock!”

Suddenly, the roar of a female rang out.

As the sound of the roar swept past, a huge invisible force fell and pressed down on Hochman.

Roar!!

At this moment, Hochman shook his arms and the roar of a beast came from his shadow. He broke free from the invisible force and avoided the third wave of missiles in the nick of time.

**************

Holy Fist Palace Tactical Hall.

Garen’s eyes swept over the sand table in front of him. He was listening to the expert’s explanation calmly with an expressionless face.

The white sand table displayed a map of the entire Earth, forming a miniature Earth. On top of it, some important places were marked clearly with bright red dots.

Garen’s line of sight fell on the miniature Earth. The planet of this world was also named as Earth.

There were three red dots flashing on the Asia and Europe region. These represented the Holy Fist Palace’s confrontations with the Blood Breeds within these two regions.

The rest of the regions in Asia, Africa and America were relatively calm. However, there were patches of red in some places in Asia like red oil, indicating that these places were also in conflict with the Blood Breeds, just that the scale was much smaller.

“In Asia, the red regions represent requests for support but the level of skirmishes are small and Headquarter has sent reinforcements there. Together with the local forces, there will be no problem in keeping the situation under our control.” the Intelligence Department’s personnel giving the explanation was a cool beauty wearing a black uniform with flesh-colored stockings. She was currently quickly going over the general situation for Garen with a serious expression.

“According to the latest news from our Intelligence Department, our focus is on the flashing red points, especially Europe where the Blood Breeds are deeply rooted. Their initiative to attack us is most likely a cover to attract our attention from something,” the female official said.

“What about the pursuers’ team?” Garen asked.

“They’ve caught up but Hochman is very tenacious. We’ve sent four bombers and a team of Special Forces with full cooperation from the Palace’s fighters and support from Dark Color witches.”

“Are there any other problems?”

“No, all other locations have enough support. The only thing the Holy Fist Palace has to do is to make up for their lack of Special Forces combat personnel. The Blood Breeds are only strong in special warfare. The local forces can still hold their own when facing them head-on in the battlefield. Taking out their speed and hypnosis, the so-called Blood Breeds only have slightly thicker skin and longer lifespan,” the female official said confidently.

“Who’s the current base commander in America?” Garen’s fingers gently tapped the America region on the miniature Earth.

“It’s United States’ Army’s Lieutenant Strong that’s responsible for dispatching troops.”

“Ask him to make preparations, as the Blood Breeds will protect Hochman,” Garen said.

“Are you saying the Blood Breed’s large movement is a cover for Hochman, forcing us to dispatch a large number of forces to guard against them?” the female official frowned.

“It is possible.”

Garen took a final glance at the miniature Earth. The flashing red dots and regions were still eye-catching.

“Let the mobile team get ready to move out.”

“Yes, sir!”

*****************

One week later….

The border of Canada, United States.

Hochman was running for his life. Above him came the sound of combat aircraft. Previously, an army from Canada had retreated after some discussion. Apparently, this operation to search and destroy received permission even across the border.

During this one week, Hochman had experienced, for the first time, the feelings of those who were hunted down by him in the past, along with Dahm’s experience.

He was continuously hunted and bombarded by the army, one group after another, and no matter where he fled, his position would be swiftly tracked down. The combination of satellite positioning and witchcraft did not allow him to find a place to hide and rest, forcing him to run forward without pause.

When he was hungry, he could only hunt and kill wild animals and eat their meat raw. When he was thirsty, he could only drink blood most of the time. There was no chance of grilling meat and boiling soup.

If he had not mastered the Water Bird Fist and invoked some strange and mysterious change in his body, he would have collapsed long ago.

“Hold on, just hold on a little bit more….” after one week of no rest while constantly being pursued, even Hochman had reached his limit. He forced open his eyelids that were about to shut any moment and rolled away on the spot. Behind him, an air-to-ground missile exploded… or was it some sort of anti-aircraft weapon?

These days, he was getting used to the continuous stream of army weapons with great power. The clothes on his body had become rags, the hair all over his body had been burnt off, his skin was blackened and there were burns everywhere. It was all thanks to these weapons.

Even though his physique had become very special, enduring all the attacks up till now had rapidly weakened his recovery rate.

However, from the moment he made the decision to kill Dahm, he had anticipated this kind of consequences. He had always suspected that the reason he was hunted down was not due to killing Dahm but to the appearance of the mysterious person, who had snatched something from his teacher, hence allowing Hochman to escape his control.

Nonetheless, he had decided to snatch the mask, and such a result was naturally within his consideration. He had arranged for subordinates that were absolutely loyal to him to secretly contact the Blood Breeds. The Blood Breeds should have taken some kind of action.

Both legs mechanically moved at a fast pace while doing all sorts of evasive actions. Behind him, Gatling guns swept over the ground, causing mud to splash around.

Hochman was unmoved and sped forward. At the end of the bushes was a dark and damp jungle where the light was dim. It was the best place to escape his pursuers.

As long as he entered the jungle, the pursuers would have a hard time to chase after him. This fact made Hochman felt relieved.

But at this moment, a familiar figure suddenly appeared before the jungle.

Pa pa pa!

A series of searchlights formed a blinding beam of light and instantly enveloped Hochman in the middle, forming a huge square.

The dazzling light temporarily blinded his sight.

“Hochman, don’t struggle anymore,” the person in front of the jungle had a good proportion. She wore a red silk cheongsam which revealed her long, curved legs in stockings. Her red hair cascaded downwards and her beautiful face gave off a cold feeling.

The combination of her charming and cold temperament gave off an inexplicably strong and fierce aura.

Especially that pair of apricot-red eyes, which exuded a crystalline beauty under the reflection of the white searchlights.

“Quentin,” Hochman suddenly stopped and stood in the center of the searchlights. His face was haggard and his original handsome countenance was nowhere to be seen. Even his voice was hoarse as he had not drunk water for a long time.

“You have never won against me. Get out of my way, I don’t want to kill you.”

A hint of contempt flashed through Quentin’s eyes.

“The current you is not in top condition.”

“You really want to go against me?” the only spot on Hochman’s body which could be considered clean was his eyes. He stared at Quentin warily, though the whites of his eyes were bloodshot.

“Not me, but us,” Quentin smiled. Immediately, a person walked out from the jungle behind, wearing a white uniform upon which the word “Holy” was sewn into the chest. It was the standard clothing of the Holy Fist Palace.

The person had spiky hair, his body was taut with muscles and the shape of his body was similar to a bear. Even so, the steps he took were silent, which was oddly contradictory.

“Xander…” Hochman recognized that person with one glance. He was one of the most powerful combatants in the Combat Club’s first batch; one of the Four Major Generals, Xander.

“Hochman, why did you betray us?” Xander asked coldly.

“Betray? This is not betrayal,” Hochman laughed. “I am not willing to stay under other people for eternity, and my life is not destined to be used as someone else’s lapdog!”

“You fool!” Xander said coldly. “Teacher had delegated all the authorities to us, especially you and General Dahm! I didn’t expect that you were still not satisfied. Did you think you could replace Teacher’s position?”

“Why can’t I?” Hochman grinned. He suddenly disappeared while being surrounded by searchlights and rushed towards Quentin and Xander.

Boom!!!

Just then, a flame pillar burst out from the ground into the sky in front of Quentin and Xander. The flame pillar had blocked Hochman’s path.

“Kill him!!” Quentin shouted while pulling Xander and retreating.

In the jungle behind, flame tongues lit up his surroundings and countless bullets flew towards Hochman. All these bullets had undergone a special process using heavy metal as materials. As long as the bullets penetrated the body, it could cause heavy metal poisoning. Some of the bullets even carried explosives which could explode and deal heavier damage after piercing the target.

After a short time, the bushes of the jungle were smashed to pieces and some places were soon lit on fire.

In the storm of bullets, Hochman dodged left and right and impressively, not many bullets had hit him. After a few evasive moves, he leaped towards Quentin and Xander.

“Let me!”

Xander was not afraid and stepped forward.

With a standard horse stance, he unleashed a punch.

Peng!!!

Fist against fist. Hochman and Xander both trembled. One flew back and tumbled to the ground while the other retreated a few steps with a red complexion.

“Again!!” Xander roared and rushed forward bringing a burst of wind with him, like a tiger that was descending down the mountain.

At this time, the surrounding ambushing gunmen had automatically stopped their actions, awaiting the results of the brawl.

Xander rushed forward aggressively and from his waist, he delivered punches one after another like cannonballs. Fierce explosive forces were unleashed without restraint. The muscles all over his body had also twisted and tightened like wire.

The steel-like fists were launched towards Hochman one-by-one but they were countered with the same force by Hochman. The current Hochman had reached his limit. He could not even let out aura to suppress his opponent. In his struggle, he could only barely exchange punches with Xander. Yet it was in this way that more and more internal injuries were accumulated.

Chapter 758: Conspiracy 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The one week without rest was filled with explosions that could come from anywhere at any time as well as various means of attack that ranged from concealed poison needles to long-range sniper attacks, and carpet bombing to napalm bombs.

The slightest slip of attention would lead to attacks from various high-tech weapons until he was confirmed dead.

Any intention of getting close and killing off the pursuers would be detected by the Dark Colors Witches and experts from Holy Fist Palace. They would quickly retreat and activate debuffs with various slowing effects to deny him any chance of closing in on them. They would only attack him from afar.

Under these conditions, he’d struggled and yet managed to kill off two mixed groups of witches and Holy Fist Palace experts. However, even more of them appeared. Squads of death soldiers had emerged; a lot of them were criminals on death row that were released just to get close to him and detonate themselves.

He felt as if enemies were everywhere. During this period of time, the thing that made Hochman most alarmed were not those experts from Holy Fist Palace or the witches from Dark Colors, it was those ordinary people.

They used various tricks and deceptions to design traps, landmines, animals injected with toxic poison, hallucinogenic gas and all kinds of powerful army weapons on him.

In this kind of situation, nevermind him, even all those veteran death apostle leveled Blood Breeds would feel a headache with all these troubles.

Previously, Hochman had almost eaten a rat that was injected with toxic poison. On the surface, there was nothing wrong with the rat but it was a poison was slow in showing effects.

“Die! Hochman!” Xander fought wildly. All the veins on his face were bulging and he was even laughing loudly. He tapped at a few points on his chest.

“Polaris Fierce Arts!!”

Boom!!

A surge of air burst out as Xander activated his secret techniques.

Xander grew and expanded by a fold and smashed his thick arms towards Hochman. The momentum was similar to a large hammer trying to smash him to a pulp.

Hochman hurriedly raised both his arms and slashed towards his surroundings.

“Profound. Dual Blade!!”

Two snapping sounds occurred. His knife hands sliced and melded two invisible air blades to form a perfect ring. The upper part of the ring went for Xander’s face whereas the lower part flew towards Xander’s legs.

This was the original Waterbird Fist Profound’s Dual Blade.

Even if it was the currently exhausted Hochman who activated the secret techniques, the slashes still had the sharpness of a real blade.

Clang!!!

Too late to change their techniques, their attacks clashed against each other.

Xander’s arms destroyed the upper half of the air blade and hammered down on Hochman’s shoulders. The huge impact crashed down and the sound of breaking bones was heard.

At the same time, both of Xander’s legs were unable to dodge the air slash and were hit directly, tearing through his pants and left two bloody wounds.

Ah!!!!

Xander howled and quickly retreated while staggering. One of the subordinates quickly grabbed hold of him. His body reverted to normal, but his thigh had been cut deeply into by a finger’s length, almost cutting off his legs completely.

On the other hand, Hochman simply shifted his shoulders and set back his bones. Temporarily, it would not affect his actions.

He half-kneeled on the ground and coldly stared at Quentin.

“Just the two of you won’t be able to kill me,” he said.

“What if I join in?”

A lazy female voice sounded behind Hochman.

He jerked his head back and his pupils immediately shrank.

*****************

Armored vehicles sped down the highway. The streetlights flashed past one by one, almost connecting to form a neon yellow rope.

Garen sat in the first armored vehicle, looking at a laptop displaying a map with the latest information from the Intelligence Department.

The map still used red dots and red patches to indicate the extent of threats in different regions.

There were two drivers and the one dispatched to give an analysis of the map was a black male officer.

“Hochman has been surrounded in this area. Lady Tu Lan together with Generals Quentin and Xander have been dispatched there. They should have reached there by now. Of course, in order to catch our target alive and successfully retrieve the mask, our tactics are based on the objective of making our target fatigued and incapacitating him. Looks like the effects are quite good and we have successfully reduced Hochman’s combat capability significantly.”

“How significant?”

“His current combat power should barely be Upper Level, but in a situation where he still has to watch out for attacks from the surroundings, he should be at his weakest,” the officer answered.

“One week without rest and he still has so much strength. This is truly a surprise…” Garen held his chin and muttered.

He had a hunch that the hunt for Hochman this time to retrieve back his Soul Primer would lead him to the mysterious man that got Hochman to tear off the Soul Primer. What kind of person was able to do all these? He was feeling quite anxious.

‘Be careful. I got a bad feeling about this,’ Black Sethe’s voice sounded weakly.

“This is a conspiracy. From the moment my Soul Primer was torn off, I have no choice but to take action myself,” Garen said.

Black Sethe went silent. He knew what Garen said was not wrong.

If he did not reclaim the Soul Primer, he would have a fatal flaw. If he wanted to reclaim his Soul Primer, he had to kill Hochman himself. He only had these two choices, and there was no way around it.

Looking at the road and streetlights outside the window, Garen began to calm down himself and adjust his state.

*******************

At the sixth hour after Garen left the Holy Fist Palace.

The Blood Union sent out a large number of Blood Breeds armed with guns and other kinds of weapons to attack the Holy Fist Palace and its allies.

In just two hours’ time, the scale had escalated to an all-out war. A large number of casualties had occurred among both humans and Blood Breeds. The army had been dispatched, but the number of casualties still soared. The Blood Breeds deployed by the Blood Union numbered at least in the three digits, and their objective was to attack all the branches of Holy Fist Palace.

This represented that the Blood Union and Holy Fist Palace was officially going to war. The battlefield was mainly concentrated in America and the news reported it as terrorists waging their holy war and the army taking action against them.

The Dark Colors Witches Association was currently fighting against the traditional witches, but the strange thing was that the Death Apostle level members did not come out.

*******************

Tu Lan stood quietly behind Hochman. She wore a crisp white blouse matched with a pair of slightly washed out black jeans. Her long red hair was tied behind her head in a ponytail style, giving off an ordinary calm feeling.

However, it was this kind of calm temperament that made Hochman’s heartbeat stop for a second.

Although he had mentally prepared for this, when he was really faced with this terrifying Death Apostle Blood Breed that also wielded Fantasy Fist, he still felt an uncertain peril.

“You guys really overestimate me… Even Lady Tu Lan herself has come out…” Hochman gave a dry laugh.

“After combining with General Dahm’s yin nature Waterbird Fist, your fist technique should have reached an unimaginable level right? Looks like it has broken through to the Upper level,” Tu Lan’s expression showed indifference as she beckoned with her index finger. “I too broke through not long ago. Let’s both have a fair fight. The others will not do anything. How about it?”

Fair fight?

Hochman almost blew his top. He looked at the injuries all over his body. Right after he broke through the Waterbird Fist and reached the Death Apostle level, he had been chased down all over the place without any time for him to stabilize. After a week without rest, he’d then fought against Xander who stimulated his potential, adding to his injuries. He would be considered lucky if he had even half of his combat strength left. Now, he had to fight with a Death Apostle at the peak of her strength? He felt like the world had completely gone mad.

Tu Lan gave a smile.

“You don’t agree? Let me tell you a piece of news. The Holy Fist Master is on his way here. If you don’t grab your chance now, it will be too late to have a fair fight later.”

“The mask is with me. You guys don’t want it?” Hochman suddenly asked, taking out the eerie mask from his tattered clothes.

At this moment, Hochman’s expression showed surprise and his gaze moved to the mask in his hand.

Not just him, even Quentin, Xander, Tu Lan and other subordinates and soldiers’ gazes had all gathered on the eerie Sleepless Faces Mask.

Weng….

The mask trembled and the mouth part of the mask slightly opened.

“What is this…what’s going on?!” Hochman felt that he’d almost lost his grip on the mask. His other hand also grabbed on to the mask, finally suppressing its trembling.

“That is the mask’s resonance.”

Screams suddenly came from the jungle. The screams belonged to the soldiers lying in ambush.

At the same time, a clear male voice sounded from the forest. A man’s figure suddenly appeared behind Quentin and Xander.

“The mask’s resonance… The twelve masks, they are finally coming together….” another female voice suddenly sounded.

Without Tu Lan realizing, the enchanting figure of a beautiful woman walked out from the bushes on the right side of the crowd.

With the guns’ mechanical sounds, Tu Lan, Quentin, and Xander, together with all the subordinates they’d brought, aimed their guns at the people that had abruptly appeared.

The captain had a bad feeling. He looked at Commander Quentin and waited for her instructions. The soldiers here were specially selected Special Forces. Even in the face of such a bizarre situation, they did not take any reckless actions and waited for the commander’s instructions while suppressing their unease.

Quentin instinctively felt something dangerous enveloping all the people here. She looked at the current strongest person at this place, Tu Lan.

“Blood Union…” Tu Lan instantly recognized the scarlet Blood Union symbol on both of them. She also recognized both of them.

This kind of strength and this kind of atmosphere only appeared on a few people in the Blood Union. The only possibility was…..

“Death Apostles…..How did they appear here of all places?!” Tu Lan’s heart sank.

“That person was right, it’s here,” the female Death Apostle piped up. “How do we resolve this now?”

“No hurry, let’s wait a bit longer…” the blond male Death Apostle smiled. It was as though they did not notice that the surrounding gun muzzles were all aimed at them. “Garen will arrive soon…”

Compared to the tattered Death Apostle level Hochman, their identity as Blood Breed Death Apostles with immortal characteristics made them invincible. On the other hand, though Hochman had survival and combat abilities on the level of a Death Apostle, he was still a human. He still lacked the Blood Breed Death Apostle’s most powerful ability—immortality.

Chapter 759: Trump Card 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!

Thunder rolled in the night sky, accompanied by a flash of lightning. The grassland below was illuminated for an instant, turning it snow white.

This grassland was located somewhere at the border of Canada, and the United States was completely deserted now. Even the people at the nearest villages and towns had been relocated by the government’s army beforehand. There was not a single soul for hundreds of kilometers.

A gust of wind passed by. The grass which stood higher than a person’s knee waved in the breeze and produced swishing sounds.

On the grassland only tens of meters away from a jungle surrounded by mountains and hills, the grass there was currently ignited, brightening up the surrounding sky.

The flames spread with the wind, burning up towards the distant grassland.

A bunch of people was standing on the burnt grassland.

Hochman was surrounded by the people and soldiers from Holy Fist Palace. Quentin and Xander were staying focussed in order to deal with anything that might happen and Tu Lan was scanning the periphery.

Outside the crowd from Holy Fist Palace was a man and a woman leading another bunch of people. These people were all Blood Breeds and Vampires dressed in black with black cloth covering their faces, leaving their blood-red eyes exposed.

The atmosphere grew tenser.

“Tu Lan, why are you siding with the Holy Fist Palace when you should be a Death Apostle?” the handsome blonde man covered in black spoke.

“I just feel that compared to the Blood Union, the Holy Fist Palace was more suited for me. This is where I can pursue my goals,” Tu Lan answered seriously.

She did not lie. Only by staying at the Holy Fist Palace was she able to receive Garen’s Soul Primer, and at the same time, she had the freedom to train in Fantasy Fist and other Secret Techniques which gave her a new goal to pursue. As compared to the boring past where she simply ate and enjoyed life, this was far meaningful.

After tasting the pleasure of constantly getting stronger in the Holy Fist Palace, she would rather die than going back to her former life in Blood Union.

Now, she was also a Death Apostle, the same as the other side, she had the right to make her own choices.

“Are you really going to be standing on the side of the Holy Fist Palace?” the man frowned.

“Herein lies my goals, my dreams, not at the Blood Union,” Tu Lan confirmed. “Maybe I was unwilling yet forced to at the start, but it’s different now.”

“What a pity….” the female Death Apostle shook her head slightly. The number of Blood Breeds and Vampires in their surroundings were increasing.

However, the same was happening for the common soldiers on the Holy Fist Palace side.

Bomber aircraft and fighter jets were flying across the sky above them and the sound of helicopters grew nearer.

The Blood Union and Holy Fist Palace were both mobilizing troops on a large scale. The forces gathering in this small area were increasing in numbers and strength.

“Although it’s a little hasty, today is the day that Holy Fist Palace’s myth is broken,” the female Death Apostle looked up at the helicopters in the sky. A red light flashed by in her eyes.

Suddenly, a helicopter turned and violently crashed into the side of another helicopter.

Boom!!

Both helicopters crashed together and exploded, turning into a ball of flames.

In an instant, countless messages were spread through their communication channel and instructions for them to retreat were conveyed. The aircraft pilots quickly fled the area in horror.

Tu Lan observed their actions coldly without any sign of doing anything. She had guessed that the other party’s intention was to use Holy Fist Palace’s top members as bait with Hochman and the mask in his possession to lure Garen to personally come and rescue them.

Apparently, they had prepared something to deal with Garen.

At the same time, Tu Lan had the utmost confidence in Garen. As long as the Fist Saint came, any predicaments would not be able to stop him from advancing.

Hochman did not expect that things would develop up to this point. Without meaning to, he seemed to have become the trigger for war between the Blood Union and Holy Fist Palace.

He gripped the mask tightly and tried to restore his strength as much as he could. Unfortunately, he had pushed himself too much and he had not sufficiently replenished food and water, causing the recovery rate of his body to slow down. He could only barely prevent his internal injuries from worsening while stopping the bleeding.

“Now the mask is the only trump card for my survival…”

He could sense that whether from Holy Fist Palace or Blood Union, there were several lines of sight on the mask in his hand. Obviously, both sides had the intention to snatch the mask.

Swish Swish!

Suddenly, two more figures appeared beside the male and female Death Apostles. They were Wellington and Scarlet Moon.

One was dressed up in a white suit and the other looked as though he had traveled far and wide. He did not have the demeanor of a Blood Breed.

“Mongo, Marianne, everyone is here,” Wellington’s sight coldly swept the surrounding, “I’ll like to see how Garen can escape this time!” his expression was calm but the words he uttered gave off the feeling that he was gnashing his teeth. Apparently, he was still holding the grudge from the time he was beaten black and blue.

“Don’t worry, we won’t let Garen return this time,” the blond handsome man said and smiled, “Holy Fist Palace, in the end, is short-lived, and today will be the day it’ll be wiped out.”

“Don’t be careless, Mongo,” Scarlet Moon gave him a look, then closed his eyes to meditate.

The other two no longer said any more words and closed their eyes to prepare.

The pressure given off by the four Death Apostles was like the ocean pressing down on all the people here, making it hard for them to breathe.

Tu Lan secretly activated the Fantasy Fist and signaled for everyone to get close to her before inching towards the weakest link in the circle of Blood Breeds.

Strangely, the Blood Breeds did not seem to have any intention of stopping them.

Tu Lan suddenly looked at the trembling mask and immediately understood.

“These Blood Breeds must have brought all the masks they’ve acquired here. They must have some sort of special skill to activate the resonance between the masks. If the mask was used as the bargaining chip, there is no need to worry that Master would not appear.”

“What do we do now?” Quentin and Xander whispered.

“Prepare to respond to any changes, as long as Master is here, everything will be alright,” Tu Lan said.

Half an hour soon passed by, the people from Blood Union remain unperturbed, showing their patience.

Just then, a great tremor came from the distance.

It was as if something was shaking violently but soon the tremor had quickly vanished.

“Here he is!” Scarlet Moon turned his head and looked at the horizon. At the gap between the hills, black armored vehicles were heading in this direction.

The vehicles came to a stop far away. It seemed the other side knew that the average person had little effect in this kind of fight.

With the opening sound of the car door, a tall masked man came down from the car. This man also had blonde hair but his eyes were not blood red. It was a clear dark blue.

The man’s attire was from the Holy Fist Palace. It was black with white edge embroidered with the word ‘Holy’ both at right chest and his back.

A thin and wrinkled little old man also got down together with him, holding a cane and wearing tattered clothes. He seemed as though a gust of wind could blow him away.

This man was AG who had just come out from the vehicle. He had just received the news about the war between Holy Fist Palace and the Blood Union and had hurriedly come. Not only him, there were also the experts from Lightless Alliance. The leader of Dark Colors Witches Association, Nasira was hiding in the vicinity, ready to lead her people to fight. They were preparing a very strong magic circle to act as support.

As soon as the two got off, the armored vehicles immediately evacuated. Apparently, they did not plan to stay behind on the battlefield. These armored vehicles looked tough and hard but when facing opponents on the level of Death Apostle, particularly the veteran Death Apostles, they could only be massacred. Their ability to control humans had reached the level where as long as their glance swept overhead, humans were likely to fall under their control.

If they did not hold back from acting against the people from the Holy Fist Palace, most likely Quentin, Xander, and the others would not have been able to wait until Garen’s arrival and would’ve been forced to commit suicide under their control.

The rain finally spilled down following the sound of thunder, giving off a depressing ambiance.

The night sky turned darker and the moon was hidden by thick clouds. The aircraft no longer flew in the air. Under this kind of weather, low altitude flight carried a very big risk and their effects in this fight were next to nothing.

Soon, a large number of human forces also received the orders to retreat. In such a battle, their bullets were not able to do anything to the veteran Death Apostles. Whatever missiles they had had difficulty in pinpointing their locations. The chances of damaging their allies were higher, and so it was better to withdraw their own people and plan their next move.

Garen and AG looked at the four Death Apostles from the Blood Union. He also saw Tu Lan, Quentin and the others in the encirclement and Hochman with the mask in his hand in the middle.

“The situation is a little complicated.”

“What are you going to do?” AG asked calmly.

“What the Blood Breeds want was just an opportunity to fight a battle to the death with me. They want me to willingly fight them. Without resorting to such means, they won’t get what they want,” Garen said. “The mask and the besieged people are used to threaten me. Of course, they may also covet the mask.”

He clapped his hands and two figures appeared behind him. They were both males wearing the white Holy Fist Palace’s attires. The two men carried a black sealed metal box and came behind him.

With a snap sound, the box opened. Inside were all the masks that Garen had collected up-to-date. One by one the masks stacked together and were constantly trembling. The trembling was not strong but strangely, the lips of the masks were slightly open and they were getting larger until they eventually became black holes that looked like they were howling. Even the mask that Garen was wearing was no exception.

“Sleepless Faces…the Blood Breeds must have brought all their masks here. Adding the mask in Hochman’s hands, altogether there are twelve masks,” Garen calmly said.

He looked at the potential points in his Attribute pane.

‘Strength 7. Agility 7. Vitality 10. Intelligence 12. Potential 33124%. Soul Limit 30.’

The two masks that had just arrived in his hands, gathered by Tu Lan herself, had provided him with a lot of potential points. Now that he had gotten himself more than three hundred potential points, he could upgrade his attributes by another margin. However, he hesitated and did not use them immediately.

Chapter 760: Trump Card 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Recently, he had looked back upon his past transmigrations. If potential points were the energy to be used as consumption for his body, then the experiences he needed to amass to form a Soul Seed were the potential points he used to upgrade his body to the limit, which were converted to energy for his soul and stored. This was a gathering process that was extreme to the limit, but this was also the only way for him to reach a higher realm.

There were two more important reasons as to why he did not immediately boost his attributes.

If he activated the Fifth Star and reached the highest limit for his attributes, then he would need to consume a large amount of life force. The little bit of vigor that Slaughtering Hands provided were nowhere enough. Once his life force was damaged, he could achieve a similar effect as restoration through supplementing his vitality with potential points.

Another point was that when he activated the Fifth Star, no matter how high the basic quality of his body was, the current highest limit for his body was at an average of 30 points. Since it could not increase, then it was much more useful as resources for recovery.

After the dispute in his heart, he looked up at the Death Apostles in the opposite.

“Let’s go, we’re going to meet some of the most powerful people in the Blood Union.”

AG grinned.

“This should be the century’s highest summit meeting…”

He quickly followed.

The night wind caused the rain to come down in sheets. The drizzle was like slanted lines pelting the people below.

Even so, no one dared to speak loudly at this moment.

Garen and AG walked closer and closer and finally stood on a hill, looking down on the Death Apostles.

This was an arrogant attitude but the Death Apostles did not show any displeasure at this. To think that the Death Apostles who were used to being arrogant in their daily lives were now being looked down on by Garen, yet incredibly, these proud Death Apostles did not show any unpleasantness on their faces. Instead, their expressions slowly calmed down and seemed even steadier.

The Blood Breeds opened up the encirclement and the people from Holy Fist Palace quickly got out and gathered behind Garen and AG. Upon Garen’s orders, even Tu Lan evacuated this place.

Very quickly, there were only the four Death Apostles, Garen and AG left staring at one another in the rain.

The only spectator left on the scene was Hochman, clutching the mask in his hands.

His body was stiff from being sandwiched between two great pressuring auras. The mask in his hand was still trembling as though it was trying to escape.

“The twelve masks are here,” the Death Apostle, Mongo spoke. “You did come for the masks.” He stared at Garen’s eyes on top of the hill without averting his gaze.

Yet, Garen looked indifferent to his words.

“Since you guys have spent so much effort in baiting me here, whatever means you have, use them all.”

Pa.

He stepped forward.

Countless shadows emerged from his feet. As though there were countless tentacles or tails spreading down the hill, they soon covered the area where the Death Apostles stood.

The rain was blown away by the impact of the shadows. The shadows were swaying, giving off a demonic feeling.

Weng…

Suddenly, the Death Apostle Mongo stepped forward. The ground where the four stood began to shake.

The earth was rent and countless cracks appeared. Lavas slowly gushed out from the cracks and formed ruddy glowing rivers.

Under the intense shaking, a blood-red longsword made its appearance.

The long sword was two meters long with a bloody eye etched on both the blade and the hilt. The blade was covered in black threads weaving into black roses.

Mongo smiled and reached for the hilt.

At this moment, the remaining three Death Apostles turned into lava and gathered on the sword in his hand, forming three rings that constantly revolved slowly around the sword.

“Final Holy Technique….Red Light Sky.”

Mongo raised the sword, with its tip pointing towards the sky.

Boom!!

With the sound of an explosion, a red bolt of lightning came crashing down on the hill where Garen and AG stood.

An intense red light shone and nothing could be made out for an instant.

Not even Garen could have expected that this attack would come from the sky.

Countless strands of red lightning wound around Garen and stabbed at his skin like swords. AG was pushed away by him at the first sign of danger.

Chi Chi Chi!

Suddenly, a white ring accompanied by dark shadows appeared around Garen and instantly broke through the red lightning.

After the lightning dispersed, Garen stood there unharmed with his left hand stretched out. The transparent wind was swirling on his hand. It was a special skill that used high-speed vibrations together with aura.

This was a godly secret technique.

The original Waterbird Fist Profound Dual Blade.

Although they were the same Dual Blade, the effects produced by Garen and Hochman was as different as heaven and earth.

“Red Light Sky… It’s finally presentable…” Garen slightly shook his hand and the cyclone around his hand flew out and expanded in mid-air, increasing its rotary speed and turning into a whirlwind of countless sharp air blades.

Clang!

Mongo waved the red sword and dispersed the air blades.

He leaped forward, heading towards Garen with his body almost parallel to the ground.

Surprisingly, Mongo did not concern himself with the fact that his final technique had been blocked. His body turned into a red line and appeared in front of Garen like a red streak of lightning with the tip of his sword pointed towards Garen’s abdomen. A dark red liquid-like flame wavered along the blade of the sword.

Garen stretched out his right hand and was about to block it before his instincts warned him of a crisis. Knowing that one hand alone could not handle the incoming attack, his left hand also stretched out.

“First Star!!”

Peng!!!

With a dull sound, a shockwave, revealed by the rain, spread out, accompanied by aura. Hochman, who was hiding nearby, took the brunt of the shockwave and coughed up a mouthful of blood. He flew and smashed into a hill, sinking into it. The mask also flew out of his grip and it headed straight for the masks in Garen’s box.

When Garen and Mongo confronted each other, Mongo did not show any expressions. With the red sword in his hand, his speed, power and combat mentality seemed to have been increased by several times, and even the recovery rate of his body had reached a horrifying point. He could still fight like this under the area that was suppressed by the Dragonshadow aura.

In this close combat battle, he waved the red sword and drew trails of bloody lines, fighting on equal foot with Garen who had activated the First Star.

In the fight between these two people, shockwaves rippled and the sound of thunder constantly shook the ground. If there were ordinary people here, just the sound of thunder could cripple their minds.

As time went by, Garen slightly gained the upper hand. His current strength was still slightly stronger than the opponent. After activating the First Star, he had fourteen points which were a terrifying level of power for the Death Apostle.

Boom!

Mongo received a hit and flew out. His face was pale and his chest was slightly sunken. Apparently, his chest had taken a punch.

While in mid-air, he crushed a red ball on the sword.

With a poof, the red orb burst open and turned into countless red dots of light, gathering on his body. At this moment, his body glowed red. It wasn’t truly a glow, but just a reflection of light from the sword upon his body which had turned bloody, as though he was a corpse that had been skinned. Looking from afar, it was as though his body was glowing.

The strength of the sacred weapon summoned by the four Death Apostles, Red Light Sky, did not lie in improving the overall combat capability but converting the supply of blood essence of the sword wielder into an eerie attack.

At the moment when the red ball was broken, a little bit of dark golden light appeared on Mongo’s sword blade. That light was only the size of a thumb and looked insignificant, but it gave off an extremely dangerous feeling.

He fell on a hill with a crashing sound and with both legs on the ground, he kicked off and charged towards Garen once again.

With this high-speed movement, Garen’s speed was not as fast as him and he had just gotten out of a crater. Facing this slash, the blade appeared instantly in front of Garen’s face and was about to stab into his head.

“Second Star…..” Garen’s both hands moved to stop the blade.

At this moment, there was a sudden pain in his head; a terrifying and massive mental force burst out from behind him. When the attack first made its appearance, it instantly appeared in his mind as though it was destined to hit when it appeared.

This familiar feeling….

An unprecedented sense of crisis suddenly appeared in his heart but Garen remained unmoved.

Since he knew there was an ambush, would he come here without making any preparation?

“Finally came out….” almost at the same moment when he was hit by the mental attack, Garen widened his eyes. A golden light flashed by in his pupils.

“Holy Phoenix!!”

The cries of a bird sounded and charged into a shadow behind him.

“Unlimited Holy Cry!”

There was a giggle and the figure of a slender girl flew out instantly from the shadow, landing a short distance away. She still wore the same short black skirt and black stockings. Her black hair fluttered and her face which was white as jade gave off an evil and mischievous feeling.

The mental attack of Holy Phoenix charged at her but was blocked by an invisible barrier. The two offset each other and produced a strong turbulence.

“Long time no see, Garen,” Nadia opened her right hand and a large slender long sword appeared in her hand. The large sword was dyed in blood as though it had just been used to kill.

At this moment, a dark golden light flashed.

Garen’s pupils contracted. Before him, the dark golden light on Mongo’s blade flew out and fiercely stabbed towards his forehead.

‘This is not a power that belongs to this world!! Dodge!!’ Black Sethe’s anxious voice sounded beside his ears, but it was too late.

Garen watched as the dark golden color flew towards him and hit in between his eyebrows.

The only thing he could do was to muster all the power in his body. The terrifying aura of the Fifth Star burst out.

Without a sound, a circle of black nine-headed Dragonshadow burst out with Garen at the center. The immense Dragonshadow aura surged and Mongo flew away like a fired cannonball, looking as though he had been hit by a giant truck.

Countless Dragonshadow gave off silent roars and instantly occupied an area spanning hundreds of meters in the rain.

Nadia smiled and looked at the Dragonshadow in the sky without making a move. The frenzied aura blew her long hair to the right. Gently stretching out her hand, she seemed to want to touch the Dragonshadow that passed by her side, her eyes showing a tinge of nostalgia.

“Only I, the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen, understood the will of Dragon King the best,” Looking at the dark figures in the sky, her lips curled into a smile. “Garen, you’re finished.”

Just then, the ground beneath her feet swelled and an unimaginably powerful suction force came out of nowhere, aiming for Nadia.

A large gray-black hand that was tens of meters wide rushed out from the ground and grabbed at Nadia.

Chapter 761: Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“That’s!?” The smile on Nadia’s face froze, and she tried to jump up, but she could not move her body at all.

Bam!!

The huge hand gripped her tightly and exploded. With one clear sound, waves of water and soil splashed everywhere, and for a moment there, nothing could be seen.

In the heavy rain, on the other patch of burnt black grass, Garen stood up once more in the midst of the dragon shadows and the chaos of the explosion.

There was a bloody hole about the size of a thumb in the middle of his forehead, and blood kept flowing out from it.

Reaching out his hand to touch the wound on his forehead, Garen licked his slightly dry lips.

“Nadia, so it was you… the person who could tear apart my soul primer, who set this ambush.”

Amidst the loud sounds and tremors, the Buddha Mother’s gigantic and gruesome body slowly bulged out from the ground.

This was a giant up to a hundred meters tall, and from afar, it looked like a black mud monster with three heads and six arms, similar to the Divine General Nezha from Chinese legend. The three heads each expressed a different emotion: happiness, anger, and sorrow. Each of the six arms held a different weapon: a bottle, a long baton, a dagger, a silk ribbon, a war axe, and a ring.

Of these, the mouth of the bottle was currently aimed at Nadia’s position, and it emitted a powerful suction power like that of a black hole. This was also why Nadia was fixed in the distance and could not move.

Buddha Mother, a terrifying killing machine from an unknown civilization. Even back then, Garen did not truly face the Buddha Mother head-on, it had been scared off by Garen’s Profound, the Flight of the Evil Phoenix, and thought that it was the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, that was why it gave in of its own accord.

Even Garen did not know what the Buddha Mother was truly capable of.

The hundred-meter mud giant stood underneath the stormy sky, several bolts of thunder blasting past its head, the sound of thunder rolling. It looked like a strange demon god in the night, unnaturally frightening.

Just then, one of the Buddha Mother’s hands was gripped tightly, keeping Nadia trapped tight. This hand originally held the silk ribbon, which was now floating around it on its own, functioning as automatic protection.

Garen was currently standing on the Buddha Mother’s right shoulder, watching everything happen in the rain beneath him quietly.

A Blood Breed Death Apostle was nothing to him, even if that Mongo gathered up the power of the other three Death Apostles, they could only barely draw with Ashen, so they had no effect on him. Perhaps he had been careless during the First Star, but if he was currently in fully-fledged Fifth Star mode, nobody could withstand even one punch from him.

“Nadia, how on earth did you descend into this world?” Garen’s gaze moved to the Buddha Mother’s tightly-clenched fist.

Rawr!!

With a whoosh, the Buddha Mother wailed out. A large hole had been pierced through the back of its hand, and a black shadow flew out of it, floating quietly in the air at exactly the same height as Garen.

The black figure stopped moving, revealing its face. It was Nadia, who had just been ambushed by the Buddha Mother. Right now her face was even paler, and a small stream of blood was flowing down her fair right arm.

“To think you could actually harm me…” Nadia licked her lips. She(1) was no longer a projection now, but the actual thing. Looking at the Buddha Mother’s giant body, surprise flashed through her eyes. “I truly have no idea where you could have found this antique, to think it still works.”

Barroom!

Lightning flashed past, instantly illuminating their faces.

Beneath them, the Death Apostles had scattered again, becoming individuals once more, and they looked up at Garen and Nadia in the sky weakly. Carefully, they retreated to a relatively safe space. Looking up at the gigantic Buddha Mother in the empty area, they all did not know what to say. A feeling of helplessness rose in their hearts.

“Is this the Holy Fist Palace’s true trump card? We messed up this time!” the only female Death Apostle murmured in a low voice, staring at that huge black shadowy giant. She suddenly felt as though she was watching a Transformers movie.

“Even the Final Holy Technique State could not kill him. This Garen… he is no longer human,” Scarlet Moon said softly. He looked extremely weak, all three Death Apostles had just used up all of their spirit and blood to power the Final Holy Technique, so that Mongo could fight, but even then, Garen could still face them head-on and blow them away. Although they had already guessed that they would be no match for him even if they joined forces, this result was still enough to turn all their faces pale.

“What do we do now? Where did that woman come from?” Wellington asked unhappily, of everyone here, only he hated Garen down to the very fiber of his being.

“Forget about that! We still have our final trump card,” Mongo said softly, looking at the giant Buddha Mother. “For this plan, that person had properly planned out the details with us, if even this trump card doesn’t work, then we…”

“What are afraid of? We can’t beat him, but he can’t kill us either! As long as the masks can’t be gathered, the Final Mask won’t appear!” the female Death Apostle interrupted him.

The four Death Apostles had lived for at least a thousand years, so looking at the huge Buddha Mother now, they were only shocked for a moment. After that, they recovered instantly, their long lives having made them unaccustomed to shock.

“How are your conditions now?” Mongo looked at the others, “What about the people we brought?”

“I don’t know, I think it’s time we retreated,” Scarlet Moon said quietly.

“Retreat? Hahaha…”

As the words rang out, a trembling figure appeared behind them, blocking them quietly. It was AG, and Tu Lan stood quietly beside him. Tu Lan’s fingers were dripping with blood, and that blood seemed to belong to Blood Breeds rather than humans.

“AG, what are you planning!?” It was still Mongo who spoke, he was the secret party’s most mysterious Death Apostle and the last to appear. It seemed that he was also the strongest, as he could speak on behalf of the other three.

“There are three of us, and you only have two Death-Apostle-level fighters, don’t tell me you plan on keeping us here?” he spoke in a low voice.

With a loud ‘barroom’, a tremendous earthquake came from the battle not far away. Garen and that woman had evidently begun to fight for real.

“If you were at your usual, full strength, I might not be able to keep you here. But now… hahaha…” A hint of hatred appeared in AG’s eyes, “Let’s settle everything, including our grudge from before, right here and now!”

Boom!

With a tap of his staff, the ground sank underneath him, and a huge semi-circular crater appeared. On the other hand, he shot in the sky, flying straight for the four Death Apostles, his body looking illusory and translucent.

Tu Lan also made her move at the same time, raising her hand and pointing it, a transparent water-like liquid flew out of her entire body, morphing into spikes that flew at the four of them.

The four Death Apostles scattered, attempting to run away in different directions, but a purple mist immediately rose around them. This purple mist rapidly gathered into several purple walls, completely surrounding the few of them in this forest.

“The Dark Colors Witches’ Purple Light Membrane.” Mongo’s gaze changed slightly, it did not seem to occur to him that the Lightless Alliance could have gathered all their members here in such a short time, completely ignoring the Blood Alliance’s assault on their other fronts. It seemed that they were dead-set on keeping the four Death Apostles here.

“Is there any point?” The hint of anxiety in his eyes faded, “You paid such a high price, just to kill us once?”

Death Apostles could not be killed, that was a natural rule that could never fail.

So no matter how weak the four Death Apostles were, they were still confident and unafraid, just looking at AG and Tu Lan with sarcastic eyes.

“Who said we just want to kill you once?” The hatred and pleasure in AG’s eyes became even more obvious. Lifting his chin, he looked at these four Death Apostles with an unprecedented gaze of madness.

“Seal!!!” he roared abruptly.

In an instant, countless waves of purple mist rushed out from behind him like tails, and strangely, there was a hint of pale gold in the purple mist.

**************

A deep cut appeared on the Buddha Mother’s huge chest.

It stumbled back, its feet sinking heavily onto the ground, like a giant in a swamp.

Garen stood on the giant’s shoulder, quietly looking at Nadia, who was floating in the air.

The heavy rain was getting thicker, the raindrops beat down on their bodies, but they did not seem to touch anything substantial at all. There were no splashes, as though the two of them were merely illusions.

Countless gazes gathered here through different devices, each of them shocked or disbelieving as they landed on the two of them.

Such a battle, in the eyes of outsiders, was no longer a battle between humans, but had already surpassed that to be the stuff of legends.

Right now, Garen had completely earned his title of humanity’s strongest Holy Fist.

And the person standing opposite him had power that was as terrifying and oppressive as the endless black clouds.

Their battle was being relayed to the higher-ups of secret organizations all over the world through all sorts of devices.

This was a battle that determined the fate of the world.

“With the way you’re training your secret techniques, this world is already beginning to repel you…” Nadia waved the huge sword in her hand carelessly, “You should never have come here.”

“You sure know a lot.” Garen’s expression did not change. He did not maintain the emission of his Fifth Star state, right now he was relying completely on the Buddha Mother to fight Nadia. He had only used the Fifth Star in that instantaneous explosion just now.

“Looking at you, I can’t help but think of the old me.” Nadia flicked her long hair lightly, her expression nostalgic. “The truth is I always wanted to kill you, mostly because you beat me a few times back then, so I wanted to save face. Thinking about it now, it was such a waste of time.”

“A Void Creature and a Void Pursuer, haven’t we always been sworn enemies? That is the True Soul vow we made to the Mother Stream,” Garen said calmly.

“That’s right, we’re destined to be enemies… So whenever I see a Pursuer with the potential to grow, I can’t help but want to destroy them,” Nadia smiled, carefree. “But thinking about it, this truly is a pointless battle…”

Her expression looked lonely.

“For the past ten thousand years, I’ve always been wandering in the Void, with no idea what I was doing… Pointless battles, one after the other, killing off so many Pursuers.”

Garen looked at her seemingly genuine expression, and did not know what to say. Up until now, he had barely lived for as long as the last few digits of her lifespan. So when it came to such a depressingly lonely life, he did not understand, neither did he wish to understand.

“What do you mean by talking so much?” The corner of his eyes swept across the Purple Light Membrane that had risen up in the distance, and he knew that the Lightless Alliance did it, while the Death Apostles were on the run.

“Your plan succeeded. They’re called Death Apostles, right?” Nadia was unperturbed as she asked with a smile.

“Since I’ve come to this planet, I should at least leave some proof that I was here. Wouldn’t you think so?” Garen replied calmly. “It’s true that the Death Apostles can’t be killed, but I can make them fall asleep, and stay asleep until the end of time.”

The rain poured down even more intensely.

The two of them did not have anything else to say for now, because the truth was they did not bear any grudges against each other.

After fighting for so long, be it Garen or Nadia, both of them had recognized the other’s power.

Garen could survive so many battles with her projections even as they grew stronger, while he grew more powerful each time. He was just like Nadia herself back then, with the blood and will of the Nine-Headed Dragon. Before she knew it, she felt as though she was seeing another version of herself, walking down another road she never had.

“The me back then failed,” Nadia spoke, “then what will happen to you, walking the opposite of the road I took…? I look forward to it…”

“Ominous Space Path!” She held up her giant sword flatly in front of her. The long silver giant sword began to distort, and several pitch-black dragon shadows appeared, swirling around it, emanating piercing wails and roars.

Translator’s Note:

Raws say ‘he’, probably a typo.

Chapter 762: Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This time, if you can still beat me, all the grudges and debts between us will be called off.” Nadia looked at Garen, who was not far away. Their battle had begun casually, then it grew frustrating due to her inability to descend upon him, then that turned to admiration and respect, and finally recognition. She had recognized him as someone worthy of the same title, a lord of the Nine-Headed Dragon.

Suddenly, she did not want to kill Garen that badly anymore. They both had the will of the Nine-Headed Dragon, she wanted to see just how far Garen could go with it.

Garen looked at her, having already vaguely sensed the changes in her.

It could be said that in the beginning, Nadia had coincidentally discovered his bloodline and thus decided to retrieve the will of the Nine-Headed Dragon by casually killing him. But after failing so many times, she seemed to have changed her mind.

“Come. Show me just how strong your true form is!”

Garen’s body abruptly sank into the Buddha Mother’s shoulder, following a crevice of mud that had opened up automatically, he arrived directly at the very core of the Buddha Mother, the control center.

The moment he sat on the seat, the whole Buddha Mother gave a huge jolt, a faint golden glow appearing all over its body. It had already been about a hundred meters tall, but now it grew even larger, copious amounts of soil flying up from the ground and gathering on its body, making its body seem even larger and more intimidating.

“Come, it doesn’t matter who wins or loses.”

Garen’s voice boomed like thunder, coming from the mouths of all three of the Buddha Mother’s heads.

In that instant, it was as though the whole Buddha Mother had become Garen’s incarnation. The two merged into one, the golden color of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures melding onto its body, making it even bigger and stronger than it had been way back in the underground garden.

Ker-chak!!

A bolt of lightning flashed past.

Nadia’s long sword also moved in that instant, there was no telling if it was lightning or the gleam of a sword in the night sky. But in the blink of an eye, the huge long sword had landed abruptly straight onto the center of the Buddha Mother’s chest.

The blade seemed to extend infinitely in a moment, and made the Buddha Mother shine with a crack like a white light from top to bottom.

Bam!!!

A gigantic baton landed with a crash, sending Nadia flying away. One of the Buddha Mother’s arms gripped a long baton tightly, with an explosive power that even Garen could not match.

With a low roar, the Buddha Mother’s giant body flew into the air, chasing after Nadia, its six arms all holding different weapons that it sent crashing mercilessly into Nadia at the same time.

Clang!!

The huge long sword emitted a sword gleam that turned into a giant silver sword, crashing into the six weapons one after the other. The Buddha Mother was actually fighting with Nadia in mid-air, the three heads and six arms turning like clockwork, while Nadia’s giant sword was also insanely strong.

Even more strangely, the wound on the Buddha Mother’s body from the Ominous Space Path was quickly being regenerated by the soil flying up from the ground, as though it was never wounded.

Garen sat in the center, controlling the Buddha Mother as though it was a peak-level secret technique master. It unleashed all sorts of attacks — grabbing, tapping, punching, holding, knocking — effortlessly, like a true martial arts master. Matched with the Buddha Mother’s six weapons with different effects, and it was practically a flawless, unbeatable war machine.

After a long time, the giant Buddha Mother and Nadia had both flown away from the original site of the battle, ending up in the sky above some unknown forest somewhere before they landed. Like an extreme coincidence, Hochman’s desperately escaping form just happened to appear beneath them. Watching the huge shadow descend from the sky, he threw his head back and roared in despair.

Baroom!

Many trees were squashed, and a large round crater large enough for two people to stand in had appeared on the ground. Hochman had already disappeared completely, turning into a mess of blood and flesh. A wisp of black smoke leaked out from beneath the Buddha Mother’s foot, darting into the Buddha Mother’s huge body.

Nadia’s body was covered in blood, she looked quite heavily injured.

And the Buddha Mother’s giant body was covered in wounds as well. Two of its arms had broken off, and one of its heads was gone. There was a large gash in half of its waist, which was rapidly absorbing soil and trees to recover itself.

Roar!!!

The Buddha Mother roared instinctively. The remaining two heads lowered, emitting a wind like a typhoon. The intense wind pressure instantly blew the grassy area where Nadia was standing into a crater shaped like a meteor.

Faced with the giant that was the gigantic Buddha Mother, Nadia held up her long sword again. In that instant, her eyes lit up.

Large swathes of shadow gathered behind her, forming a giant shadow Nine-Headed Dragon.

At the same time, as though in resonance, a black light lit up in Garen’s eyes from where he was sitting inside the Buddha Mother. Countless shadows like black oil extended from underneath him, these shadows quickly spread out from the Buddha Mother’s huge body, turning into nine dragon shadows of different sizes.

This was pure aura, and it also came from the battle of the Nine-Headed Dragon Wills. It had nothing to do with their bodies, just the connection between wills.

“Dragon’s Roar!!”

At nearly the same time, Nadia and Garen both chose the ability at the very core, in the deepest recesses of the Nine-Headed Dragon’s bloodline and will.

Two terrifying Nine-Headed Dragon shadows, each up to a thousand meters tall, raised their heads at the same time, and roared furiously at the other.

Roar… Brr!!

In the end, the roars simply became a sound of pure vibration.

The invisible tremor began with the two of them in the center, but instantly spread up to several thousand meters around them. All living creatures around them were instantly decimated by this huge spiritual tremor.

The giant python in the forest fell off the tree branch, utterly lifeless. The forest leopard tried its hardest and ran several steps away, but then it crashed into the ground head-first, and could no longer get up. The birds and black eagles flying in the sky stiffened instantly, and fell down like a rock, their bones shattering as they landed.

The moment that roar and tremor blew past, it was as though the large area of green grass and trees was covered with a layer of grey, filled with a silent aura of death.

In that invisible yet terrifying howl, the Buddha Mother instantly fell apart. It shattered into countless pieces, raining down everywhere.

The piece at the very core collapsed completely, and a black shadow flitted out of it, it was Garen.

All the muscles on his body were bulging up horrifically, as though forming armor plates on his shoulders. His body was several times taller than an average person, and he emitted a powerful aura, like that of a huge monstrous beast.

Falling down from the sky, Garen stretched out his right arm, and pressed down hard.

Bam!!!

Amidst a loud, deep sound.

That giant, boa-like arm crashed into a huge silver long sword.

Garen’s expression did not change, his left arm making a light noise like a flying bird, and somehow carried up a gentle, warm wind, with a vague sound like that of crisp wind chimes.

He instantly used the Waterbird Fist’s Final Profound, the Flight of the Evil Phoenix, with one hand.

Garen’s left arm seemed to morph into a giant flying phoenix, flapping its wings and carrying a huge, terrifying power and penetration as it rushed for Nadia.

At the same time, Nadia raised her left knee, and met Garen’s left arm.

There was another flash of golden light.

A circle of black shadows erupted between the two of them. The two huge shadowy Nine-Headed Dragons wrestled with each other, biting ferociously. In the middle of the shadows, there were Garen and Nadia.

Bam!!

Nadia was sent flying several dozen meters away, crashing past many trees and finally sinking into a mountain wall. Many rocks rolled off the mountain, nearly burying her whole.

“This is absolute power.”

Garen stood on the spot, his body as large and terrifying as a demon god.

The mask on his face had shattered completely by now, revealing the face underneath. Strangely, his forehead was currently covered in golden lines, like so many golden veins, and it made him look unnaturally gruesome.

The Holy Phoenix Scriptures state allowed his spirit potential to reach its explosive maximum for a short period of time, gathering in his aura, so it had an extremely powerful destructive power.

And right now, Garen in the Fifth Star state had already achieved the peak of this body. The deficiency in his soul had also been filled up, but to his surprise, there was no movement in his mind at all. The Demonic Book, that had been one step away, was now beginning to sprout after absorbing Hochman’s successful soul primer.

Once it sprouted, he would have truly created another Soul Seed.

“Black Sethe, do you see that? The second Seed is finally almost complete…” Garen glanced at Nadia’s direction, murmuring softly.

But strangely, Black Sethe did not respond at all.

Garen suddenly felt something amiss.

“Black Sethe?” he called again.

There was nothing. An ominous feeling grew in his heart.

Hah!!

There was a flicker of black light in front of his eyes, and Nadia suddenly appeared in front of him, slicing at him with her sword!

Blocking the blade with a clang, Garen’s other hand reached for her head fiercely.

Just then, the dragon shadow behind Nadia bit down on Garen’s dragon shadow.

Garen grunted once, and retreated several steps back, a piercing pain coming from his brain.

Steadying his footing, Garen called Black Sethe a few more times quietly, but there was no response.

Standing beside a field of tree stumps, he suddenly lost all desire to fight.

“To think that you still disappeared in the end.” He did not feel sorrow, just the same sort of sorrow he felt in the Totem World. He was left alone again…

Facing Nadia, he already knew the outcome of this match.

“There’s no need to fight anymore,” he said suddenly.

Nadia was also standing between the trees, covered in blood and breathing fast.

“You won.” She sat down on a tree stump, and raised her head. “Don’t want to fight anymore?”

“This body of yours is the main reason you descended here,” Garen said calmly. “This is not your body.” It was not her true body, meaning it could not be revived, it only had one life. It was simply one level stronger than a projection, that was all.

“You noticed?” Nadia laughed. “Let’s call it quits, then. That friend of yours disappeared? Hahaha… You feel it now, don’t you? Our very own Void…”

“Is this how you’ve been living for the past ten thousand years?” Garen asked softly, his body slowly returning to his normal height. Now that the victory had been decided, the two of them became like good friends. With no intention to continue fighting, they actually stood together and began to chat idly.

“It repeats over and over again, like a cycle. I’ve gotten used to it a long time ago,” Nadia said with a carefree smile. She was beginning to bleed from all the orifices on her face, evidently her internal injuries were acting up.

First she had fought the Buddha Mother, which, under Garen’s control, was equivalent to a larger, powered-up version of Garen, with terrifying power. After that, she fought against Garen’s true self with the Fifth Star. This body that Nadia had descended with could no longer take any more injuries, it was already on the brink of collapse.

“You win again this time…” Nadia looked up at the sky, “You have to be careful, that golden secret technique of yours will be repelled by the planet. As you are right now, there’s no way to resist that. Don’t let yourself enter the Void carelessly, the war between the Warlocks and the Void is about to start again…”

Sitting there, her voice gradually grew softer, smaller, weaker, until finally she was completely lifeless.

With a smack, that huge sword also shattered completely, turning into countless dots of silver light that gradually faded into the air.

Garen suddenly had a feeling, that perhaps it was about time to leave again. That powerful sense of repulsion was getting stronger, and he calculated the time. When his Soul Seed formed, that would be the time for him to truly leave this world.

Chapter 763: Settled 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The heavy rain flew in the wind, pouring down in spades. Visibility went no further than a couple meters.

In the torn-up forest, trees were bent and broken, the leaves mingling with the grass, all of it slowly growing purple.

In the middle of the forest, a large cloud of purple mist had directly covered up an area several dozen meters in diameter.

AG and Tu Lan stood next to each other in front of the purple mist, quietly watching the roiling mist inside. A stream of purple liquid flowed out from underneath both their feet, going straight into the purple cloud.

As the purple stream flowed away, the two of them also grew slightly paler.

“How is it?” Tu Lan asked softly.

AG’s whole body was drenched in the rain, the rainwater flowing down his hair and face, completely soaking his clothes, but he did not care at all. He just kept his eyes fixed on the roiling purple mist in front of him.

“We have gathered all this poisonous mist specifically to counter them over such a long period of time, and we also melted our Death-Apostle-level vital blood into power to suppress them, they should be unconscious right now.”

” hundred and twenty-eight poisons and hallucinogens specifically targeted at Blood Breeds, even I would not be able to escape that within a short period of time. Our witchcraft will probably be successful this time.” Tu Lan nodded. She had only asked so she could determine whether their plan had succeeded this time or not.

“I never expected it, I had even been a member of the Wellington family, but now I’m gonna make a move against my own clan chief,” she sighed.

“There’s a saying from the East, that water flows to the depths and people walk towards the heights. The old and broken should be eliminated, this is the natural selection of the new over the old,” AG said matter-of-factly. “Speaking of which, are you interested in becoming an Elder of our Lightless Alliance? Until now, we only have three Elders in myself, Garen and Nasira.”

“An Elder?” Tu Lan began to consider it.

From the battle with the Death Apostles just now, she could tell that AG earned his title as a witch equivalent in power to the Death Apostles. He had strange and unpredictable moves, took the initiative to rush forth for close-distance combat, but he also later lured the enemy into breaking ranks, allowing the purple mist to instantly separate the four of them.

Compared to Blood Breeds, witches with power equivalent to Blood Apostles definitely had many more moves. Although they did not have the immortality Blood Breeds had, their many different moves were also rather troublesome to counter.

Tu Lan thought about it, and at the same time, the black grassy plain that had been reduced the ashes and had fallen silent, began to ring again with light footsteps.

In the pouring rain, these footsteps were barely audible, but AG and Tu Lan were both top-level fighters, so they naturally could immediately tell where the steps were coming from, and they raised their head to look at that direction.

Through the veil of rain, a familiar figure was slowly walking towards them.

Blonde-haired and one-eyed, with handsome features, the clothes on his upper body had been completely stripped away, revealing powerful muscles. On his lower half, he only wore black slacks.

“Garen!” AG’s expression lit up. “You won?!”

It was not only him, beside him, Tu Lan looked rather happy as well. Garen’s appearance clearly indicated that he had won his battle with that mysterious woman from just now.

“How are things on your side?” Garen glanced at the purple mist, and felt the highly poisonous mist roiling inside, frowning slightly.

“This is the top-level poison mist I created, those four should have probably all fainted by now, their regeneration ability will definitely be drastically reduced by this,” AG said confidently. “Not only is this purple mist highly poisonous, it also contains the combined power of Nasira and the hundred witches under her command, so it is completely airtight and secure. There is no way they can escape!”

Garen nodded, and said no more. AG and Tu Lan wanted to ask him about that mysterious woman, but they did not know how to start.

Garen was also just waiting quietly for the purple mist’s time to end.

He had also guessed that the Blood Alliance would merge with Nadia, that was his worst case scenario, but he had prepared for it nonetheless. In the end, it proved useful.

The Blood Alliance had already thrown everything into this gamble, even their mysterious fighter who no one knew about was willing to join the Alliance, so it was obvious that they had gotten desperate.

“What about Ashen?” he asked quietly.

“There’s a good guy right there. No need to worry about him, as long as we don’t kill the Death Apostles, he won’t make the first move, he should probably be recuperating in Australia right now,” AG replied. “He’s already contacted me directly, the Blood Alliance has nothing to do with him from now on. I bet these guys from the Blood Alliance totally broke his heart, hehe…” He chuckled deeply.

“End it quick,” Garen sighed. Suddenly he felt bored of it all, fighting back and forth with the Blood Breeds was actually an exercise in futility. In his eyes, the Blood Breeds were no more than this world’s backwater natives, fragile and weak.

But thinking about the situation from before, Garen still perked himself up, and maintain vigilance.

After all, Madia had used this common understanding of theirs to hide her secret plan in the Blood Breed Death Apostles’ attack. It was exactly that Death Apostle Mongo whom he looked down on, that suddenly used something he could not control while attacking, and managed to wound Garen. After that, he was nearly ambushed by Nadia. If it weren’t for the Buddha Mother giving him time to catch his breath and lighten his injuries, that instant would probably have been enough to kill Garen in an instant.

A hole in his soul as well as a sneak attack wounding the middle of his forehead., if he did not have the Buddha Mother, he might truly have fallen right there and then,

Looking at the loud of purple mist in front of him. Garen raised his hand lightly, the shadow behind him abruptly elongating, turning into a wisp of black smoke that darted into the purple mist.

“Let me speed up the process.”

The assimilation of the black smoke into the purple mist seemed to give it a huge push.

This black smoke of Garen’s was actually the Slaughtering Hand Life Force that he had trained to preserve Black Sethe. By mixing this Life Force with his aura and emitting it to add it to the purple mist, he used the changes in Nasira and co’s witchcraft to turn it into a huge driving force.

In just an instant, the roiling purple mist grew a lot thicker.

Seeing such an intense change, AG’s pupils dilated slightly, but he hid it quickly. Beside him, Tu Lan glanced at him without her expression changing, but no one knew if she had noticed his expression. Once the Blood Alliance’s four great Death Apostles were sealed off and unconscious, the Blood Alliance would no longer be a threat, and the strongest power in the world would be the Lightless Alliance. When that time comes, the struggle for power…

As Garen joined in, the purple mist finally finished its process, and as AG and Tu Lan watched on, dumbfounded, the witchcraft that should have taken another half hour rapidly began to dissipate after a mere twenty-or-so seconds.

At the very core of the purple mist, there was a deathly pale sphere of roiling white mist, this mist slowly fell to the ground after the purple mist dissipated.

Bam!

The white mist sphere burst apart instantaneously, and immediately vanished without a trace. The four Death Apostles who had been there all disappeared, leaving behind a white stone plaque embedded into the ground. There were extremely complicated symbols and glyphs flowing on the stone plaque.

“Allow me.” AG took one step forward, his staff pausing after it tapped the ground.

Instantly, the purple stream under his and Tu Lan’s feet disappeared completely, and the black smoke that Garen shot out also flew back to him of its own accord.

Another pause.

The symbols on the stone plaque began to spin rapidly.

The last pause.

Pst-pst-pst-pst!!!

In an instant, the entire stone plaque broke apart abruptly, turning into four wisps of white smoke that shot off in four directions, disappearing into the veil of rain in an instant.

“It is complete.” AG heaved a breath, “There are specially-designed suppression tombs in the four directions, used to suppress the Death Apostles vital blood and Blood Nucleus, as long as we keep maintaining the poison supply, there’s no way they can wake up for another few thousand years.”

“Ashen is still around,” Tu Lan reminded him.

“As long as we have His Excellency Garen, Ashen is meaningless by himself,” AG laughed. “We have His Excellency Garen to thank this time for heavily wounding the four Death Apostles, otherwise we would not be able to suppress them this easily either.”

“Forget it, let’s go back.” Garen, however, did not look particularly happy. He turned away and walked into the heavy rain, the sound of an engine approaching from the distance, evidently the Holy Fist Palace’s army was rushing here.

AG and Tu Lan exchanged a glance, both slightly surprised. They had destroyed the Blood Breeds and suppressed them completely, this was a great deal, but Garen seemed kind of listless and disinterested.

But no matter what, AG still felt extremely happy. He had finally gotten his long-awaited revenge, and the troubles he had always kept in his heart were solved, so he felt unspeakably light.

***********************

Within a few short days, the people in power throughout all the continents and countries in the world had all heard of the battle between the Lightless Alliance and the Blood Alliance.

They had been controlled by the Blood Alliance before, but now they all saw the way things were going, and all turned to stand in line behind the Lightless Alliance. At that moment, thanks to mass propaganda against them, the Blood Breeds became the villains in the eyes of all. Some past events as a result of other triggers were also forced onto the Blood Breeds, in order the persuade the unknown and unknowing public.

The United Nations quickly declared a blood-sucking rabies epidemic one week later, and made all Blood Breeds, including vampires, examples of this epidemic. They even announced the features of this disease all across the world, and requested that all countries quarantine such patients, in order to prevent them from wreaking havoc in society.

According to the symptoms spread by the United Nations, the main characteristics of blood-sucking rabies included a pale complexion and eyes that turned red when the person was angry. The patient also needed to drink blood every so often. They also had mental problems, in that they would think that they were vampires, resulting in physical and mental confusion.

Immediately, the Holy Fist Palace and the Lightless Alliance sent their men out to help the governments catch these ‘blood-sucking patients’. The Holy Fist Palace found the Blood Alliance headquarters almost immediately. After Tu Lan took the lead and killed some stubborn ones, they absorbed most of the Blood Breeds from the old light party, and the extremist secret party members were mostly killed in secret. The global situation began to settle down.

**********************

Standing on the roof of a tall building, Garen’s hair billowed in the wind.

He was holding a cup of freshly-brewed green tea, there was still steam rising from it. Standing by the banister, Garen looked down at Washington at night.

The Capitol in the distance looked like half an upside-down cucumber, and was strangely funny. Under the illumination of the nighttime lights, the whole building was dyed platinum.

Beside the Capitol, there was a scattering of tightly-packed buildings, their light looking like sand in a desert, more lights than one could count. The different colors — red, yellow, white, and blue — wove together, with some black shadows in between.

The flow of traffic vaguely seen between the buildings was like a golden river, moving slowly but steadily, as though it was the pulse of the whole city.

Garen drank his sweetened green tea and looked down at the gigantic city below.

“What do you plan to do after this?” he asked quietly, in perfect Spanish.

Chapter 764: Settled 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What plans?” a man behind him repeated softly, “I’m doing very well in Spain right now. I found a school, and now I’m teaching children.”

A slender man suddenly walked out of the pitch-black shadows on the roof. The man was dressed completely in white, and had white hair. Even his skin had a translucent sheen of white. There was an indescribable sense of freedom in his eyes. He was completely different from when Garen first met him.

“This sure is different from the Ashen I first met,” Garen said mildly.

“I really like this kind of life right now. No battles, no plotting, it’s very calm and normal.” Ashen seemed to have become a lot more cheerful.

“I never would have thought,” Garen turned around, “that the strongest Blood Breed in the world would become a teacher in a human school.” He looked at the strongest Blood Breed, Castine, who had suddenly invited him here. Connecting that with the information he just received, he too felt something that he could not quite describe.

“How are Arisa and Isaros doing?” he asked quietly.

“Not bad, my wedding with Isaros is coming up soon, you’d better come join the celebration,” Castine laughed. Although the sound still seemed soft and weak, it gave off a crystal clear feeling.

Garen sighed a little inside. He had just found out that Isaros was getting married, and the person she was getting married to was the Blood Breed Ashen Castine. When they met the parents back then, tables were nearly flipped at the family gathering.

Afterward, he found out that after Ashen was critically wounded in the battle with him, Isaros had found him while he was recuperating, hoping to remove the Scarlet Moon Holy Technique deep in their consciousness. Perhaps a lot of things happened when they were interacting.

Apparently Scarlet Moon had appeared in the process as well, and assuming that Isaros and Arisa were on Garen’s side, he tried to kill them. Ashen saved their lives, and somehow or another, the two of them fell in love.

Garen finally understood why the sisters kept giving him that indescribable feeling, this proved that the feeling was right. As a result of the Scarlet Moon Secret Technique, she had actually gotten hooked up with the number one Death Apostle. No one could have imagined this wedding, perhaps there was another long story behind it.

“I don’t want to bother with these things anymore, isn’t your Holy Fist Palace doing a good job with it? With Tu Lan around, the Blood Breeds have a place to return to, and the world is at peace again.” Castine chuckled, as though he had truly let go. “I just want to live a peaceful life, like a normal person.”

“Do you know what they’re doing?” Garen suddenly asked out of the blue.

Castine froze for a moment, and his smile vanished.

“I don’t want to care, and I can’t. Besides, with you around, no one would dare disturb the order, isn’t that right? –”

“I’m leaving,” Garen interrupted him.

Both of them fell silent.

There was only the sound of the wind blowing past the roof, carrying a hint of cold.

“Humans are never satisfied. Once they have power, they’ll want more,” Garen said calmly. “In order to attain immortality, they will come after you sooner or later.”

The Holy Fist Palace was now the number one power, and many of the higher-ups were the people in high positions from before, such as Cece, such as Quentin now, Xander, and many other higher-ups from the combat club who joined later.

The Royal Fist Technique could extend one’s lifespan, but how could it compare to the Blood Breeds’ natural immortality? The battle had just died down, if it weren’t for Garen iron-fisted suppression, there would probably have been many people who tried to research the Blood Breeds’ immortality with violent means, and even others who would be deeply interested in the mystery of the Death Apostles. Out of the only remaining Death Apostles, Tu Lan had a high position, so no one would dare touch her. But Castine was different, he was alone outside, and his personality was unnaturally weak, if someone caught the people important to him and threatened him with them, he’d give up in a heartbeat. That was exactly how the secret party could ambush him last time.

The human greed was limitless.

Castine wanted a peaceful life, but that would never be more than an illusion.

“You’re leaving?” Castine paused, “Where to?”

“I probably can’t ever come back…” Garen replied calmly. Recently he could feel the repulsion of the planet grew stronger and heavier. No matter how powerful he was, he was still just a single individual. Even Nadia could not fight against a planet on her own, much less Garen. Faced with this repulsion, he could only stay for a few more days at the most.

“Then what do you plan to do?” Castine looked at this young man, rumored to be in his twenties, and suddenly felt that his mind was far older than twenty.

“At first I planned to pass on the position of Holy Fist to you, but now that seems impossible,” Garen said calmly. When he found out that Castine was somehow Isaros’ husband, he had that thought. After all, he was the most powerful, with him in the throne, he could lord over all the Blood Breeds and humans, but now Garen could tell that he was set on retirement.

“Come back to the Holy Fist Palace and become Vice Palace Master, I’ll pass the position of Holy Fist to Tu Lan.” They were the only two suited for the job, neither of them had many ambitions, so they could hamper the Lightless Alliance and AG’s plans from the throne.

This was especially because he would soon be retrieving all the soul primers. When that happens, the Holy Fist Palace would no longer be bound by anything material, so they would need a powerful force to keep them together.

“I’ll consider it.” Castine lowered his head and thought for a while, but still nodded slightly in the end.

Isaros and Arisa had no parents, so they had basically become part of Garen’s family. Isaros also learned all her martial arts from Garen, and that saved her life many times. A whole series of ties made the two sides unspeakably close, until they were practically one big family. With that in mind, Garen had no reason to harm him.

Garen had a feeling that after he left, the whole world might descend into chaos once more. The Blood Breeds’ longevity, and the Blood Breeds’ immortality, these were all the root of all chaos. On the surface, the Holy Fist Palace looked stable in power, but in truth, he had created all this with his iron fist, so once he was gone, all the factions from all over would definitely start to grow restless.

But none of this had anything to do with him anymore, he was most concerned with his arrangements for his family. As the most loyal students of the Holy Fist Palace, Ninox, Quentin, and Xander were all reliable, and Ashen’s personality meant that he was no problem either. With this group banded together, even if Tu Lan had any other thoughts, she would not make a move easily.

Nevertheless, nothing in the world is absolute, and even the most perfect or secure safety measures would one day be broken.

Garen knew very well that after he left, no one in this world would be able to surpass the Blood Breed Death Apostles, and Ashen would always be the number one Blood Breed, no competition.

After all, no one would have Soul Seeds, or attribute talents. Even the undying Blood Breeds would not be able to reach the highest heights since their secret techniques were not good enough.

Garen sighed inwardly, in the end he still decided not to leave behind any of the true peak-level secret techniques he practiced. Other than the Fantasy Fist, be it the original Waterbird Fist, or the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, or even the White Cloud Secret Technique, all of these secret techniques were only powerful because his soul primer maintained them at top form. They were mostly good for fighting and killing, not for leveling up and cultivating. Dahm and Hochman were only so powerful because of the soul primer.

Once he called back the primers, their battle ability would drop a notch, and the effect would be felt the most in their practicing speed. That speed would drop drastically, the reason they could level up so quickly before was also because the after-effects were shared by the soul primer, so they did not have to worry. Once he retrieved them, that meant they would have to carry the burden of these after-effects themselves. That was when they would see just how cruel a demonic technique could be.

They leveled up quickly and grew very powerful, but one misstep, and they would die very quickly too…

Only when he thought of that did Garen realize just how big an impact his leaving would have on the whole Holy Fist Palace.

“Aren’t you afraid that the Blood Breeds would train in the secret techniques and become unstoppable?” Castine asked.

“The strongest Blood Breed with secret techniques would still be no match for you, secret techniques were tailored for humans after all, they would reach a certain bottleneck and be unable to progress from there, because their make-up is different,” Garen said, shaking his head. He glanced at Castine. “If you can’t help it, retire.”

This sentence came out of nowhere, and Castine did not understand, but Garen’s expression when he said it carved those words deep into his mind, until he could not forget it even if he tried.

********************

Holy Fist Palace

The huge palace on the snowy mountain, matched the snowy-white ocean of clouds beneath it, made it look like it was built on the clouds, with the same airy feeling as a divine palace of the gods.

The many people walking up the mountain were all members, come to visit, to look around, to learn, to exchange. There were also several teams from the Palace in charge of logistics and the like, practically forming several long lines, flowing into the Holy Fist Palace from all directions like streams flowing into the ocean.

People walked in and out of the Palace, Garen was holding an internal conference, the external matters were mostly handled by Tu Lan. By now, the Holy Fist Palace had swollen up to an extreme degree, while the combat club and the Nighthawks grew bigger and stronger.

“You guys go rest, I want to walk around on my own,” Raffaele said to the two young ladies taking care of her as they walked down a corridor in the Palace.

“Alright, please contact us with your communicator if you need anything.” The two girls were happy to get a break as well, smiling as they quickly retreated.

Raffaele watched as they slowly disappeared down the corner of the corridor, and felt her heart lighten up a bit. Then she quickly walked towards the place she had committed to memory from before.

Ever since she received the news of the Blood Alliance’s overwhelming defeat, Raffaele understood for the first time just how powerful the Holy Fist Alliance was. Apparently the Fist Saint Garen had defeated the four Great Death Apostles all by himself, and was as unstoppable as a demon god!

This difference was worlds apart, and it let Raffaele truly understand what Mother meant by the root of chaos. In just twenty years, he had surpassed the Death Apostles’ accumulation over several thousand years, this was an existence that should not exist, it went against the rules of nature. His very being was a tumor that disrupted the natural cycle of life.

But according to Mother’s predictions, this Fist Saint Garen, known as the strongest in the world, still had a fatal flaw. Or rather, according to the prediction, this flaw was also the whole Holy Fist Palace’s flaw. She just had to break that flaw, and she could directly destroy the foundations of Garen’s martial arts, as well as those of the entire Holy Fist Palace higher-ups.

Chapter 765: Endnote 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Following her memories, Raffaele quickly arrived at the secret room she had been at before.

Opening the door to the room with ease, she walked in and closed the door behind her. Raffaele walked straight to the wall at the very bottom of the room.

She rubbed the ring on her finger a few times, and the ruby on it immediately emitted a red laser-like light. The light shone on the wall, and immediately, it reflected a few spots of pure white back.

Raffaele was instantly overjoyed.

“The thing is still here. He hasn’t noticed yet!”

She felt around the wall for a bit and found that ring again, tugging at it hard.

Crack…

Amidst the soft noises, she pulled a stone platform shaped like a cuboid out of the wall. There was a metallic cylinder embedded in the middle of the platform.

Raffaele grabbed the cylinder’s ring. She pulled at it, but it was surprisingly heavy, and did not budge at all.

She frowned, and began to chant softly.

“Mother, grant me courage, blessings, and strength.”

As soon as she said those words, a red light flashed past her hands, and she just had to pull lightly, instantly lifting up the entire cylinder.

There was a hollow space in the middle of the cylinder, and inside there was a notebook with a black shell. For some reason, this book gave off a strange feeling, as though it was absorbing all the light from its surroundings, just like a black hole.

“This is it!” Raffaele quickly flicked her finger, and instantly held the notebook in her hands. She flipped through it lightly, and found that it was full of all sorts of high level secret techniques! She immediately looked ecstatic.

She quickly took a red paper board from her pocket, it was covered densely with many glyphs and symbols. She pressed this against the notebook.

“Mora!”

She quietly recited the chant to activate it.

Immediately, there was a burst of red light, and both the paper board and the notebook vanished at the same time.

“I did it!” Raffaele felt instantly relieved. Pulling the cylinder back again, she quickly left the secret room, looking left and right down the corridors. Once she was sure that no one had noticed her, she strode confidently down the other corner.

Not long after she turned the corner, Garen’s figure abruptly appeared at the entrance to the secret room. He looked at the direction Raffaele had left in, but did not enter the secret room.

“Don’t we need to deal with her?”

Tu Lan’s figure slowly appeared behind Garen.

“It’s too late,” Garen shook his head slightly, turning around to glance at Tu Lan. “I might need to leave.”

“Leave?” Tu Lan was slightly taken aback. “Where to?”

“I don’t know…” Garen lowered his voice. “If I leave, would you be willing to protect the Holy Fist Palace for me?”

Tu Lan looked thoughtful. She did not brush it aside, but instead she thought about it very seriously for more than ten minutes, and Garen did not seem impatient either, waiting for her quietly.

“I think it would be hard for me to stay for a hundred years,” Tu Lan spoke after much consideration. “If it weren’t for you, I would have left to train secret techniques on my own a long time ago. That would feel much better than wasting time here.”

“You sure are honest.” Garen shook his head and laughed, only then did he remember that Tu Lan’s true personality had always been lazy and unambitious, living each day as it came.

“The only reason I’d stay a hundred years would be for you.” Tu Lan pouted, acting uncharacteristically mischievous. “I’ll watch your house for a hundred years.”

Her eyes shifted. “Or else… Just take me with you.”

“Hah?” Garen did not expect to hear her say that all of a sudden. “Why?”

“It’s boring without you…With you around, I have a proper target to chase,” Tu Lan replied very honestly.

Garen was speechless, and decided to just ignore her. If he could take someone with him, he would have done it a long time ago, and this time was not like the last. This time the planet was repelling him of its own accord The Holy Phoenix Scriptures truly were impressive, they could help the Buddha Mother reach another level, a terrifying level. If he was perfectly honest, without the powered-up Buddha Mother, he probably could not have defeated Nadia. In the end, when the Buddha Mother had been utterly beaten up and broken, the body Nadia had descended into was already on the brink of collapse, and he only beat her because he faced her head-on in the Fifth Star state.

Although all these details were included in his calculations, the Buddha Mother powering up did indeed surpass his expectations, the Holy Phoenix Scriptures merged with the Buddha Mother, increasing its power again.

“The world will become boring when you leave.”

As Garen left the corridor, Tu Lan shouted from behind him.

“Who knows?”

Garen shrugged.

********************

On a small island near the North Pole

The icy cold seawater kept washing over the black rocks by the shore of the little island. The whole island was covered with black rocks, and it looked just like an oval black pebble in the middle of the blue sea.

In the blue sky, the sunlight was cold rather than warm, and the scattered clouds were like flights of stairs, floating slowly in the sky. Several fluffy white seagulls also flew past occasionally, some diving head-first into the sea and then quickly flying out again, with decently-sized fishes in their mouths.

Somewhere in the island’s forest of black rocks, a beautiful woman with long white hair was crouching down slowly, looking at something placed on a red stone slab on the ground.

It was a pitch-black notebook, thick, with a cover like a whirlpool that absorbed the gazes of all living creatures around it.

The woman’s long white hair dragged on the floor, scattered all over her. Even if you looked closely, you would not know just how long it was, the strands of long hair tangled and twined together, forming a road behind her like a long train.

She picked up the notebook lightly.

“This is the root to the Fist Saint Garen’s martial arts?” she murmured softly, lightly brushing away the bits of dust that had landed on the book.

“I just have to destroy it and critically wound the Fist Saint, then the world will return to its original path…” the woman murmured, a hint of determination in her eyes.

She flipped open the book lightly, and the contents inside presented themselves to her eyes.

They were lines upon lines, and paragraphs upon paragraphs of strange, unknown words. The words seem to have some sort of magic that kept her gaze glued to it, until she could not pull away.

The martial arts contents in there had, in an instant, opened up a path for her that she had never once imagined.

“This– This is–?!” The woman’s expression changed slightly, and she wanted to push the book away, but her hands grabbed it tightly despite herself, keeping it within her line of vision. She suddenly had a feeling that if she could learn all the martial arts recorded here, perhaps she could walk down a brand new, unprecedented path of evolution based on her own current foundations.

All of a sudden, she sensed an unknown gaze land on her head in an instant.

“Satellite tracking?” She frowned slightly, looking up at the sky, then she quickly kept the notebook away, disappearing into the forest of black rocks with a few bounds.

That gaze swept past the island and seemed to find nothing, continuing to sweep on its merry way.

*****************

America, the CIA

“We didn’t find anything, perhaps our satellite system is not concise enough yet,” an old admiral said softly in front a giant blue screen. He watched the red dots blinking on the world map on the screen, then he turned his head around to look at the young man dressed in white beside him.

“Thank you for your cooperation, but I can track her myself.” The man had golden hair, but one of his eyes seemed to be slightly rolled back, as though he was blind in one eye. It was Garen, who had come out from the Holy Fist Palace. “The reason I’m here this time is because I need you to help me gather manpower. I can lead the way to the Lion Mother’s old base.”

“Your Excellency the Fist Saint can actually find items that have completely disappeared? What a magical martial arts.” The old admiral looked rather interested.

“You can try to practice it if you’re interested.”

“I’ll try.” The old man nodded.

He adjusted his earpiece, listening to the collective responses from the outside world through it.

“The fifth fleet is all ready, you can go out to sea with the ship. The fleet commander, Hente, is a fourth-generation disciple of yours, he’s training in the White Cloud Secret Technique.”

“In that case, many thanks.” Garen nodded and walked up to the world map, looking at the map on the blue screen. He reached out his hand slowly, and tapped a part of the sea near the North Pole lightly with his finger.

“Over here.”

“You sure she’s there? There’s nothing on the naval map, it’s just sea.” The admiral frowned.

“No, there’s a small island there,” Garen replied with certainty.

“Perhaps it’s a matter of proportions. Some islands are too small to be seen on the map, we can zoom in and see.” The admiral did not seem to move, but the map on the screen magnified all of a sudden, zooming in from a view of the world to that piece of sea, and soon enough, a black dot the size of a sesame seed appeared on the screen.

“Eh?” The admiral was slightly surprised. “There really is an island.”

The screen zoomed in some more, and the black dot was instantly magnified, turning from a sesame seed to a small apple, and further, until it was the size of a basin. There was the occasional wisp of the clouds floating past, covering up parts of the island.

From the satellite footage, they could vaguely see that the island was covered with pitch-black rock formations, with no forests or any trace of green.

“This is the biggest we can go. There seems to be something interfering,” the admiral said, frowning.

“This is the place.” Garen looked at the image on the screen carefully. “Inform the fleet to head straight for this island.”

“Alright, operation codename Lionhunt, commence!” the admiral said solemnly after nodding.

Garen looked at the black pebble island, and smiled strangely.

“I’ll give Pentagon a copy of the Lion Mother’s knowledge about witchcraft this time, and I’ll also retrieve my things. Let’s work well together.”

“Of course, let’s.” There was a hint of desire and excitement in the admiral’s eyes.

Compared to the Holy Fist Fist Technique, he was more interested in the mysterious witchcraft, and the Lion Mother had achieved Death Apostle-levels of strength, she was the ruler of the witches all over the world. If this top-secret mission were to succeed, they would gain knowledge about Death Apostle-level witch’s training, that was a temptation beyond imagination.

That was also why, when they found out that Gare was going to attack the ruler of the witches, many factions all gathered up their power to finally mobilize an entire American navy fleet. Under the guise of practice drills, they launched a top-secret assault straight away.

As for the revenge of the witches after this, they knew that even the old secret party’s Blood Breeds had all been killed at the height of their power, and many of the light party’s Blood Breeds joined the Holy Fist Palace because of Ashen. Among the Blood Breeds, most of the power still rested with the light party, after all, they had been leading the Blood Breeds for far too long.

Most of the light party’s Blood Breeds wished for a peaceful human life, that was also why they joined the Holy Fist Palace so quickly.

Just like that, the power of the Lightless Alliance snowballed, growing bigger and stronger. In comparison, the power of the witches was diminishing, and barely worth a mention.

With the situation the way it was, even if the witches retaliated, they would have no effect on the Lightless Alliance at the peak of their power. After all, there were just too few of them.

“Then I’ll personally make a trip there.” Garen pulled back the finger he had pressed against the map.”

“Good luck.”

“I never believed in luck,” Garen smiled, and turned to leave the command room.

Chapter 766: Endnote 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Half a day later…

As the evening hours approached, the afternoon light started to dim.

White steel battleships started to appear on the horizon one by one as they surrounded the small black island. Their thick cannons were aimed at the island and jets started to appear in the sky like a swarm of bees.

There were at least ten military satellites in the sky monitoring this nautical area.

Among the aircraft carriers, the largest white aircraft carrier was like a gigantic, notched, white log of driftwood as it positioned itself near an island in the deep sea area, aiming at the black island a distance away.

Surrounding it were at least tens of ships of various sizes.

Garen and a few high ranking captains stood at the ship’s bow, looking at the black island from afar. The evening light bathed onto them, giving off a soft luster as it reflected off their white uniforms.

Behind them were multiple aircraft carriers with jets preparing to take off. As its engine roared, the wind gusted strongly, causing people’s shirts to flap wildly.

Garen too was in a general military uniform. It was a unique ranking military uniform given to him by the country’s secret service to avoid being exposed during the military practice.

Surprisingly, Baldy of the Nighthawks and Tu Lan were among the high ranking officers.

“The surveillance aircraft has sent back its data on the details of the map. The aircraft carrier team in the area did not detect any submarines and not even a human figure,” the captain reported softly to Garen through the ear microphone. The jet’s roar was so loud that they couldn’t listen properly if they talked face to face.

“Are you sure there’s no sign of anyone?” Garen frowned.

“Yes. There’s no sign of human activity,” the captain responded personally as he knew that Garen and his men were not familiar with the fleet’s system as they were all outsiders.

“Prepare to fire all at once,” Garen took over the captain’s military binoculars as he looked at the island far away.

The island was completely deserted and was only filled with uneven surfaces of black rocks.

“Level this island,” Garen ordered calmly.

“Understood,” the captain nodded as he commanded his fleet through the ear microphone.

Soon, the ship at the very front started its bombardment.

Boom boom boom boom boom….!

Among the explosions of bombardment, the first cannon barrel recoiled instantly and white smoke constantly billowed from it. Then, the remaining cannon barrels on the ship fired off at the same time.

Following its lead, the other battleships fired off as well.

The series of bombardment shook the whole island as smokes, vapor, dust, and pebbles flew up in the sky. The black stones on the small island were instantly turned into dust. The small island was bombarded as if it was being hammered by a person with a huge hammer, flatting everything on the surface. With every bombardment, a huge amount of black rubble flew about everywhere.

Soon the whole island was engulfed in black smoke.

After a while, the whole island’s upper region was filled with white smokes and dust.

“Board the island!” Garen gestured his hands and he immediately started jumping from the battleship into the sea.

A small boat appeared out of nowhere and caught him coincidentally before heading straight for the small island at full speed.

Tu Lan and Nighthawks jumped down as well and, similar to Garen, were caught by the boat and went straight to the island.

Other than these three, no one else dared to get close the island. This was because Garen had arranged beforehand and stated that those who did not possess enough strength would die regardless.

Three boats raced towards the small island. Soon they slowed down as there were huge amounts of hidden coral reefs in the shallow region surrounding the island.

“Let’s go!”

Garen stood up, sprinted on the water surface and went straight to the island while the others followed from behind. Tu Lan was a natural at this and Baldy of the Nighthawks, who practiced the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, had managed to learn this in the Holy Fist Palace.

The bombardment stopped and there were jets revolving the island, observing the situation below and feeding the latest intel to Garen and the other two.

After a few splashes on the water, Garen gently landed on a flat surface beside the black stone crater as he adjusted his headset.

“Be alert of the surrounding at all times. Notify me immediately as soon as you notice anything strange.”

“Understood,” a response was immediately sent through the headset.

Garen looked over the horizon and most of the obstacles on the small islands were flattened out and craters formed by the cannons could be seen everywhere. The whole area was a total mess.

“Come out Lion Mother. I know you’re here.”

He slowly walked to the center of the island but still, no one responded.

Without the slightest change in expression, he soon arrived at the edge of a normal looking crater with the other two as they scanned their surrounding.

Boom!!

He stomped the ground with all his might and the ground instantly exploded as if it was hit by an explosive, forming another crater that rivaled the crater formed by the cannon.

What was even more ridiculous was that the rubbles flying off from the newly formed crater didn’t even hit the other two at all.

The power he showcased with his leg made those crew members who had never witnessed the strength of the Holy Fist Palace stared with their mouths wide open.

After stomping out a crater, he gently jumped into the crater with the other two and stomped on the ground once more.

Boom!!

This time, rubbles didn’t fly out from the ground but a pitch black hole was formed underneath his leg.

“This is it!” Garen’s gaze changed a little bit. When he realized that he had found his target, he immediately jumped into the pitch black hole while Nighthawks and Tu Lan followed behind without any hesitation.

Inside the hole was a pitch black rugged tunnel. As the trio sprinted forward, they soon noticed a faint glimpse at the front.

It was the end of the tunnel and it was glowing blue.

They sprinted into the light and arrived at a huge and spacious cave lighted in blue.

There was an unimaginably beautiful naked woman with white hair standing calmly inside the cave’s flat surface. She had a black note in her hand as she calmly stared at the arrival of the trio.

“Lion Mother?” Garen was the first one to stepped forward and asked softly.

“Holy Fist?” the lady’s gaze was very calm. “I knew that I’d fallen into your trap and revealed my location when I heard the ruckus coming from outside.”

“You just didn’t have enough information to work with,” Garen said calmly. “If you knew that I could sense the Demonic Book’s location, you wouldn’t even allow your underlings to steal the Demonic Book.”

“That’s right…” Lion Mother sighed. “Come to think of it, this is the only item that is the root of this result.” She lowered her head as she looked at the Demonic Book in her hand with a strange, glazed stare.

“I have tried to destroy it but no matter what I do to it, the book would instantly turn into an illusion the moment it was hit. I couldn’t destroy it no matter what.”

“Regardless, I’ve already won.” Garen walked forward slowly and with each step he took, his body expanded slowly. The black and thick black smoke-liked aura started to spread out from his legs.

“That’s right… You’ve won…” the Lion Mother nodded and raised her head up. However, blood started to flow out from her eyes. “However, I would do everything in my power and correct the course of the world, even if it means putting my body into the abyss for eternity. Don’t you dare think that you can have it your way…!!!” Her last tone immediately turned from the usual calmness to a horrifyingly sharp tone.

In an instant, a wine red light, at a speed surpassing sound, shone onto Garen as if it was an actual light.

As the red light bathed onto Garen, his body started to twist and turn about.

“What is the world…?” he was stunned because even though he didn’t feel any pain from his body, the Demonic Book’s Soul Seed started to react rapidly.

In an instant, the world’s rejection force was multiplied by numerous folds.

Garen’s face immediately turned pale as he immediately retracted his body’s aura back into his body, keeping only the layer of black shadow on him. It acted as a black armor that protected his body from the rejection from the planet.

“The rejection… has been increased… This person!” Garen’s gaze turned sharp.

The red light from the Lion Mother kept bathing onto Garen as if it was endlessly emitting onto him while her body started to melt like a candle.

As the red light kept emitting onto him, the rejection force onto Garen kept increasing over time.

“Kill her!” Garen wasn’t able to move at all and could only shout in dissatisfaction. He couldn’t leave this place now as he still had a lot of things to do!

Before he even shouted, Tu Lan and Baldy had already sprinted forward. The twisted stream of water turned into a giant icicle but it was broken off by Tu Lan’s palm.

A huge boom was heard and a waist thick icicle flew out instantly, piercing Lion Mother’s body without much resistance.

Thud!

A huge hole was created in Mother Lion’s body. She moaned even though her face had melted to the point where it couldn’t be recognized. With that attack, her body melted even faster and after a while, she had completely turned into a pool of blood, lost her humanoid shape, and even the red light had stopped as well.

Boom boom boom!!

Garen took a few steps back and sweat started profusely dripping from his face. It was fortunate that he’d brought Tu Lan and Baldy along in case of emergency, but he didn’t expect that he would need them this early on.

Lion Mother was about to sense the planet’s rejection of his existence and she was attempting to hasten the process.

“Is she dead?” Tu Lan was in disbelief as the icicle pierced her bloody body. “Is she really the Lion Mother? Would she die this easily?”

She had prepared herself for a difficult battle since she was the most mysterious witch queen in history, but she didn’t expect her to be so easily dealt with.

“She had used up all of her life force in exchange for the rejection force to exile me,” Garen’s face was still pale as he responded. “You can say that she has no remaining energy to defend herself the moment you attacked her. She had no plan to live after this from the very beginning.”

Tu Lan and Baldy were in disbelief as the legendary Mother Lion was defeated this easily.

“Go and check around this place,” Garen leaned against the wall inside the cave as he gestured his hand to tell them to ignore him. He wasn’t injured but exhausted from the pure will of fighting against the planet’s rejection of him.

Both of them soon found a few ancient books, bamboo piece, stone piece and a large black crystal ball with a wing mark on it inside the cave.

“The Mother Lion should be proud of herself since she was able to give me this much trouble,” Garen responded as he felt that he only had a day left or two on this planet. He didn’t know what to feel about it.

A mere Death Apostle decided to use such a unique method against him. She must have realized that physical attacks were of no use against him before she decided to go about on this route. If she couldn’t kill him, she would rather chase him away.

Chapter 767: Endnote 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Holy Fist Palace

Rafaelle was sitting quietly in her room as she distractedly flipped through a thick book. The evening light shone through the window, bathing onto her white tender legs, warming them.

“Why hasn’t anyone realized that I’ve already obtained that book?” she was confused as she stared at the book in her lap without processing the contents within it.

Suddenly she could feel a burning sensation on her chest. Without any hesitation, she pulled out the white gold necklace and she noticed that it was turning red.

“What’s going on?! Why is the Alert Necklace activated?!” she immediately stood up and the book thudded onto the ground.

She held onto the necklace as she scratched her finger with the sharp edge of the necklace and rubbed some blood onto the necklace.

“Mother?? What’s going on? Why is the necklace activating?!” she whispered

There was no response.

Raffaele started to panic.

“Mother! Speak up! Mother?!”

“Stop wasting your breath,” the door was slammed opened from outside. A beautiful woman came in together with a group of strong looking members in Taoist robes with a “Holy” word sewn on it.

“Wizard Hong Ji, you are suspected of possession of another person’s body and mind control. I shall now apprehend you in the name of Holy Fist Palace!”

The girl scoffed with a cold look on her face.

“You! You guys!?” Raffaele’s face immediately turned pale.

“Bring her away!” the woman waved her hand and two female members approached her as they tried to restrain Raffaele.

“No!!” she shouted in a sharp tone.

Raffael’s face turned pale and she agilely took a few steps back and a few somersaults as she landed behind the sofa.

“Die!” the beautiful woman instantly turned into a few after images as she followed Raffaelle closely while attempting to punch her.

Hong Ji, who was impersonating Raffaelle, was actually just a normal middle-level witch. Since she was not in her own body and fighting against a stronger opponent, it was only natural that she was defenseless against her.

“Take her away,” Quentin said calmly as she stood up, turned around and left the room.

****************

Evening hour

In the small town at the bottom of the Holy Fist Palace’s mountain.

There was a quiet room. The lights were switched off as it was pitched black. The only light source was from the sun as it shone through the window, faintly lighting the room, leaving a few spots of lights on the mattress.

Garen stood still in the darkness as he stared at Raffaele who was laying on the bed. Her golden hair had spread about on the pillow as she slept soundly. She was like a beautiful person posing on her side, revealing her pale and delicate hand as the white blanket had completely covered the rest of her naked body.

As he listened to Raffaele’s breath, Garen leaned against the wall and took a deep breath. He then recalled the events for the past twenty years that had occurred since he first arrived this planet.

“Say something if you’re awake. Stop pretending that you’re asleep,” he whispered.

Raffaele slowly opened her eyes. She didn’t move at all as she was still laying by her side.

“What do you wish to say?” she whispered.

“I’m sorry,” Garen pondered for a while before voicing up.

Both of them didn’t say anything afterward as the room settled into an awkward silence.

After a while.

“Why are you apologizing?” Raffaele broke the silence.

“You wouldn’t be involved in this if not for me,” Garen said softly. “Whatever. Have a good rest.”

He turned to the doors and gently opened it.

“Come back to Grano.”

He opened the door and left the room.

Clicked. He closed the door not knowing what to feel. He felt a little bit of troubledness but it was negligible as he’d been calm.

The room was quiet as usual. Perhaps Raffaele didn’t know how to express her emotions and feelings so she could only stay silent. However, both of them could feel that they couldn’t be together no matter what.

Perhaps Raffaele had reported to her Witch Association beforehand after she knew of the downfall of Lion Mother. The witches and the Holy Fist Palace were fated to fight against each other. The weakening of the witches was avoidable as well and they would lose their power from this world.

After losing their only Death Apostle, all the witches had lost their only protection and would hide in the darkness from now on.

Garen was the main enemy to the witches in general and in this scenario, they wouldn’t be able to be together no matter what.

After leaving the room, Garen slowly walked down the streets of the small town. The Demonic Book in his mind had turned into an oval-shaped bud as it looked very colorful while shining brightly like a rainbow.

The bud was vibrating softly and no one knew when it would blossom.

Garen understood that it would be time for him to leave this world when it had bloomed. The planet’s rejection force had already reached a critical level. The moment he relaxed, he would instantly be rejected by the planet.

However, there were still things that he’d yet to finish. It wasn’t to take back his soul primer as the primers had already been taken back before attending the meeting. While the weakening of the Holy Fist Palace would not be immediate, it would be after a few days.

As he walked along the streets, Garen might have looked slow with his footsteps but he was actually incredibly fast; he covered a great distance with each step. He soon arrived at the vacation resort where his family was staying.

Lights could not be seen from the outside at all.

Garen slowed down his footsteps as he recalled that it was currently spring and entering summer soon. Hence, his parents should be away and be giving talks. As professors of a university and well-known researchers, their workloads were greater than usual in this period.

As for his sister, she should be either fooling around at Rexott with Rod or attending classes.

“Guess I’ve miscalculated…” Garen smiled wryly.

He originally planned to visit his family one last time, but unfortunately…

He took out the key and entered the quiet and dark room.

He walked towards the sofa and sat on it as he casually threw the keys to one side, enjoying his last moment in this world peacefully.

It was too late for him to call their family as he might be leaving this world in twenty to thirty minutes time.

He sat on the sofa as time passed slowly.

No one was interrupting him as he’d ordered his subordinates to not disturb him beforehand.

He left a message for Tu Lan and the others. It was regarding the work arrangement after he left. He also left a few gifts to AG and vouched that the Lightless Alliance, Holy Fist Palace, and AG Nasira, who was representing the Dark Colors Witches, would be in balance before he left.

The Dark Colors Witches Association had stopped calling themselves the Witch Associate as they had officially changed their name to Shadow Council two hours ago. AG had gathered all witches, regardless of gender. Those who possessed an above average strength would be part of the Witches Council, which was part of his plan to unify the witches. Perhaps he was in a huge conference at the Witch Palace even now.

Time passed slowly.

Garen sat quietly on the sofa as he could faintly feel that his body was reacting strangely. It was the chain effect caused by the planet rejecting him. The magnetic field started changing and all sorts of radiative interferences started to kick him out as if he was a threat.

Perhaps it wouldn’t be a bad option to leave quietly just like Black Sethe. Garen sincerely thought so.

“Teacher Garen?”

Suddenly a clear and cautious female voice came from the door.

Garen looked at the door.

“Cece?”

The girl who was standing by the door was Ninox.

She was wearing a pair of white jeans and the Holy Fist Palace’s Taoist clothes with the “Holy” word embedded in it. The female Taoist cloth streamlined her thin waist and the jeans too perfectly, showed off her thin legs and hips. Combined with her elegant face and ashen, tender skin, it gave off a beautifully refined and slightly sexy vibe.

With a black ponytail, Cece’s eyes stared into the house.

Garen looked at the most talented female disciple in this world and felt that his loneliness had been washed away.

“Why are you here?”

Ninox’s face turned red as she didn’t dare to look into Garen’s eyes.

“I… I had been visiting sister Pella for a game of chess…” Pella was a family member of the neighboring family, who was also a close relative of a high ranking member of the Holy Fist Palace.

As she felt Garen’s conspicuous gaze, Ninox panicked a little. She tried to take a few steps to avoid his gaze but her legs couldn’t move at all.

She would never dare say that the reason she came to visit Garen’s family every day was to leave a better impression on his family.

All her follow friends who had come in contact with Garen said that they feared Garen as he gave off a mysterious and powerful vibe. It was as if he was from the God’s realm; he was so perfect that he didn’t seem human at all. Many people respected him and there even were girls idolizing him. However, she knew that it was a dream that could never be achieved as she believed that Garen would never like her type.

However Ninox understood that teacher Garen was still a person and just like everyone else, he required companions.

“Come and have a sit,” Garen smiled. “I didn’t expect that you would be the one who would accompany me at this time. Fate can be very mysterious at times.”

“What… do you mean?” Cece didn’t comprehend his words as she stuttered while walking into the house before gently closing the door. The whole living room was pitch black and the only light source was the street light shining into the house through the window.

Garen shifted himself to make space for her so that Cece could sit on the sofa. No matter how dark it was, they weren’t affected by it at all as both of them were Secret Technique Elites that possessed strong five senses. It would be natural for them to able to see clearly in the dark room.

“What did you mean…” Ninox could feel that something was amiss and quickly questioned him.

“There will be ups and downs in life, separation, and unification. You’re still young so you may not understand the meaning behind these words, but you’ll definitely figure it out one day,” Garen smiled. “I’m not saying this casually.”

“Are you leaving?” Ninox understood Garen’s intention and panicked. “Are you going into hiding?”

Chapter 768: Endnote 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen lost his cool and laughed. It was indeed true that those who were in the loop would definitely link everything like that.

After a while, he slowly reached out his hand and pulled out his index finger.

His clean nails had started to turn half transparent.

He smiled and gently clenched his fist, “Do you see it? It’s the law of the world…”

“Law?” Ninox’s pupils contracted as she saw the half transparent finger.

“Don’t be sad,” Garen said calmly as he gently caressed Cece’s hair.

“You’re the most talented disciple I have. Do not be constrained by your emotion.”

Cece started to feel a sense of agitation as he lowered her head and clenched her fists tightly.

Ding… Ding… Ding…

It was the bell from the outer world.

Garen was stunned as he saw the buds in his mind blooming. In that instant, the bud bloomed and gave off an unparalleled golden luster…

He stood up and his body involuntarily expanded to the point he reached the fifth star. His monstrous demon-liked body stirred up the airflow inside the living room.

Hu…!

A strong gust blew against Cece and she was forced to take a few steps back.

“Teacher!” panicked and confused as to what was going on, she raised up her head and looked at Garen, who was standing in front of the window under the moonlight.

The breeze became stronger as it blew everything in the living room off onto the carpet as it made a ruckus.

“As my last gift to you in this world,” Garen stared calmly at his most valued disciple, who was also his most loyal member.

“Destiny depends on you, and it is also my gift to you.”

Pew!!

A black light flashed as a black line was traced through the air, landing accurately onto Ninox’s forehead.

In an instant, Ninox’s head raised up and she was sent a few steps back.

“Consider this as a trace of me existing in this world…”

Roar…

A deep roar echoed through the room as countless black shadows crawled out of Garen, fusing together and forming the shape of the black nine-headed dragon.

In an instant, cracks propagated on the surface of the dragon’s shadow with a clear and high tone, and it shattered into millions of pieces as if a glass sheet had been smashed.

“Teacher!!” Ninox rushed towards him in an attempt to grab hold of the black shadow, but her efforts were futile and she clutched at nothing.

The Nine-Headed Dragon shattered, turning into countless black debris.

She stood still, dumbfounded. She didn’t realize that tears were flowing down her cheeks and she couldn’t stop crying at all.

*************

In this instance at a certain square in Madrid, Ashen was holding onto Isaros’ hand as he subtly shifted his head, gazing in a certain direction.

“What’s wrong?” Isaros’ cheek was blushing red. She looked at him curiously and followed his gaze, only to see a street of densely packed buildings.

“Nothing,” Ashen smiled. “I just felt that someone I knew had left.”

“Left?” Isaros was curious.

“Don’t worry about it. Let’s go watch a movie,” Ashen pinched Isaros’ face affectionately as they held each other’s hands and walked into a cinema.

**************

Indonesia.

“Let’s try scuba diving in the dark this time. With the lights underneath the water, it’s going to be so much more exciting than during daytime,” Vivien chuckled as she checked over the scuba equipment on her.

“How is it going, Lisa? Are you done preparing?” she looked at a petite girl in a diver’s suit.

“All set!” Alisa gestured an OK to her.

“How about you, Rod?” Vivien tilted her head as he looked at the tall man.

“I’m alright… I think we should dive in the day… It’s very dangerous at night. What if we encountered a shark or something…” Rod was still worried.

“What’s there to fear about sharks? With my brother’s underlings around, the sharks would be committing suicide if they come after us! I’m still not over the shark fin soup I had last time, so it’s a good opportunity for me to get more of it!” Little Vivien gestured in confidence. She was currently enjoying life every day and was considered a rich and beautiful girl. With such a ridiculously overwhelming background as her main support, even the high-class merchants would have to respect her.

In addition, the trio, Vivien, Rod, and Alisa, was considered this generation’s overlords. It was fortunate that the trio’s personalities weren’t reckless and so they didn’t develop into bullies.

Vivien pointed at a black beach nearby them.

“There’s twenty-four-hour guard duty over there! There’s nothing to be afraid of. Let’s go down into the water!”

She was the first one to jump from the boat and was swallowed by the sea.

Rod and Alisa exchanged looks hopelessly and then proceeded to don their oxygen masks.

Waters were splashed and two of them entered the deep sea with their diving suit.

The trio did have enough capital to not care about their expenditure at all.

Even if Garen was no longer around, Alisa’s sister was Ashen’s lover. No matter what happened to the Holy Fist Palace, Garen’s reputation as the Holy Fist would never be shaken and the upper-level members would definitely be the first ones to protect them no matter what. In such a short amount of time, the appearance of the Holy Fist had become the very icon of overwhelming strength and the mental idol of the Holy Fist Palace. Furthermore, there had already been people idolizing him before this.

For example, Ninox, Xander, Baldy and his wife.

****************

Hu!

Raffaele got up from the bed and she was drenched in her own sweat. She seemed like she’d just had a horrible nightmare.

Her face was pale and her gaze was rather unfocused as if she’d just realized that she was at an unknown place.

As she used the blanket to cover her upper body, she stood up from the bed as she could faintly hear some ruckus from outside.

She looked down from the window and could see a lot of luxurious cars, even limited edition ones, passing by the area. A lot of high-class gentlemen were getting down from the cars under the protection of bodyguards as they walked to a building nearby.

A huge amount of military soldiers had locked the whole area down with yellow tapes.

Raffaele opened the window and a series of soft conversations could be heard among the winds. However, they were very faint and she couldn’t hear their voices clearly.

Her gaze shifted and she drew an invisible symbol in front of her. The voices drowned by the wind were amplified.

“… Lord Holy Fist shouldn’t have disappeared by accident. Based on his individual strength, there should be no one who can fight against him one on one.”

“Based on this logic, does that mean that what Captain Cece said is true?”

“It’s very likely since Lord Holy Fist’s martial arts have reached a realm beyond our imaginations. If we related him to the stories in the east, it wouldn’t be impossible for him to achieve the level of flying in the sky.”

“That’s in the realm of fantasy! I believe Lord has gone to another place to search for a stronger martial art,” one of them said so.

“Regardless, we need to announce that Lord Holy Fist has isolated himself from the world to the public. The main power of the Holy Fist Palace is him so we must delay the truth as long as possible. Furthermore, Lord Ashen is currently our Vice Palace Master. We don’t even need Lord Holy Fist to maintain our power,” one of the eastern practitioners broke down his analysis.

“This is a good idea.”

“Right. Let’s go with this for now!”

Raffaele looked in their direction from afar and she could only see a few heads moving about as the voice came from inside the house. She didn’t realize that two contours had appeared quietly at the dark corners of her room while she was eavesdropping on them. They were the Upper-Level Blood Breeds from the Holy Fist Palace. If she had been someone with no qualifications, she would’ve been killed already.

“Garen…” Raffaele muttered softly.

****************

New York.

“I hereby announce, the beginning of the world’s first Witch parliamentary election!!”

In a hall filled with thousands of people, AG was in a white suit. His hair was neat and tidy, giving off a waxy reflection, and he had a clean and delicate silver crutch in his hand.

He stood on the main platform as he looked at the densely packed witches. He had a feeling of satisfaction that couldn’t be described in words.

Indeed, he had succeeded.

After revealing his secret on how to maintain his strength while leaving his ancestral land, he had immediately gained ninety percent of the witches’ support, regardless of gender. The number one issue for the witches had always been them being unable to leave their ancestral lands. Once they did so, they would exhaust all the blessed ancestral water which they always carried along and their strength would decrease dramatically.

Now that AG had gifted this secret technique to the masses, all male and female witches were no longer bound by this chain.

This also meant that the witches were now qualified to stand on the world’s stage as well.

The old witches who held power were replaced by the Shadow Council and AG was the first speaker who was elected by a majority vote. This was also a milestone of the arrival of the supernatural generation.

The Death Apostle level AG had successfully replaced Mother Lion.

Nasira had become the Deputy Speaker as she assisted AG.

It was time for the Witches to rise with the world…

In the same year, the Holy Fist Garen of the Holy Fist Palace had passed on as he tried to surpass his limits. Once the news was out, countless of martial art practitioners were devastated.

While AG and the rest of the countries tried to maintain their powers in terms of supernatural strengths and the Holy Fist isolating himself from the world, this sparked everyone’s greed. Hence the world was once again thrown into chaos.

***************

Garen’s vision was completely black as he felt that he was ejected out of the planet by an unknown force.

His body had turned into a blob of black dragon-shaped aura as he was forced into the endless starry space away from the planet. He looked behind at the blue planet that was shrinking in size and dimming at the same time.

His speed gradually increased and reached its limit.

The surrounding stars blinked brightly and he wasn’t sure where he was heading, nor in which direction.

“I can’t just fly out without any direction,” Garen felt that his body had completely melted and became a pure aura with his soul as the guidance.

Suddenly the universe around him started trembling.

Splash!

He seemed to have been dumped into some sort of fluid, as Garen thought that he had been thrown into the sea. He was caught in a ferocious tide from the vacuum space.

His soul could clearly see that he was surrounded by light yellow river water while moving at high speed.

“No… This isn’t water… This is aura in a liquid state!” Garen was stunned as he finally knew where the planet’s rejection was sending him to.

He was at the Mother Stream! It was also the place where he’d first appeared!

Chapter 769: New World 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Mother Stream was endless as it bypassed the space-time continuum. No one knew exactly where it originated and no one could see its ending point as well. Every Secret Technique practitioner could only see its ferocious current.

The moment Garen entered the Mother Stream, he looked out from within the river and what replaced the universe’s starry sky was a dimensional space filled with rainbow-colored light.

“Is this the scenery of the Mother Stream?”

It was his first time seeing himself floating in the Mother Stream this clearly.

His accumulation last time wasn’t as vast as this time. Furthermore, his current world was of a higher level than the previous two so the aura he accumulated was exhausted at a much lower rate than last time.

Garen could feel that his aura, which had transformed into the black nine-headed dragon, was being constantly corroded by the fluid. It was as if the fluid was a very acidic acid that kept melting him away as the surface of the black nine-headed dragon was bubbling ferociously, with small black debris turning into powder.

“I wonder what world I’ll be placed into this time…” Garen looked deep into his soul and saw two glowing Soul Seeds floating inside. One was icy blue while the other was a faint yet rich gold. These two seeds were like flowers as they were placed inside beautifully.

Buzz….

Suddenly an oppression as powerful as the sea passed by the river’s surface. A faint numbing anger and growl could be sensed from the oppression.

“I smell it… the Void Hunter… The scent of the Warlock’s descendant…”

“Where is it… Where is it…!”

The overwhelming oppression kept surging through the Mother Stream. Series of huge waves formed as if there was an ongoing hurricane.

The waves of pure spiritual ripples expressed the oppressor’s will clearly.

Garen’s soul looked up and saw the seven-colored barrier writhing as it cracked loudly.

“What is that…?” even before the opponent had approached any closer, he could sense an overwhelming danger when it was still outside the barrier, as it was able to induce giant waves just with its will alone.

Deep down, Garen knew that he had encountered a super creature among the Void Creatures. Hence he suppressed his aura much as possible by reducing his surface contact with the river.

He could faintly feel all sorts of overwhelming power from its will. The source of its strength was similar to his, which was the Soul’s Strength. However, his was at least ten times stronger than Garen’s in terms of Quantity.

This sort of existence was something he couldn’t hope to fight against!

“The Void Creatures… No wonder Nadia warned me to not enter the Void arbitrarily…” Garen put his thoughts away while not having a single bit of fear at all. He was purely flowing the Mother River’s current without any destination in mind.

After some time, a few powerful void creatures appeared outside the realm outside the river once more. Each and every one of them had at least ten Soul Seeds and their soul color was colorless. Each of them riled the Mother River and this made Garen understood how dangerous the Void Creatures outside the Mother Stream was. All he could do was to minimize his surface area to extend the time of his drift.

It was a journey of life and death whenever he entered the Mother River. Once his aura had been completely corroded, the soul would be next in line and this would injure it severely. He would then disappear within the Mother River, becoming one of the many imprints inside it.

The frequency of the powerful Void Creatures appearing increased as time passed.

Eventually, Garen was able to differentiate their strength based on their will and aura alone.

Only creatures of soul seed level were able to sense the movement inside the Mother River. Furthermore, the Soul Seed’s foundation was the colorless rank and the seven color ranks were the stronger ones. Each increment in level would mean an improvement in its quality.

These creatures that noticed Garen’s presence were at least colorless rank. Perhaps their training regime was different from that of the humans as they had to gather tens of soul seeds even though they were still at this rank. As a human, Garen had only obtained two soul seeds and these souls’ colors weren’t even cleansed properly. This meant that he hadn’t even entered the Soul Seed Level and was nowhere close to the colorless rank.

Fortunately, he would require only five Soul Seeds to enter the colorless rank. After all of them were purified into colorless, he would be able to step forward to the next level.

He had drifted for a long time and soon, Garen could feel that the river’s current was slowing down and was no longer as fast as before.

Most of his aura had been corroded away and he only had a fifth of it left. He felt that he had entered one of the many forks and with a jolt, he seemed to have crashed into a barrier as he was swept into a very narrow passage.

As the current slowed down, he could sense that the surrounding seven-colored barrier had become weaker and thinner through his soul seed.

After some time, Garen had exhausted all of his aurae and his own spiritual energy was being corroded.

It was fortunate that he was much more resistant as compared to before now that he had two soul seeds, hence the corrosion rate was much slower than when he had one soul seed.

He flowed along with the current. With his aura spent, he started to panic, as he’d put two lifetimes of effort to obtain this amount of soul strength. With it being corroded, every second counted and if one of his soul seed were to be destroyed, his effort of a lifetime would be wasted!

The current of the Mother River slowed down as if there were something blocking just up front.

Garen flowed along the slowing current and he soon realized that the surrounding river had changed its color into green, which was the color he saw when he first saw the Mother River.

It changed from yellow to yellow-green to finally green.

Within the river, he shrunk into a black blob of a sort. He went with the flow along with other contaminants.

Garen looked around and the edge of the river had narrowed down to a few meters apart from the horizon.

“The powerful Void Creatures from the previous days seem to have disappeared.”

Garen was unable to determine how many days had passed so he could only estimate. The powerful Void Creatures had stopped appearing and it seemed that he was headed to a rather secluded area.

He looked around and the river was filled with contaminants such as white bone debris, strange looking metal and some rotting feathers. There even were some sort of plants and leaves as well.

However, he didn’t encounter any soul’s substance like him drifting in the river.

It wasn’t just his immediate surroundings, he hadn’t encountered any existence similar to him ever since he was drifting about. It was as if the Mother River bore no life.

Time passed slowly…

Soon, The seven-colored barrier above the Mother River started to crack open.

After that, holes of various sizes appeared from the crack. Some were the size of an ant while some were as big as a fist.

Garen looked out of these holes and could see black gas rotating like a whirlpool, leading to an unknown location.

However, the situation didn’t allow him to delay things further as one of the two soul seeds started to show signs of corrosion. If he didn’t find a way to leave the river, he would lose one of his soul seeds in a few days!

“I have to do something! I need select one of the holes and leave this place!” Garen had made a decision. He started to sense the colorful barrier above the Mother River. Some of these holes were so small that his body wasn’t able to fit in at all and only holes of the size of the washbasin were big enough for him to enter.

He could sense from the black gas that these holes would lead him to an unknown universe. No one was entirely sure what sorts of dangers it had to offer but the had no choice but to choose one.

Finally, he saw a hole the size of a washbasin.

As he was about to be washed past it, Garen released all of his spiritual energy. The spiritual energy merged with the Mother River’s aura, turning it into a powerful force that pushed him out from the surface of the river.

With a splash, Garen broke free from the river and went flying towards the hole.

Thud!!

At this moment, a wave riled up and engulfed him whole, pushing him back down.

With a huge splash, Garen was sent back into Mother River once more.

He panicked and tried to jump out once more. By the time he struggled free, the hole was already far away from its original location.

“Damn it!” Garen was back into the Mother River. He could sense that his soul seed had corroded once more and he was very upset about it. These were the essence he gathered in two lifetimes and now it could be corroded at any moment.

He had already sensed that the Mother River seemed to have a mysterious power. The Mother River had already taken him, who had been living for so long drifting in the river as one of itself and would not let go of him easily.

He had completely missed the hole at this point. Although current was slow, it was determined to drive him far away from it.

“No wonder there were so many of these holes, the Mother River wouldn’t flow into it.”

Garen understood what was going on.

“I can only wait for the next opportunity…”

He waited patiently. It was fortunate that the Mother River had narrowed down even further and the seven-colored barrier was filled with holes of various sizes. All of these holes were filled with black rotating whirlpools. Some were the size of a nail while some were the size of a head but it was rare to encounter one the size of a washbasin.

Garen waited patiently. After a while, another washbasin-sized hole appeared within his vision.

“This is the one!” he released his senses as he confirmed the location of the hole with extreme precision and started to gather his strength. He knew that he needed to immediately sprint out before the Mother River reacted when he released his strength. If not, history would repeat itself and pull him down back into the river.

The hole was getting closer… and closer…

Chapter 770: New World 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As Garen waited for the best moment to leap out of the surface, his body, which was in the form of a black blob, shrunk slowly and became much smaller than before.

Finally, when he was a small distance from the hole.

Splash!!

Within the crisp clear sound of the water splashing, a black shadow emerged out from the river and flew directly towards the hole.

With a thud, the shadow was absorbed into the hole. The green river of the Mother River below reached out a whip of water which danced about for a few moments. Once it realized the target had escaped, it collapsed and everything was calm once more.

***************

Garen jumped into the hole and he felt that he had jumped into a layer of black, sticky and oily substance.

There was no light or anything around him at all.

Garen could sense that his surrounding area spanned hundreds of meters apart, but there was nothing in here at all. There was only him moving forward at high speed.

It seemed like an area where there was no light nor gravity. Garen could only feel that he was moving at a very high speed.

“Luckily the Mother Stream’s corrosion doesn’t exist here, so I should be able to last for a while,” Garen looked around carefully but he didn’t notice anything but himself. The sticky sensation previously had disappeared. Perhaps he had gotten used to it.

He felt that he was transmigrating in a mysterious tunnel.

Perhaps ten days have passed, maybe twenty days, it was so long to the point that Garen had lost track, and he had been traveling forward this whole time.

Debris started to appear in the surroundings. He seemed to be inside a very long black passage and cracks started to appear around him. What made it strange was that he could see the light of the stars through these cracks.

Thud!

Suddenly everything in front of him was empty and Garen seemed to have been ejected out of some sort of a tunnel. His surrounding lit up instantly and he was ejected into a beautiful nebula.

Garen felt that there was a fiery hot giant fireball behind him as the light radiated in all directions.

“That’s a Guidance Star…” he recognized the name of the fiery golden star.

The Guidance Star behind him had covered almost his entire field of vision. Magma was moving about lazily on the surface. Dark red magma was crawling on the surface like a worm and there were blinding golden geysers gushing at other parts of the surface as well.

Garen, who was in the shape of a black ball, looked around to see densely packed stars blinking everywhere. Some of the light blue stars glowed faintly while some old and mysterious looking ones were stationary as he moved about.

Garen noticed that the black tunnel that he was ejected out from had disintegrated after maintaining its shape for a short while.

He didn’t know what that was but it was most likely the warp gates extended by the Mother River. It connected all the universe’s worlds together. It was something Black Sethe had casually mentioned before as if it was common knowledge.

If it was the Mother River’s warp gate, then it would most likely be impossible for him to return. This was because these warp gates usually lasted for a very short amount of time. It was short-lived and would pierce through many parts of the spacetime continuum, but would be automatically disintegrated by the universe’s force. It was a once in a lifetime occurrence.

When he had reached this space, he had no idea how long he would have to wait for the Mother River’s warp gate to open once more. According to the Warlocks’ knowledge, there were theoretically an infinite amount of worlds in this universe as the universe would die and being reborn endlessly. It could extend to countless worlds and even a minute difference would mean that it was another world as well.

Garen floated among the stars quietly and soon could no longer sense the Mother River’s warp gate behind him. The radiation from the Guidance Star pushed him forward towards the center of his field of vision but the direction slightly deviated.

According to the Warlocks’ research, the Mother River only existed outside the living realm. This was because the Mother River’s water was made out of liquid aura and aura was made from the living being’s spiritual essence. This meant that new beings could be born there.

It was very much confirmed that living beings would exist near the Mother River.

Unsurprisingly, he immediately sensed a huge blue planet in the direction where he was heading to. It was as if the planet suddenly decided to appear in his senses.

Garen passed through a white barrier-like protective net and landed directly on the planet. What accompanied him by his sides were large amounts of debris. He seemed to have caught up to a large scale meteor shower…

***************

“…Mother Planet’s invisible defensive net has detected an abnormally huge meteor shower today. According to the researcher, the largest meteor has a radius of 2.1cm and the smallest one is just a few mm wide. They will be burnt up by the atmosphere and there would be no debris from the meteor shower…”

“You should eat more because you’ll need to go to school again tomorrow.”

Inside a rather simple white room, a family was having their lunch on a round table. There was a variety of tasty looking fried vegetables placed on the table. Steam subtly dissipated from the stew, giving off a mouthwatering fragrance.

At the table, there was a middle-aged woman who kept dropping vegetables into the bowl of a teenager.

There were two adults, one elder, and three children eating quietly on the table. All the plates were made from white porcelain and some part of them had already chipped off. It seemed that this family wasn’t that well off.

The white light in the room was slightly dimmed and there was very little furniture inside as well. There were only tables, chairs, television, sofa and a picture of an old man framed onto the wall. Other than that everything was white and clean.

The two adults’ faces were covered with wrinkles and both of them looked very tired. They were wearing their bleached working attires. They had golden hair, blue eyes, and sharp noses. However, their faces gave off an easterner’s vibe.

The television by the side was broadcasting the evening news repeatedly.

In the family, two of the younger siblings were looking at the big bowl of vegetable stew placed in the middle of the table. However, they didn’t reach out their hand to take it but to stare at the eldest one eating at one side.

“You should eat more. Remember to study well in school. Your dad and I have suffered so much because we didn’t do well back then,” the middle-aged woman kept passing more vegetables to the youngster.

“I know I know. How many times do you have to say it! You’re so annoying!” The black haired, blue eyed boy grumbled. Similar to the only elder in the table, he didn’t inherit his parent’s hair color. He had a long fringe which covered at least half of his face while a look of annoyance twisted his face as he casually replied to his mother’s nagging.

The teenager was in a clean uniform, and its collar and cuffs had a vertical blade emblem that was glowing faintly on it.

“Alright, I’m full,” the youngster placed down his bowl and hurried into his room. He immediately slammed his door after entering the room.

“Let’s eat,” it was only then the only elder voiced up while the remaining two children started reaching out their hand towards the food.

“Take it easy…” both middle-aged parents smiled as they gave half of the remaining stew to their children and the meats to the elderly.

“That’s enough. I’m an old grandma who can’t eat much. You guys can have it as both of you need to wake up early in the morning to work,” the elder sighed as she pushed away the offered meat.

Inside the room.

The black haired youngster ran to the only computer inside and switched it on.

His name was displayed at the corner of the computer: Nonosiva Lin.

Nonosiva was different from his peers of the same age. He was the only hope of his family as he had been admitted into the nation’s best mech academy, Lakyusaier, with his outstanding results during his middle school days. The academy was also known as the Blackboard Academy.

It was a very well known academy among the nearby states. It had a long history and had produced a lot of state-level senior generals. With the alliance segregated during the chaos, the districts were basically represented by the academy’s strength. This was because the academy had gathered all the powerful individuals into one and they possessed their own uniquely inherited mech sects. Out of all the academy, Blackboard Academy possessed the oldest combat strategies known in multiple states.

With Nonosiva admitted into such a prestigious academy, it was only natural that his family had placed all of their hopes on him.

In this society with its order on the verge of collapse, the academy had the most authority as it led the government’s military and acted as its guardian. It was every man’s dream to be able to become an official Mech Pilot.

Nonosiva switched on his computer and quickly entered into the homepage called the new Blackboard Academy. As he was requested to enter his password, he used a scanner to scan the blue blade shaped emblem on his collar.

The black website then revealed that the password was correct. After validating his access, he immediately went to the database.

The Combat Techniques for all sorts of mechs appeared on the menu.

Level one Curved Steps, Level one Lightsaber, Level one Cannon Fire Control, Level one Magnetic Cannon Technique, Level one Life Cycle Maintenance…

Knowledge was categorized in detail and was displayed on the menu.

Nonosiva ignored the purchasing catalog and went to the very bottom to key in his personal information.

‘Nonosiva. Lin — Possessing Level one Curved Step, Possessing Level one Cannon Fire Control, Basic Awareness Module…’

To be able to receive an official rating meant that Nonosiva’s strength was considered very good among his peers. Most of his friends of the same age were still at the Basic level and were hence unqualified for a level rating.

One should know that it was extremely difficult to even achieve the lowest level. One would only be qualified for graduation after achieving level one in every subject within eight years of study inside the academy. Nonosiva had managed to obtain two level one qualifications before the start of his second year semester, which meant that his results were indeed very impressive. He had always been among the top three in his class.

He looked at his results and couldn’t help but to smile ecstatically. He unconsciously started touching the small crescent-shaped device inside his shirt.

Compared to those formidable students who had good family backgrounds and outstanding personal trainers who trained them daily, he who had obtained such an amazing achievement with his poor background was only able to do so with assistance.

He had a secret which would allow a normal student to improve rapidly and stand out from among tens of thousands of students and become one of the hundreds of elites admitted into the Blackboard Academy.

Chapter 771: Moments 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Fiddling with the Moonfang inside his pocket, he quickly registered for the assessment with his personal details.

“Nonosiva Lin, registering for the Level 1 assessment of Magnetic Cannon.”

The Magnetic Cannon was a weapon assembled with highly magnetic metal into a cannon that fired out at top speed, achieving the specific goal of destroying metal armor in a targeted long distance attack. However, because its recoil power was strong, it would naturally be difficult to be accurate with it.

“As long as the five levels are achieved, I’ll be eligible for professional tactics lessons!” Nonosiva mumbled, his heart blazing with determination.

Professional tactics: each one of them was the accumulative end result of different generations of research. They were huge techniques that were combined with all sorts of brilliant tactics using the most advanced optical computers. Even the legendary inheritance tactics were improved and developed versions of these basic tactics.

Currently, with the operation of the Will-powered Mech over the past few hundred years, there have been countless tactics that trained the consciousness. In terms of mech operating, it seemed to have reached a peaking point.

The Mother Planet Federation and the Galactic Alliance were facing the threat of the Finite War, which had been going on for thousands of years and was soon reaching a critical point.

All sorts of different consciousnesses have brought along their own trademarks and strengths. Even though they came in waves, the weak were eradicated and now only the cream of the crop remained.

Every time Nonovisa reminisced about this magnificent history, there was always a desire and impulse that he could not suppress. It was said that during the campaign, there was a mech that was the strongest, which could change the situation on the battlefield on its own. It was hailed as a miracle.

He gripped the Moonfang in his pockets.

“I’ve got this in the bag, I can certainly pass the assessment easily!” he was strangely confident of the Moonfang that he’d unexpectedly obtained. His love and passion for the mech was also a reason why he’d chosen to enter into the school’s mech ranks.

It had been revealed he only had normal intellectual requirements, but with this Moonfang, he was able to overcome this step and enter Blackboard Academy.

The Moonfang had an automated control mech which helped with manipulating the battle, if it was on one’s person, it would provide one with assistance.

Automatically calculating the projectile track while automatically avoiding any obstacle, this was just some external hack!

Xu Wei adjusted the webpage in frustration while carefully looking over anything that was related to the assessment.

He believed that as long as he has the Moonfang, he would easily pass.

Nonosiva had been born into a very poor family; his parents were only ordinary office workers and the pay was just average. Meanwhile, Blackboard Academy’s fees were very expensive, and there was still a huge sum to pay as a security deposit, in case any practice mech was damaged.

To ensure that he got to attend the academy, both of them did their best to save what they could borrow from people. Only then were they able to gather a smaller sum for his school fees and security deposit, although they still had to pay the bank loan’s interest each month.

This high-class academy was unusually expensive, so in order to allow their older brother to have a chance to succeed, the younger brother and sister gave up their chance to further their studies, even though both of them had good grades.

He also became the family’s only hope; everyone was proud to say that he was the oldest brother or child to outsiders, and they even let him eat his fill of the non-manufactured food first before they started eating it themselves when they were home.

Dong…

The doorbell chimed.

“What?” Nonosiva was always very focused when reading his materials, and it made him impatient whenever he was disturbed.

“Nono, your points for this month have been added to your card,” his father Rondo said.

“Okay!” Nonosiva was warmer this time. Him applying for this assessment was exactly the time that he needed the money, and there were also a few things that he wanted to buy but did not have the money to.

His father Rondo coughed a few times, then left to rest.

Nonosiva stood up, walked to the door and had a look. On the bench next to the door, there was a white card, and there were blue, faintly shimmering digital numbers on the top.

He held it up and used his fingers to give the number a swipe, the numbers immediately changed.

“Only this little!!!? Nono’s face changed, “How is this enough for me!!?” He eyed his parent’s room, his face twisted hideously.

Bang!

Slamming the door loudly, Nono angrily marched back in front of his computer.

He was not content! When compared with other students, his family was not all that bad, but the other students were ampler than he was most of the time.

This could not be helped, as the families that were able to be involved with mechs were naturally slightly well off. On the contrary, there were not a lot of students who were lucky like him.

Rumble….

Suddenly, there was a clap of thunder rolling, and the window was slightly vibrating from it.

By the window, the black curtain was flapping in the wind, blocking Nono’s sight and flying in his face.

“That was a big wind…” he quickly got up to close the window.

Swoosh!

A bit of black light suddenly flew in from outside the window. It came in at an angle where it was blocked by the curtain and it suddenly stuck on his body before disappearing.

“What bug was that?” Nono jumped and closed the window before checking over his body carefully. He’d felt like something has collided with his body just now, maybe it was a small bug.

He looked for a while but did not find anything, so he went back to where he was previously and sat down.

He never noticed that there were now tiny lines of blood vessels on his face that looked like a fine, blood-red web that covered his face, which was rather horrifying.

Nono was only focused on the computer screen, showing no signs of distraction.

Luckily the blood vessels on his face were only there for a while before they slowly vanished back into his skin.

The next day

Blackboard Academy basic training field

Amidst the field of black sand, two gray humanoid mechs stood facing each other. They were surrounded by a multitude of red dots, each representing a surveillance detector.

Two bots standing motionless while surrounded by red lights, it was eerily peaceful.

The grey mech that had a shape like it was holding its belly started to have puffs of air jetting out from behind it.

The mech was about five meters tall, and in the middle of its metal belly was a small glass window. Inside was a seventeen or eighteen-year-old teenager seated there.

“Today’s fifth assessment, ready!” a bearded man shouted from the side of the field. He was in his 30s or 40s and was a tall and burly man. He had tanned skin, a beaten-down look and was wearing a green cap.

Next to the man stood many similarly aged teenagers. There were guys and girls, all clad in the Blackboard Academy uniform.

“The shooting training is secure, move out, move out, all non-related personals please leave the danger zone…” a calm robotic female voice rang throughout the field.

The man glanced at both of the students inside the mechs.

“The official assessment is a fight to the death, you guys be careful,” he called loudly, his voice full of confidence.

Seeing the “no problem” sign given by both mech pilots, he nodded. He illuminated his hands and then waved them down furiously.

“Begin!”

Woo…

Two deep sounds of engines revving up rumbled suddenly.

The mechs in the field started up at the same time, whipping out a grey-white pistol, and aiming at the opponent.

The bearded man nodded, then started to explain to the students next to him.

“Their movement is not bad, you see the pistol in their hands? That is a magnetic gun. There is no need for the real magnetic cannon in the assessment. Even though this magnetic pistol does not have the same power, it has a recoil power similar to the magnetic cannon and it’s very cost-effective to use in practice.”

The students next to him all nodded.

“Then do you think Nonosiva can pass his assessment this time?” a girl with brown wavy hair, dark skin and a normal face asked.

“Mina, are you two friends?” the teacher looked at her. “This is up to him to decide, but the first few assessments were not bad, so his chances of passing are high.”

“Nono is the third place of our class, but he only registered to take the level one assessment when he’s in the second year now… ” the boy next to Mina whispered.

“All of you work hard, then you may be in his place too!” the teacher smiled in agreement.

Before the voices died down, the two mechs had suddenly started moving and shooting at the same time.

Red sparks could be seen at the mouth of the pistol briefly, but both the mechs seemed to have failed, missing each other. Instead, they were pushed backward violently by the recoil.

The two in the field were like two grey animals, expanding their arcs quickly and avoiding all the possible areas the other could aim at. In a flash, there was dust everywhere, and only thundering engine sounds could be heard.

They shot out magnetic bullets, managing to hit only the empty fields behind each other after missing before they were temporarily blocked by an invisible, corrugated barrier.

Inside one of the mech, Nonosiva had one hand on one joystick, while the other was typing quickly on the tight-knit panel of buttons next to the joystick.

He was not in sync with the mech’s mechanism; his speed when it came to robot control was not very quick, and there were a lot of moves that he was not able to do, hence the mech would dodge on its own.

At this time, next to the mech’s control system, there was a small white silver Moonfang that emitted a white pale glow as if there was something fluorescent within, and there was a faint sound of grinding gears coming from it.

“I am someone with a secret weapon! Hahaha!!” Nonosiva would become irritable every time he got into the mech, it was a contrast to his usual quiet self. It was as if all the pressure he suppressed were freely expressed here.

The round screen in front suddenly shook violently; the mech also started to avoid the opponent’s shots.

His third shot had better accuracy than the previous two, and Nono’s face glowed with satisfaction. However, using his willpower to control the mech was very draining. Controlling the mech with willpower while supporting manually with the control interface was currently the most popular method of control.

However, to him, it was still a heavy load. As the mech quickly adjusted the steering, the huge amount of inertia created was something that he as the driver needed to take up.

He did not realize that the Moonfang next to his hand has already been moved due to the movement of the mech and small cracks could already be seen. The temperature inside was getting higher and higher.

Chapter 772: Moment 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Nono was still immersed in capturing his opponent in the shooting game and did not feel any different.

The Moonfang that he’d acquired was actually made from parts of the control assistance of a high-end mech. The resources inside were not much even in the beginning, and after idling and then being used for so long, the resources inside had nearly been used up. On top of that, it did not have a cooling feature, and as the high temperature from its usage was unable to be cooled down, the Moonfang started to crack.

Kachak!

Suddenly, there was a crisp sound, but it was immediately drowned out by the mech’s machinery noises inside the cockpit. Nono did not realize this at all, that the crescent moon had slowly dimmed, losing its previous white glow.

The mech rolled to the right, avoiding the fourth shot from the opponent.

As Nono rested for a while, he saw that the opponent’s mech was adjusting its pistol. He recognized this as the technique of a two-timed reload, but he did not panic. Even though his control speed was unable to react to the incoming attack in time, considering that his real skills were only that of a beginner’s, this kind of moment was always aided by the Moonfang’s automated control to avoid attacks like these.

His finger was already clicking on the fire pistol button, and now all he had to do was to wait to avoid the opponent’s attack and then, attack.

Suddenly he felt that something was wrong, why was the mech not moving?!

“What is going on!!??” he saw that the opponent’s pistol was pointing towards him, but the mech remained quiet and he was now panicking slightly. He glanced at his Moonfang briefly, only to realize that it had cracked open and that there was no longer any light inside.

“No!!! My Moonfang!!”

He cried out loud, his eyes reflecting unspoken horror. If the magnetic pistol hit the cockpit, he would be disabled, if not dead!

He tried to grab hold of the Moonfang, but the sudden wave of fear in his body had paralyzed him! His whole body was frozen and he could not even move a finger.

At that moment, the pistol was getting lower and lower, and the finger on the faraway mech had already pulled the trigger.

“I don’t want to die!!! No! No!!” Nono finally broke down, he cried, his face dripping with tears.

“If you don’t want to die, then give me the body…” a voice from his heart rang.

No one could see it, but Nono’s face was suddenly covered in multiple blood vessels. A huge, terrifying web of blood vessels covered his face in an instant.

A dot of black passed by his deep blue eyes.

Crash!!!

Nono only felt his head being flung, his consciousness that was full of fear was now filled with satisfaction. He avoided the situation that he was the most fearful of, plunging straight into the unnaturally tranquil dark…

It was only for a moment that he lost complete consciousness. He was contented, he was away from danger, but he didn’t know that once he sank, he would never have a chance to wake up again.

The changes in the soul were abnormally complicated, but in the outside world, only a moment had passed.

Nonon opened both his eyes wildly. His irises were now an unnerving black.

At that moment all the fear in his face vanished, and it was replaced by a peaceful and calm expression.

Bang!

The magnetic cannon was fired.

Red sparks were seen as the pistol’s grey bullet headed straight for the mech’s cockpit.

“Something’s not right!!!” Garen had just accepted this body, and it felt wrong!

The strength of his soul was restrained in the body and he was unable to use his strength. And this was not even the most troublesome part; the most dangerous thing was that the inner body structure and genetic arrangement of the humans here were different from the last two bodies that he had reincarnated into! Completely different!

A piercing pain jolted the body that he’d just occupied. That was because the spirit was too powerful for the vessel that it’d occupied.

This kind of grinding caused him to be unable to connect with the nerves completely in the body, and so even moving was extremely difficult. His whole body was in piercing pain as if a drill was digging into his bones.

Garen tried his best to slow down the magnetic bullet, but it was too lates as he could only connect to his five senses in such a short span.

The magnetic bullet was about to hit the cockpit, and if it was hit, this body that he had not mastered yet would be seriously wounded. A great amount of strength from the soul seed was needed to occupy a body and it could not be undone after it was occupied, otherwise, the strength of soul used earlier would be wasted. In his current situation, he could not bear to suffer this loss, for the soul seed would face a danger of collapsing.

The most important thing was once he had occupied the body, it was equivalent to having a legal identity in this world. Should this legal identity perish, he would be decomposed forcefully by the laws of this world and there was even a possibility of him being sent back to the river.

“What should I do!!?” Garen was thinking swiftly. He had not anticipated the incompatibilities between the body and his soul. His initial plan had been to take over the body during a crucial moment when the original body was weak, but this situation was unexpected.

There was now a sense of an impending threat. According to this weak body, there was no way to block such a powerful weapon.

——-

At the field

Of the two mechs, as the one of the left lifted its arm to fire, the one on the right unexpected froze. Its fluid motions had suddenly stopped.

Bang!

The gun went off.

The students standing next to the teacher all shouted in shock at the scene. Each of their faces was nervous, and their eyes were all wide open.

“What’s going on? Why did Nono stop!”

“Is there something wrong with the mech?”

“He’s done for, he’ll be heavily injured if not dead!”

No one would have expected this outcome, and even the teacher had his mouth wide open. Even though Blackboard Academy always used the rule of survival of the fittest to run the school, if it really happened it would be a murder case, and even if the mech was faulty, there would still be punishment, even for him.

Moreover, Nono was one of his class’ best students, one of the top three, and if anything happened, it would be a big hit to his class.

But it was too late now, no one knew what to do. Even if they called for a halt it would be too late.

Mina was covering her mouth with her eyes full of shock and horror; she could do nothing to help.

Just at this moment.

On the field, on Nono’s mech curled-up arm, its arm’s magnetic pistol suddenly readjusted its aim and pulled the trigger.

Bang!

The two bullets missed each other, but the huge recoil shook Nono’s mech violently.

One in front and one at the back, both mechs seemed to be hit at the same time.

The examinee that had fired the first shot did not manage to avoid it because he was stunned, and he knew that Nonosiva’s mech was a sure hit.

After the two shots were blundered, both mechs had a small hole that the grey bullet was stuck in, from which leaked green smoke. The bullet was still moving but it had slowed down drastically as if it had already pierced halfway through the mech.

As Nono’s mech had been pushed back by the recoil, causing the cockpit to move, it was the shoulder that had been shot. Even though the mech was destroyed, its pilot was okay.

Only then did the audience let out sighs of relief. Wiping the sweat from his forehead, the teacher was relieved. Nonosiva really was his class’ best student and he was burdened with high hopes, so if anything happened here…

“Not good! The mech on the other side got hit in the energy module!!” a student shouted out.

The bearded man was snapped out of his relief.

Judging the other mech’s condition, his face started to become twisted again.

“Come save him quick!!” he yelled.

There was a bang from the other mech at this moment and the entire mech had exploded. Half of the body was covered in flames, and the fate of the driver inside was unknown.

——–

Garen sat in the cockpit, his whole body drenched in sweat. Underneath his skin, the nerves of his muscles kept twitching, sending wave after wave of pain to his brain.

“This is entirely different… This body… No! Everyone’s body here is entirely different! The structure of it is entirely different!!” he shuddered.

If it wasn’t for him pushing Nono’s spirit out completely at the final moment, lending his spirit as a last resort source of energy and using his consciousness to control the mech slightly, it would have been the end just now. If he did not have his body, the hard work from the previous world would definitely be all for naught,

But the current situation wasn’t really great.

The body was still violently rejecting him at times.

This was the best body he could find after entering this planet and searching everywhere for the most suitable vessel. However, he couldn’t have known that the body’s genetics were completely different from the previous bodies’.

Even though he was currently using his spirit to force the body to readjust, it was impossible to be active in the body in a short amount of time. The body was stiff, and he could not make even a single movement. It was as though he was a living corpse, and all he could do was to blink.

It was because he’d suddenly forced the body to move, which had caused Nono’s body to be even more injured. A lot of his nerves were damaged, and it was not the best of situations.

To put it frankly, there was no difference between him and a vegetable.

Even if he fully grasped the body, it was still a long genetic rearranging and adapting process. Garen felt that this world’s structure seemed to be firmer than the Blood Breed’s world; it was as if it would have a huge rejection and suppression of any non-homologous substance.

He’d already felt it when he was searching everywhere for a body while in the state of the spirit soul seed.

From Nono’s shattered spirit’s stored memories, he saw the control method of the mech; it was the special power that was produced from humans’ specially trained bodies. In other words, it was a special energy field.

It was completely different from his spirit’s strength and mental strength; it was a brand new force above the mental concentration power.

“This could be trouble…”

Feeling the differences in his body, his heart sank.

He could no longer guarantee that the body was able to completely recover, and if it couldn’t recover…

Chapter 773: Lowest Point 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When everyone lent a hand to rescue the pilots from the two mechs, they discovered that both of them were already unmoving.

On one side, Garen’s entire body was spasming while his eyes were tightly shut. It seemed as though his whole body was convulsing in an abnormal, terrifying manner.

Meanwhile, the other blue-haired youth’s whole body was blackened with burn wounds. He had already fallen into a coma and was unaware of his current situation.

Both of their conditions were unusually severe, prompting the bearded instructor to contact the hospital immediately when he noticed trouble. The ambulance from the hospital arrived swiftly and took both of them away.

The remaining group of students watched the ambulance leave. Only a few people and instructors got into the ambulance and rode with it while others went to inform the school authorities and leaders to record the state of the accident and injuries. Injuries like these on school grounds were common and would require people to come over and determine if there were mishaps with the mechs. However, cases involving flawed mechs were extremely rare in this school.

“I really don’t know why Nonosiva’s mech stopped moving suddenly. If that had not happened, this problem would not have happened during this test.”

“Who knows. Perhaps Nono himself had an illness that broke out unexpectedly?”

“No way. He would have undergone a full physical examination when he entered the school.”

Students from various classes discussed among themselves in hushed tones before going their separate ways and walking towards their dorms. The test instructors had left and it was obvious that the remaining tests that were supposed to be held today were canceled.

One white-haired youth furrowed his eyebrows and stood there for awhile while looking in the direction the ambulance had gone before leaving slowly.

His name was Fervale and he was one of the top three students of class C5. He was the No. 1 student in his class throughout the entire year, and almost no one could shake him from his solid position.

He could already understand the individual in second place clearly. There were still certain qualities which that person lacked, and this created a distance between them. Fervale was confident that he could keep this distance between them until graduation. However, he could not understand the student in third place, Nonosiva, properly. That person was extremely quiet, and only a few people were interested in being his friend in class. Therefore, not much information was known about him.

“But this is meaningless now. These standards don’t scare me,” he mumbled to himself softly before turning around and walking towards the simulation training area.

*********************

The ceiling was white.

When Garen opened his eyes, the first thing that he saw was a clean white stretch. There were faint dark blue fluorescent electric circuits twinkling on the ceiling that looked very high-tech.

“You’re awake?”

He heard a voice beside his left ear. The voice was not speaking in a distinct language but a strange tongue-curling type of language instead. Fortunately, he was able to understand it because he had absorbed Nono’s language memories.

He remembered that they were words from the Federation’s language.

The person was speaking in a male voice that sounded somewhat gruff.

Garen tried to turn his head towards the side determinedly to look at the speaker, but the stiff muscles and nerves throughout his whole body would not listen to his commands at all.

He finally saw a muscular man with a full faced beard stand up. A large face then appeared as the man lowered his head and stared at him. He looked to be around thirty to forty years of age, and his eyebrows were slightly furrowed.

“How do you feel? Are you alright?”

Garen tried to open his mouth determinedly. He recognized this man as Hamm, the instructor who was in charge of the class that the previous owner of his body was studying under. Although he wanted to answer, he was unfortunately unable to control the nerves on his face and could only blink and make murmuring noises at the back of his throat.

“You can’t even speak?” a disappointed look flashed in the man’s eyes. “The doctor’s diagnosis said that the nerves in your entire body suffered serious injuries while your muscles have cramped up. They could only force you to relax by injecting you with a tranquilizer.”

Garen made a few murmuring noises. He was still unable to speak and was getting impatient because of his inability to move.

“Big brother Nono, are you alright?” said a female voice beside him. The instructor quickly used his hands to turn Garen’s face towards the side slightly before he was able to see the situation on his left side instantly.

There were four male and female students sitting on his bedside currently. The one who spoke earlier was a delicate and pretty girl with a beautiful figure. This girl had short red hair and was currently gazing at him with great concern.

Fragments of memories floated up in Garen’s mind suddenly.

This girl’s name was Lisa and she was the current girlfriend of Nonosiva whose body he was currently inhabiting.

There were three other people besides Lisa; Nono’s friend Aier, his partner in crime Mina, and another person whom he did not really recognize.

The three students who were dressed in white school uniforms and blue suspenders sat beside him and looked over with concerned gazes.

“He can’t speak. He suffered nerve damage and it’s going to be extremely troublesome now,” said the instructor softly on the sidelines.

“Did the doctor mention the cause of this?” asked Lisa.

“He doesn’t know,” Instructor Hamm shook his head.

Garen listened to both of them speak on the side while he tidied Nono’s remaining memories quickly. The strong force that exploded outwards when he’d forcefully pushed Nono’s soul out to control the mech had created a sudden tear in his soul. Therefore, a large part of the fragments had either dispersed or disappeared. As Garen was only able to absorb the few remaining bits, the memories that he gained were incomplete.

From the conversation between the few students and Instructor Hamm, his current situation was extremely serious. He would need to recuperate for a year so that his injured nerves and muscles could heal after the surgery.

Garen observed the few people who had arrived carefully. Through Nonosiva’s memories, he knew that they were the only few people whom Nono considered as friends. Lisa was his girlfriend while Aier was his good friend and practice partner whom he had the best relationship with. Meanwhile, Mina was his seatmate and partner in crime whom he had always been on good terms with.

He did not have a deep impression of the last person as they probably did not have a close relationship.

When he heard them chatting, Garen gradually understood the entire situation.

Nonosiva was a quiet person who did not have many friends in class. The only people that he was on good terms with were the ones who were present here. He was usually a cold, arrogant person who would not approach strangers. In reality, he was also concealing his Moonfang secret. However, in the eyes of outsiders, he seemed icy and prideful.

Now, he had suffered severe injuries unexpectedly and had almost turned into a human vegetable. However, the instructor had mentioned that there might be a way to quicken his recovery. Unfortunately, he would then owe the academy a large sum of money for his medical fees. The opposing mech pilot that he’d wounded had also suffered serious injuries and would also require expensive medical fees.

“Inform his family then.”

Instructor Hamm made the final decision before standing up.

“I still have matters to sort out so I’ll be leaving first.”

It seemed as though he was in a bad mood as he took long strides out of the ward before the sound of a closing door could be heard around the corner quickly.

Nonosiva’s few close friends were the only ones left sitting in the room now.

Once the instructor had left, the few people who remained quickly became agitated and unsure of what to say.

“Nono, rest well. I have some things to do too so I’ll come and see you again later,” his girlfriend Lisa ground her teeth and stood up while speaking softly. Her cheeks were red and she lowered her head.

The sound of a shutting door could be heard quickly again. The student whom he was not very familiar with got up and left silently as well.

Only Aier and Mina remained in the room.

Aier had short brown hair and looked like a regular and somewhat gentle youth. He took an apple out silently and began to peel it.

“Nono, just relax and recuperate. With your standards, you’ll be able to catch up quickly when you’re better. Don’t worry.”

Garen blinked in response.

Mina sighed.

“Your parents are almost here. They’ll be at the hospital soon enough.”

Garen continued to blink.

The few of them stopped speaking at once… They could only sigh at the thought of Nono encountering an unexpected hardship like this despite being one of the elite students. However, both of them were Nono’s best friends and were extremely confident that he would recover quickly. Although he would owe the academy a large sum of money, he would be able to pay off that debt in the future.

Both of them became bored while sitting on the side before they began to talk about how this situation occurred suddenly during the test.

Garen lay on the sickbed and closed his eyes slowly while pretending to be asleep.

Soon, he could faintly hear the sound of the parents of this body rushing over. Other than the parents, the younger brothers and sisters had arrived as well before the ward was filled with the unsuppressed sobbing noises.

Nono’s family had average financial circumstances. It was already extremely difficult to provide for his university fees and they were only able to this by giving up the school fees of his younger siblings. The current need to fork out this large sum of money added more wrinkles on the faces of the two adults while their gazes began to darken as well.

“Relax, relax. Nono possesses powerful strength and he’s such an excellent student. Won’t it be a simple task for him to earn big bucks once he has passed the test to become a mech pilot?” consoled Mina frantically.

Aier agreed quickly as well and explained how mech pilots would earn their money while mentioning their yearly income that was worth millions. Coupled with their high remuneration and benefits, he would be able to clear his debts within a year. It was no big deal.

This improved the expressions the faces of Nono’s parents slightly.

Garen opened his eyes halfway and made a few murmuring noises to acknowledge his parents and younger siblings.

Since he had occupied this body, he would naturally need to accept this identity.

Next, the nurse came in and wiped down Garen’s body while the other people who were waiting inside the ward earlier went out and waited.

Garen had finally gotten an interval to check his current body.

He closed his eyes as his spirit sunk into his body. All of his blood veins, meridians, and organs within his entire body appeared inside his soul.

He checked all of them carefully and could not help but sigh.

“This difference… It is somewhat wide… On the surface, it seemed similar to the bodies that I inhabited in the two previous worlds. However, it’s actually completely different as the fine cell mechanisms are completely different.”

His soul was born from his bodies from the two previous worlds. While he was currently occupying this body, there were extremely strong reactions of incompatibility which had resulted in his inability to control his body until now.

Both of his soul seeds were constantly releasing qi to modify this body. Unfortunately, the soul seeds had undergone consumptions that were too great in the Mother Stream. They could only modify themselves slowly at an extremely prolonged pace.

Garen shifted his vision towards his own Attribute Pane. Apparently, huge changes had occurred throughout his Attribute Pane because his body had changed as well.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 0.5, Agility 1.1, Vitality 0.3, Intelligence 1.3. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 40.’

“Apparently my Soul Limit has upgraded because of my soul seeds. This is the only bit of good news.”

Garen’s mind was slightly consoled and he continued looking downwards.

‘Potential — Void Pursuer’

‘Soul — Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, Holy Phoenix Demonic Book.’

‘Secret Technique — None’

When he saw that his Secret Technique Pane had returned to zero, impatient feelings immediately stirred in Garen’s mind. He already knew that condensing his soul seeds would mean that everything that he had practiced throughout his life would be condensed inside as well, leaving him with nothing. However, this still troubled him although it had already happened twice.

He began to check on the more detailed parts of his current body such as the functions of the various systems, operations, and cycles. As a martial arts master, he naturally possessed extremely impressive foresight that allowed him to reach a conclusion from the first step quickly.

Chapter 774: Lowest Point 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This body is completely unsuitable for practicing advanced martial arts…” Garen’s thoughts sank into depression at once. As this new body build was different, it could not adapt to the practices of various Secret Techniques. Moreover, a lot of time and energy would be required to modify this body to suit it to advanced Secret Techniques. Unfortunately, this was something that he could not afford to waste time on right now.

He could only practice certain low level, average Secret Techniques such as martial arts that were used for muscle training or Secret Techniques that did not involve the control of vital energy. Pure martial arts like these which did not involve actively controlling vital energy were merely third-rate Secret Techniques that were far from White Cloud Secret Techniques.

“Unless I modify this body completely into my previous build…” Garen began to ponder on which path he should take in the future.

This world looked more powerful than the previous worlds. While he was travelling back and forth across planets, he could see an unimaginably large invisible protection belt that was miles apart from the space that Earth occupied.

Through Nono’s remaining memories, he knew that this planet was probably attached to a large country called the Mother Planet Federation. Not only did this federation possess a planet, there were actually more than forty-five planets. It was worthy to be called a colossus.

It belonged to a completely different level from the previous other planets.

There were star rated countries which also possessed numerous planet nations. Most of these countries were attached to a larger nation called the Galactic Alliance. Both of them had been cooperating to resist the Finite people for more than a thousand years.

During this resistance, there were other neutral parties besides the Mother Planet Federation and Galactic Alliance. They were a thousand in total and they were of various sizes, and they imparted continuous support to maintain the balance between these three giants. There were five or six planets that were larger countries and one or two smaller ones that relied on different specialities to ensure their continuous lengthy existences.

Meanwhile, this body that he was currently inhabiting was one of the citizens who was living inside the colossus known as the Mother Planet Federation.

However, the current situation was becoming less stable recently. The chaotic struggle and war between the three main forces had continued on for too long. It had created various debts within the country and increased the indignation between the population. In an unexpected sweep, all three forces were hit by a powerful financial storm that almost toppled their constitution. The public credibility of the national government was lost completely while the three main forces fell into internal chaos. Each major fleet set up a established an independent regime and almost formed separatist warlord regimes.

The planet where Nono was living in was one of the planets that were controlled by the Mother Planet Federation. However, since it had already fallen into complete chaos, various powerful forces were now occupying its territory to develop themselves willfully.

The place where they were living was part of the range that was controlled by the Blackboard Academy.

“It’s really such a chaotic place…” this was the first time Garen had stepped into a world like this. It was humongous, extensive, and vast. By using a planet as a unit, certain powerful and first-rate fleets and extremely terrifying Star Cannons would be able to destroy a planet instantly.

Worlds like these could be considered as technologically-advanced peak worlds. Garen knew this and was worried that he would need to behave himself when Nadia arrived, as there were terrifying major war weapons like Star Cannons here.

Even if he was able to practice his Secret Techniques, he knew that relying on them while going on a rampage was still a wild idea…

He calculated for a moment and realised that even if he managed to reach his 40-point Soul Limit, it could only resist the equivalent of a nuclear or hydrogen bomb. It would not be able to resist a Star Cannon that could destroy an entire planet, as the difference between their powers were simply as different as night and day.

Other than Star Cannons, he was afraid of the war weapons in this world that could hurt his body to its limits. Terrifying civilizations that could control more than ten planets would definitely not be so simple.

“Looks like I won’t be able to use the Secret Technique method directly anymore. If I want to condense any more Soul Seeds in this world, I should test out the power systems here.”

Garen began to recall the remaining memory fragments in Nono’s mind before transferring all of the information regarding the power systems here.

Unfortunately, Nono was too weak and could access any high level information. Meanwhile, only a few pieces of his fragmented soul remained, making it completely impossible to view its contents. Only some information regarding the topics that were covered in the grading test remained.

“Mech Pilots can use their Willpower to control the high level fighters during Mech battles. Powerful Mech Pilots can get the Mechs to release terrifying battle abilities. There was even a record of a Mech that was able to defeat an entire fleet during a campaign. This was the ultimate instance of personal heroism.”

Garen browsed through these fragmented memories carefully.

“Strong and high-level Mech Pilots and equally powerful Mechs are almost equivalent to undefeatable strategic existences.”

“High rates of casualties inflicted by powerful and advanced weapons allowed Mechs to become terrifying war weapons that could even overtake battleships. Various Mech sects emerged and heralded a historic era. These sects used various Mech battling styles and specialized and celebrated abilities. The Blackboard Academy’s inherited sect used a suspended black disc as a well-known, high-speed cutting weapon and is considered as a purely long-range attack sect.”

Garen scrutinized the remaining bits of information carefully.

He could vaguely feel that the Willpower in this world could greatly benefit his third condensed Soul Seed. Perhaps this was the fundamental route to condensing his third Soul Seed. According to Nono’s memories, the time and space of this universe had already developed his Willpower to a frightening level that was vast and endless. Numerous impressive figures of the past who had a place in history had once walked a great distance on this path.

According to certain legends, there were sects that could use their Willpower to strengthen normal Mechs greatly and achieve powers that were vastly improved. There were even sects that could practice terrifying specialized abilities through their Willpower, allowing their Mechs to have strange specialized abilities.

When a Mech Pilot integrated their Mechs with their Willpower, the powers that were produced were not as simple as adding one with the other. On the contrary, it was rumored that they would form terrifyingly taboo Mechs that could overpower dying stars.

“In this world, Willpower is everything. It is an invisible form of unnatural powers that anyone can grasp. However, the difference lies between the condition of their natural talents.”

Garen’s mind understood everything.

Although Nono had not left many fragments behind, the amount of information was still enough to surprise his mind.

The strength of this current world and universe had surpassed the previous worlds by an unknown degree.

Willpower was like a specialized unnatural power that could only be utilized through Willpower Mechs and other facilities. Meanwhile, every single Mech Pilot was a powerful existence that was constantly unearthing their strong Willpower.

Vigilant feelings formed in Garen’s mind. Since this world had already possessed thorough research on something as insubstantial as Willpower, it was very likely that they would also be one step ahead in their Soul Seed research. It seemed like he would need to be even more careful from now on.

It was fortunate that there were no unexpected or strange occurrences when he reincarnated this time.

Even at peak levels, his current powers could not even be compared to the size of a domain of the planet, much less a dying star. Perhaps Nadia would be able to reach this degree if she used her the full extent of her powers at once.

This was an Army-level strength!

Garen doubted that an existence that had achieved the Demon King level of Ancient Endor existed in this world. However, it was fortunate that it was merely a rumor.

“No, the powers of the Dying Star Level may be even stronger than the Demon King Level. They merely have different systems,” Garen compared them in his mind quietly. He was becoming slightly more in awe of this world.

“Seems like I can only advance according to the systems of this world. My top priority right now is to heal my body first. I’ll forget about modifying it for now as long as I’m able to allow this body to get used to my soul to get rid of the rejection reactions.”

Garen made up his mind and began to carefully control the vital energy that his Soul Seeds were releasing so that his body could adapt.

On the surface, he was merely closing his eyes and resting.

Once the nurse had finished wiping down his body, she took the water and left. His parents, younger siblings, and friends then entered and chatted softly for a while. Soon after, his family left the room, as they were worried that they would disturb him.

When Aier and Mina saw this, they too got up and left as well. They placed some money at his bedside quietly as a contribution.

Meanwhile, Garen continued to drift into the process of adjusting his body. However, it took a long time as his nerves had suffered serious injuries. In order to heal himself without losing his Soul Seeds, he would need to wait at least five years. Unfortunately, this duration was far too long.

Therefore, it was important for him to wait until the restoration surgery. The medical techniques of this time period would be extremely advanced now and there would definitely be impressive basic techniques to repair damaged nerves.

As long as the nerve restoration surgery succeeded, there was a chance that he could shorten the time period. He would be able to adjust to this body completely within half a year without any after effects.

Although he could not practice advanced Secret Techniques, some pure mental training and simple aura and muscle exercises could be used instead.

*********************

Time passed day by day.

Instructor Hamm came to visit Garen a few more times but did not say much. He was merely there so that Garen could feel relieved while recuperating and waiting for his operation.

While his parents left for work, his younger siblings would usually come over and take care of him. They would deliver meals and help clean the ward. This gave Garen a glimpse of this family’s unity.

However, the thing that made him feel the most helpless was the fact that his younger siblings seemed afraid of him. Although he was currently unable to move, he could still see that Nonosiva’s influence over them had been built over a long period of time. This caused his younger brother and sister to act frightened and cowardly around him.

Although he was unable to speak now and could only lie down, neither of his younger siblings dared to look him in the eye.

His few friends visited often as well. Mina had already come a few times and would always bring some money with her. Once, she had even brought a general ATM card with her. Usually, only individuals with at least a thousand dollars would be given these cards for their savings accounts. Although this was equivalent to the monthly earnings of an average adult, it was also the minimum monthly expense of a Blackboard Academy student.

However, Mina put the card down without a second word and left.

Later, Garen realized that this card contained money that was put aside by both Aier and Mina. This changed Garen’s initial impression of Nonosiva slightly. Despite his certain flaws, he could not be a terrible person if he had friends like these.

Meanwhile, his supposed girlfriend Lisa had disappeared and had not come to see him again after the first time. It was rumored that she was currently seeing another boy.

The upcoming operation approached.

******************

Blackboard Academy

There were lofty metallic buildings with black outer walls throughout the academy grounds. The exteriors of these buildings resembled gigantic black discs that were embedded within the ground.

When looking at it from afar, the academy seemed like a flat white area with more than ten black discs embedded there.

Some of these discs were larger than others and there would be a little door and entrance at the bottom. Cars and people moved between the black discs in a bustling manner. The academy was built below a tall mountain that was flattened. A large black battleship was parked at the top of the mountain where there were black symbols engraved on the surface. Meanwhile, the large academy grounds were located below the mountain.

The pointed nose of the front of the battleship stretched over the border of the mountain and hung over the sky above the academy, casting a large dark shadow over it.

Within a room in the front of the battleship.

Inside a black room, a group of people sat around a round silvery-white table. They were all dressed in black uniforms and were the teachers and instructors of the academy.

The Head Instructor and Vice Head Instructor were seated in the main seats.

“Regarding the five series of public funds that have been allocated by our academy during this semester for one of the students named Nonosiva, I personally feel that this should not be the academy’s responsibility. There were no problems with the Mechs or the site. Therefore, the academy is not obligated to bear the cost of his operation and compensation.”

The Head Instructor was a muscular man with bronze skin who glanced at everyone while he spoke.

Chapter 775: Misfortune 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was an independent council within the academy’s Mech actual combat department. The department was one of ten organizations that were responsible for the matters regarding actual combat. Despite being a grassroots council, it had the ultimate power to decide the allocated funds.

“Nonosiva? After testing the Mechs, we determined it was definitely not an accident caused by a Mech malfunction. There were no problems when we evaluated the site either. Therefore, we shouldn’t bear the responsibility,” a bespectacled middle-aged woman nodded in agreement beside him.

“I don’t think that’s right,” said Instructor Hamm while furrowing his eyebrows. “According to the rules of the whole academy, medical bills for wounds that were sustained during the curriculum need to be assumed by the academic departments. This student should definitely already have basic insurance after paying school fees for so many years.”

“However, our department is facing financial issues now. Take a look at the things that are written here… Nerve restoration operation,” the Head Instructor picked up a piece of white paper and furrowed his eyebrows while skimming through the information. “The cost of this operation is not insignificant. If we pay the full amount, it may affect this year’s performance bonuses…”

“The Head Instructor is right.”

“We should not be responsible for providing this sum of money in any way. He’s right, we don’t need to compensate him.”

“I am in favor of the Head Instructor’s suggestion.”

Everyone who was seated there was an instructor in this department. They were the primary teachers of the academy and had obviously voiced their opinions at once when they heard that their benefits would be affected.

Instructor Hamm’s expression became somewhat unpleasant.

“This isn’t right though. You shouldn’t openly go against the academy’s general rules…”

“People are alive but rules are not. The rules are just a piece of scrap paper if we don’t have the finances. We’re not merely being difficult, we just don’t have this ability,” said the Vice Head Instructor helplessly while shrugging his shoulders.

“That’s true, we can’t just affect the lives of everyone seated here just because of one of the students in your class. Isn’t that right, Instructor Hamm?” said someone else in a dissatisfied tone.

Hamm scanned his surroundings before his gaze finally fell upon the face of Head Instructor Dylan.

“He was wounded during a class test. Don’t tell me the academy actually plans to release him and let things run their course without a single concern? Won’t this make the other students in the school fearful?” he said loudly.

Head Instructor Dylan wrinkled his brow slightly.

“Hamm, you must remember that this is Blackboard Academy. Fearful? What is there to fear? People need to sharpen their minds to come here and those who fear will simply die when they go out into the world. Survival of the fittest and natural selection were the highest rules and school codes of the academy originally.”

“I disagree with your views!” said Hamm in an even louder tone. “When we signed the contract to join the academy, we already agreed to be responsible for these students to a certain degree! Once the students of the academy discover that we can’t even ensure their basic safety, the consequences will be unimaginable!” he attempted to persuade the Head Instructor again.

“Alright, that’s enough. The allocated funds for this incident have been decided,” Head Instructor Dylan raised his hand and exchanged glances with a few of the other instructors who were council representatives.

“Head Instructor!” Hamm stood up suddenly.

“Don’t waste your breath,” Dylan glanced at him indifferently. “The second item is written below. Instructions have been sent from the superiors. Recently, there were wanted criminals who may have passed by through the Federation. Everyone needs to return and tell the students to be more careful when they go out. Tell them not to visit dangerous places frequently. As for the matters regarding a new eastern branch of the academy that will be built, the previous plans can be brought up now…”

Fury began to burn in Hamm’s mind. He glanced around and noticed that the few instructors who were once close to him were now evading his gaze. Suddenly, a tremble ran through his mind.

“Good! Very good!”

He suppressed his inner fury before turning around and walking away.

********************

In the hospital corridor

“The operation fees cannot be postponed any longer,” said the doctor to Instructor Hamm while furrowing his eyebrows. “It’s already been two weeks. If you drag it on any longer, it will be too late even if we do proceed with the operation. You haven’t received the allocated funds from your side?”

Hamm nodded his head with a somber look on his face.

“If this goes on, I’m expecting that the situation will only worsen. If this boy’s nerves are not restored in time, he may even face problems walking in the future,” the doctor began to sound slightly impatient. “In the beginning, we agreed to prepare the operation measures beforehand because of the Blackboard Academy’s reputation. However, we’ve waited a long time for the funds to arrive. It’s almost time for us to place an order for our drugs, so what do you want us to do?”

Hamm remained silent. After coaching for so many years, the most exceptional students he had taught were Fervale and Nonosiva who ranked first and third in class respectively. Now, one of his best students who had the chance to become a true Mech Pilot in the future was about to lose his life over delayed operation fees. This made him feel extremely uneasy. Misfortune like this made him recall his own bitter experiences in the past. No one had been there to support him during that time, and he could only control his life with his own strength. Fortunately, he was able to control his fate in the end. However, his Willpower had decreased by more than half of its initial value because of his heavy injuries. Finally, he could only retire as a regular instructor at the academy.

“Trust me,” he took a deep breath and made up his mind instantly. “The funds will arrive soon enough. I’m going to urge them to hasten things so that the funds will arrive in full tomorrow!”

“Are you sure?” the doctor was somewhat doubtful.

“I’m sure! You can prepare to perform the operation already!” Hamm lit a cigarette and took a deep puff.

This was not his first time doing this anyway. To hell with them! He could just smoke less and save some money, right?

His mind became calm at once.

“Alright, I’ll trust you this time,” the doctor nodded. After all, they were friends. “I’ll go and inform the operation theatre then. Also, this is a non-smoking zone!”

“Okay.”

Hamm nodded and stubbed the cigarette on the rubbish bin beside him quickly.

*************

Garen lay on the sickbed. He was still unable to speak and could only make murmuring noises and blink his eyes. He could not do anything else.

This body had sustained extremely deep injuries that were impossible to heal in a short span of time.

His younger brother was carefully peeling a white pear beside him.

Garen could not move at all. Instead, he could only wait for his Soul Seeds to heal his body naturally. He observed his younger brother Alan and noticed that his face had lost much of its initial cowardice and was slightly more confident by now.

“Big Brother, you need to get well soon. You’ve been staying in the hospital for so many days and the hospital fees are so expensive. The recent earnings in our household have not been prosperous either…” his younger brother nagged him softly as if he was a little housewife.

This fellow was not more than fourteen or fifteen years old. However, it seemed as if he had not developed properly as he still resembled a twelve or thirteen-year-old. His black hair was constantly hanging downwards and covering half of his face. He liked lowering his head as well and always wore large framed glasses that made it impossible to see his features clearly. Meanwhile, his skin seemed sickly and pale.

He gave off a cowardly air that was not manly at all!

He was constantly hit and scolded by Nonosiva because he was disgusted and embarrassed by him. However, the younger boy had never retaliated.

He never expected that the younger brother who had always been bullied by him would now be the person that was taking care of him the most. Even his younger sister did not visit him as much as his brother.

“What’s his name?” Garen’s mind began to ponder. “Alan? Kellen? Or is it something else?”

He had not absorbed much of Nonosiva’s memory fragments. Therefore, he was still unclear about many things until now.

He could only obtain some information whenever his family arrived or he heard his younger siblings speak.

Knock knock knock.

The sound of someone knocking a door could be heard.

“Come in,” called his younger brother softly while standing up.

There was a squeaking noise when the door was pushed opened gently before Instructor Hamm walked inside.

“The operation is scheduled for tomorrow so get ready, Nono,” he said in a low voice while looking at Nono who was lying on the sickbed.

Garen blinked to show that he understood.

“The school has successfully reimbursed the medical fees. There will be a recovery period after the operation has been completed so just rest well in the hospital and don’t worry about anything else. As for your progress, there are many things that you don’t need to be frantic about,” Hamm attempted to soften his tone as much as possible, despite not knowing how to console others properly.

“Thank you, Uncle Hamm,” his younger brother stood on the side and bowed immediately to display his gratitude. Although he had merely increased his volume slightly to speak in a louder tone, his face and neck were flushed already.

“You must be Baylon. Good boy,” Hamm patted the younger boy’s shoulder and nodded. “Alright, I still have matters to attend to so I’ll return to the academy first. Take good care of your older brother.”

“Un… Understood…” Baylon was getting tongue-tied.

“It’s bad for young men to be easily embarrassed!” Baylon’s demeanor made Hamm laugh.

Once Hamm had left, Baylon closed the door properly and let out an unsuppressed cheer at once, “The operation fees have finally arrived!” he turned back to the front of the sickbed. “Many thanks to Uncle Instructor Hamm!”

Garen blinked in agreement.

“Big Brother, you’re going to get better soon,” said Baylon determinedly. However, he lowered his head in fear immediately when he saw Garen’s gaze shifting over and glaring at him. It was clear that he had recalled Nonosiva’s terrifying temper.

After receiving this good news, Garen could finally sigh in relief.

It was true that he could heal this body, but his Soul Seeds would definitely need to pay a heavy price and he’d incur great losses. Moreover, it would take a long time. With the current support of the operation, he would be able to restore his health quickly and control his body once again.

However, he could sense certain secrets regarding the medical fees through Instructor Hamm’s eyes earlier.

When his parents returned in the afternoon, they paid the warding fees with a tired look on their faces. They rested at his bedside for awhile and instructed young Baylon to take care of his older brother properly. Once they discovered that the operation fees would be reimbursed, the whole family was uncharacteristically happy and sighed in relief immediately.

It seemed as if his younger sister did not visit often because she was afraid of Nono. According to his parents, it seemed as though she liked going out a lot recently for unknown reasons. However, both of the parents were too busy working and had no time to pay attention to her. They were fine as long as she came home to eat and sleep on time.

Everything was moving in the right direction.

**********************

The cool moonlight of the night shrouded the entire Blackboard City in silvery gauze.

On a street somewhere in Blackboard City

Numerous magnetically levitated sedan cars moved along the roads constantly, their lights creating a dazzling light show. Drunkards could occasionally be seen waddling clumsily on both sides of the pavements, spewing nonsensical songs as they went on their way.

Between the black buildings beside the street, ten blinking black shadows could be seen vaguely. They flew and danced between the black buildings quickly.

Whenever these black shadows fell, they would not make a sound when they landed on the walls or roofs of the buildings. They resembled spiders that could land and climb up objects quietly before dropping somewhere else gently and jumping in another direction.

They flew around and passed through the sky but none of the cars or people below had noticed any trace of them.

“Disperse carefully!”

A voice echoed in the ears of one of the leaping black shadows.

“Mind your own business!”

It used a device to single-handedly stick itself to the wall before looking downwards at its surroundings. It jumped down suddenly and crashed into the glass window of the lofty building on the opposite side at once.

Crash!!

An ear-piercing alarm sounded at once while red light flashed and illuminated the entire floor.

A few black shadows rolled and evaded the red laser lights that were scanning about. They dodged the lasers as quietly and dexterously as leopards before arriving in front of a safe. One of them stretched its hands out before a fine needle sprang out and pierced the safe immediately.

Chapter 776: Misfortune 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was a clapping noise before the safe was opened. The black shadow took something out and retreated without looking back. The black shadows then leaped back out of the shattered glass window after a few somersaults. The entire process did not even last a minute. Their speed was terrifying!

“You dare leave?!” a white shadow flew inside with a strong gust of wind. It was actually a white Spider Mech that was more than five meters tall. A male voice echoed from the inside.

“I’ve been chasing you for half a month! Where are you going to run to now?!” the voice inside the Mech sounded somewhat exasperated.

“You want to catch me? Are you going to try?” the black figure sneered softly and did more than ten continuous backflips over the sloping wall of the skyscraper as if it was merely flat ground before jumping over the Spider Mech instantly.

Clap! He pressed something against the top of the Mech. However, the Spider Mech was completely unable to react in time. Both of their reaction speeds were on completely different levels.

There was a humming noise before the Spider Mech’s movements were obstructed at once, making it unable to move at all.

“Go!” the black figure jumped up in mid-air and spoke a few more sentences into his headset rapidly.

Numerous lasers formed red lines that extended past his body, barely missing him. They hit the walls of the skyscraper and left burn marks there instead.

Tch! Tch tch tch!!

The number of red lasers increased instantly when a group of white Spider Mechs appeared near the far end of the wall. All of them had eyes that were flickering with red light as the lasers shot from their direction.

The black figures flipped and flew outside while dodging and jumping between the lofty buildings constantly as if they were apes in a dense jungle. While the ten red lights continued to intersect with one another, the figures disappeared within the darkness between the buildings quickly.

Simultaneously, Spider Mechs that were chasing the black figures filled the entire Blackboard City at once. Those black figures escaped into the shadows quickly and disappeared without a trace.

****************************

Garen woke up from his dream suddenly.

There was a stretch of darkness before his eyes but it seemed as though something was moving slowly outside the window of his ward.

He twisted his head over determinedly before a pair of eyes appeared beside his pillow suddenly and glared at him intently.

“You could actually detect me?” the owner of the eyes spoke in a low voice.

Only then did Garen realize that the other person was merely pressed up closely against the window of the ward and had not actually entered. The pair of red eyes were huge and bright, making its female owner seem unusually close.

“Interesting…” the owner of the eyes was fully dressed in black clothes. She seemed to be moving slowly and passing through the ward. She had evaded so many people and even alarm devices but had never expected to be discovered by a regular patient here.

She hesitated for a moment. The whirring noise of an oncoming police car could be heard faintly from downstairs. The sound of the jets and engines of the Mechs could be heard as well, meaning that a large group was chasing them.

The window was pushed opened gently before the black figure slithered inside through the opening. She was initially just passing by this area and had not expected that a patient would notice her.

She dropped on the ground quietly and moved her arm backward to close the window. The black figure was now standing in front of Garen’s sickbed.

“This means something. You could actually detect my movements…” she glanced at the sign at the front of his bed. “Your nerves sustained serious damages, huh?”

“Who is this person?” Garen lay on his bed without a trace of panic and merely stared at the other person silently.

This person was dressed in tight black clothes that resembled fish skin. He could vaguely see that she was a girl as she had a curvy figure. Her waist was slim and her legs were slender but he could not see her hair as it was wrapped with something. Her face was also completely covered with a black veil.

“What are you looking at?!”

Bang!!

Garen felt a painful sensation in his head suddenly. The girl had lifted him in one go before she’d flung him on the ground violently, his head crashing against the hard floor with a dull thud.

This woman’s behavior had changed drastically and she was now stepping on Garen’s body with one foot furiously.

“Perverted little devil! Looks like I’ll have to dig out both of your eyeballs!”

Two black needles shot out of the fingertips of her right hand before stabbing downwards directly when they were accurately positioned at Garen’s eyes.

“This woman!!” Garen’s head was burning with fury. How dare she dig his eyeballs out for no reason?! He spat suddenly.

There was a hissing noise when a mouthful of his spit shot out like an almost silent arrow that flew towards the woman’s right eye directly.

“Do you want to die?!” the woman was able to dodge his saliva but her gaze had turned fearsome.

However, her black needles had tilted slightly when she tried to evade Garen’s spit. They scratched his face and formed two deep bloody wounds there.

There were not normal needles as their edges were actually as sharp as blades instead!

She stomped one foot against Garen’s waist furiously before the woman leaped upwards and took a few steps backward suddenly.

She turned her head and glanced at the ceiling and noticed that the saliva had formed a tiny depression there. Although the ceiling was wooden, it was clear that the strength that was used to shoot the saliva would have caused terrible injuries if it had hit her eyeball instead.

“I never expected that I would encounter strange things just by entering a sick ward,” the woman circled Garen carefully and investigated him for a moment. She only approached him again when she was certain that he did not have any more tricks up his sleeves.

She elbowed Garen’s lower abdomen violently. The hit caused his body to curl up suddenly while his face turned pale.

Next, she used her foot to step on Garen’s neck, making it almost impossible for him to breathe.

“Move again!” the woman spat angrily. “Move!”

There was a banging noise when she kicked Garen’s chest brutally. A cracking sound could be heard after that when his breastbone broke.

Garen became even more furious. If it was not for his inability to move, he would have destroyed this woman with one slap at once.

Bang!

There was another dull thud when she used her foot to step on Garen’s abdomen violently.

The sound of the alarm below them rang louder and it was obvious that the search team was approaching.

Tch!

A red laser shot in from the window suddenly, leaving a black burn mark precisely on the woman’s shoulder.

“Damn!” The woman groaned in pain. The black needles on her fingers were pointed downwards and about to stab Garen’s eyes violently. However, she had accidentally made eye contact with him.

His eyes resembled whirlpools and were as dark and blue as the sea. They possessed a faint but strange form of attraction.

“I will find you.”

The woman could read the meaning behind his eyes and felt a frightened tremble in her mind suddenly.

Tch tch tch!!

Three red lasers intertwined to form a net that was flying towards her suddenly.

Without much time to react, she could only leap upwards suddenly and bounce off the wall like a lizard before crashing out of the window.

The crashing noise of broken glass could be heard before the black figure disappeared into thin air.

The noises from the chase drifted further away quickly.

Garen lay on the floor. His body was covered in blue and black bruises while his eyes were filled with obvious exhaustion.

Cough cough cough…

He started to cough.

“If one of my Soul Seeds were destroyed because of you, you’re as good as dead!!” Garen glared in the direction where the woman had left.

If he had not used the Fantasy Fist to distract the woman with his gaze at the final key moment, the alternate ending would have been extremely dangerous.

“I’ve already sustained such serious injuries despite having just arrived in this world. What a good beginning.” Garen’s gaze became even more profound.

He had engraved that woman’s eyes into his memory. Someone who dared to almost destroy one of his Soul Seeds would surely be repaid at the right time.

Outside the sick ward, the sound of footsteps could finally be heard. The door of the ward was opened before the security guards rushed in with the nurses.

“A patient has been injured! Prepare a full body checkup immediately!”

The doctor in the hospital room yelled loudly.

********************

In the darkness of the night

On the outskirts of Blackboard City

Multiple black figures leaped and passed through the dark quickly. Their bodies would distort and become invisible occasionally. It seemed as though they were disappearing in mid-air before reappearing again after a while.

There were at least ten black figures. Soon, all of them had gathered inside an abandoned factory on the outskirts of Blackboard City.

The interior of the factory was completely silent except for the cricket chirps that could be heard occasionally.

About ten black figures had gathered here and had now formed a circle.

“Is everyone alright?” asked one of the black figures softly.

“This test was too simple. I could get the information easily. It was completely pointless,” said a female black figure flippantly.

“Goldfish got injured though. Did everyone else see? Goldfish actually got hurt during a battle chase of this degree.” a different woman could not help but laugh loudly as if she had seen something extremely funny.

The woman called ‘Goldfish’ stood among her team but remained silent. However, her red eyes grew colder.

“I encountered an unusual accident…”

“If you’re inadequate just say so. An accident? Find a better excuse,” sneered the woman who was laughing loudly earlier.

“Fifteen points will be deducted from Goldfish’s task. Any other problems?” asked the leading black figure unquestionably.

“No…” Goldfish ground her teeth faintly.

“Hey~~ Are you unhappy?” asked someone cynically.

“If your genes were discovered by a human team because of the blood that you left behind during a real mission, we would be forced to abandon you when the time comes,” said the leading black figure indifferently. “You must understand. Punishment of this degree is only done so that you will be able to gain a deeper understanding of your future.”

“I understand.” Goldfish lowered her head and tightened her fist furiously.

“Alright, this operation is dismissed. I will solve this incident with Goldfish separately through the higher-ups. Give me all of the mission items.”

All of the black figures passed the items in their hands over to him.

*****************

The surgery began earlier than planned.

Garen lay face up on the operating table. The effects of the drugs from the anesthetic injection were appearing quickly.

His mind began to turn fatigued gradually. He looked at the blindingly bright operating light above him before drifting into deep slumber.

Yesterday’s accident resulted in even more troublesome injuries throughout his body that could only be resolved with this operation.

An unknown amount of time passed. It could have been an hour or even two.

Garen awakened slowly and felt numerous tearing pains throughout his entire body. The most obvious pains came from his chest and abdomen while other discomforts could be felt throughout his whole body.

“This is a side effect from the extremely tiny robots that was placed inside your body during the surgery. The presence of pain means that your nerve restoration was successful so you’ll have to endure it.”

A low male voice echoed from his bedside.

“I understand.”

Garen nodded slightly before reacting immediately. He could nod and even speak again!

“Looks like the effects have been extremely good. You just need to let your nerves heal their wounds. You’ll need to recuperate for a period of time,” the one who was speaking was a male doctor. He asked Garen about his various sensations for a while before carefully informing him about the things that he needed to pay attention to. Beside him, his parents and younger siblings noted everything down carefully and thanked the doctor continuously.

Aier and Mina were also by his bedside. It seemed as if they had been waiting outside the operating theatre as well.

“You have such good luck. To think that you would be able to survive safely after encountering death,” Mina shook her head in astonishment.

“What ‘good luck’? This just means that I have great skills,” Garen was in a good mood and could even joke with Mina now.

“I need to tell you something later,” Mina nodded.

Chapter 777: Trouble 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

They waited until the doctor and the others had left and Garen’s parents had gone to work before Mina and the rest said a few words quietly and sat beside Garen’s bed again.

“What did you want to tell me?” Garen was still unable to move his body. However, the nerves in his head were not injured so severely as they were located in the area that was protected by the Soul Seeds. Aier, who was beside him, helped to lift his head and lean it against the pillow.

Mina paused for a moment.

“Although the instructor forbade me from saying it, this is something that you’d need to know sooner or later. It’s about the problems with your recent operation fees.”

“Oh?” Garen furrowed his brow.

“The cost of the operation wasn’t reimbursed by the academy?” his younger sister Ker asked in a puzzled manner. This was a question that the others wanted to ask as well.

Mina shook her head slightly.

“It wasn’t,” she glanced at Garen and his younger brother and sister around him. “It’s not what you’re thinking. Nono, your medical bills were actually paid in advance by Instructor Hamm. The academy was completely against the application for your expenses and did not provide any funds.”

“Instructor Hamm?” Garen was slightly shocked.

None of them spoke for a while. His younger brother and sister did not know what to say. Meanwhile, Garen had never been one to reveal his emotions. He merely leaned against the sick bed as if he was pondering something.

Mina did not care about what Garen was thinking about and chose to finish talking about the things she knew first.

“Aier and I asked about these things in the academy for you. Initially, you could have sent in a request for your operation fees to be reimbursed. However, the family of Oscar, the student you injured, has connections. In order to punish you for injuring Oscar badly during the test, although they could not take revenge on you directly because of the school rules, they were able to pull some strings to ruin your medical fee application easily.”

Her expression was somewhat grave when she told them everything that she knew.

“The operation cost 1.5 million dollars. The cost of nerve restoration operations are certainly not cheap,” said Aier beside her. “Even for Instructor Hamm who’s earning a good salary…”

Garen glanced at Aier and Mina beside him. Both of them really had good relationships with Nono and were clearly his trustworthy friends. Most people would not put in so much thought for the sake of others.

The people whom Nonosiva came into contact the most in the academy were Mina and Aier. Although Instructor Hamm liked him a lot as well, his affections were distributed equally among the top three students in the class, not just Nonosiva. Frankly, he had never expected the bearded man to do something like pay for his operation fees with his own money.

The nerve restoration surgery had really helped him. The effects were even better than anticipated. Coupled with his self-healing abilities, he would only need to lay in bed for a month before he would recover completely.

“Thanks for reminding me. I will remember Instructor Hamm’s favor,” answered Garen sincerely while nodding.

“Our instructor didn’t do this just so you could return the favor, he was only hoping that you would not lose your future just because of this accident,” answered Mina honestly. “It wasn’t just you anyway. Instructor Hamm has helped many other students this way. He’s a good person.”

“Is he? Good person…” Garen allowed his eyelids to droop while repeating the phrase once more.

The personalities of Garen and the previous Nonosiva were naturally different. Although Nonosiva was originally quiet and preferred to listen when he was with his friends, Mina and Aier merely assumed that he had changed after this incident. They found it somewhat strange but did not think that it was a major suspicion.

“That’s right, your body will probably take a month to recover. Once that’s over, come to class as soon as possible to catch up. Otherwise, we won’t wait for you,” Mina stood up and smiled. “It’s time to go back to class. We’re off. You should rest properly.”

Aier followed suit and stood up as well.

“Go on. Don’t worry, I’ll be able to catch up to you in no time,” Garen smiled.

“Goodbye Big Sister Mina and Big Brother Aier,” his younger brother Baylon and younger sister Ker stood up and sent them off as well.

******************

A month of recuperation passed by quickly.

Garen spent his days laying on the sickbed. At first, he was unable to move at all but could gradually move his hands slowly during the later stages. After that, he could get down from the bed and walk when his recovery speed increased.

He was usually supported by his family members, especially his younger brother Baylon. Occasionally, his parents would come over and help as well.

Garen did not share many sentiments with Nonosiva’s parents. But in this world, Nono’s parents were merely sincere people who had made quiet sacrifices without complaining. This gave him a slightly favorable impression of them.

After all, the money that was used to pay for his daily hospital stays were paid for by Nono’s parents who worked from dawn to dusk. Therefore, he owed them some gratitude at least. Since he had occupied Nono’s body, he would naturally be responsible to perform the necessary duties of a son to Nono’s parents.

His recovery went smoothly. However, the places where that woman had brutally fractured his bones were still aching slightly. Although the restoration surgery had solved the problem of his fractured bones while his Soul Seed’s stimulated restoration had been fully healed as well, the memory of the young woman with red eyes continued to appear in Garen’s mind.

That person had nearly caused him to lose one of his Soul Seeds.

Moreover, the most pressing issue was his Willpower.

After Garen had occupied Nono’s body, once the body had healed completely, he began to fully test out and understand the inner workings of the body structure at the first opportunity.

He did this in order to comprehend the true meaning of Willpower.

Meanwhile, the conclusion that he obtained shocked him greatly.

This thing called ‘Willpower’ was actually a force field that was condensed and formed by the entire body of the people here.

If the brains of humans could produce empty powers such as one’s consciousness, then one’s Willpower basically referred to treating one’s entire body as a brain and producing a special force field using it.

Moreover, only people from this world possessed physiological structures that could produce Willpower.

Once Garen had painstakingly investigated the source of Willpower, time was almost up and it was already time for him to leave the hospital.

After a series of procedures were conducted, Instructor Hamm, Nono’s parents, family members, Mina, and Aier had arrived. Once everything was settled, Garen returned to Blackboard Academy and assumed Nonosiva’s identity.

***************

Blackboard Academy

Physical examination and testing room

Beep beep…

When the red indicator light flashed, Garen straightened his body while sitting in front of the large silver crab-like scanner so that the pincer-like scanners of the ‘giant crab’ could move around his body continuously.

“All of your health data is normal. Student Nonosiva, you should lose some weight,” announced the giant crab loudly without holding anything back.

“I’ve gotten chubbier after living on campus recently,”

Garen got down from the machine and walked in front before speaking to Aier who was waiting on the side.

“Where’s Mina? Why haven’t I seen her during my recovery training sessions during these past few days?”

“The Jujitsu Association that she’s part of has been selected by someone. As the Vice President, she was forced to return to deal with the situation,” Aier smiled and shrugged.

“Oh? Why were they chosen?” Garen and the other two people had become even more familiar. Although he was a slightly cowardly person, Aier was still a young man who would truly dare to step forward for the sake of his friends. His continuous contributions during Garen’s hospitalization period had allowed him to gain Garen’s approval as well.

“Recently, there’s a new student who’s already extremely arrogant despite just joining the academy. He’s been sweeping through the martial arts associations throughout the school for the sake of making things lively.” Aier was unconcerned about matters like these. “We’re just peace-loving enthusiasts so why would we care about things like that?”

“You’re right,” Garen nodded in agreement. “We’re peace-loving enthusiasts. Things like hurting and killing just don’t suit us.”

“It reminded me immediately of the collective tests of our C series classes. The instructor’s fury was released on the top three students including yourself. Have you recovered?” Aier patted Garen’s shoulder.

“I’m still alright.” Garen did not what to say and could only answer honestly.

“Instructor Hamm placed all of his expectations on the three of you,” Aier lowered his voice. “You should go and test your Willpower since your body has healed.”

“You’re right.”

Garen did not have most of Nono’s memories. Although he could remain quiet and use the excuse of losing his memories from the severe injuries to gloss things over, he had yet to obtain enough information about the problems regarding his Willpower. All of the memory fragments regarding Willpower had disappeared and Garen had yet to come into contact with teaching materials that dealt with the Willpower aspects. He could only take one step at a time.

Once they had heard that Nono’s body had healed completely and could already reach the standards to test his Willpower, Instructor Hamm and Mina, who was still at the Jujitsu Association, rushed over at once.

**************

Inside the testing room

Tiny red and blue indicator lights flickered on the various testing equipment. A female school doctor in white clothes carefully placed a series of testing leather goods such as leather gloves, leather apron, and a leather helmet on Garen. He was made to wear all of the test attire.

Garen stood on the testing platform. It was a circular silvery-white platform that resembled a large coin that was placed on the ground.

Instructor Hamm stood and Aier stood on the sidelines and had arrived specifically to observe Garen’s test.

“Good luck!” Aier raised his thumb towards Garen.

Garen smiled and stood on the platform steadily.

“The test is starting…” an old-fashioned mechanical voice echoed throughout the testing room.

A ray of blue light rose upwards from below Garen’s feet before slowing down gradually and moving above his head.

Even Garen felt curious now. After he had occupied Nonosiva’s body, he wondered about the changes that he would undergo. Apparently, his Willpower would form a force field that was produced by his body. Since he had replaced Nonosiva, he pondered about the changes that would happen. He could not even guess the possibilities.

To Garen, Willpower was an incomprehensible existence that could not be physically touched. Furthermore, this was completely foreign territory and power.

He could feel a hot sensation when the lines of blue light rose from the bottom of his feet.

The time it took to scan him was not fast but considerably slow instead. Garen closed his eyes after looking at his current condition and state in the large mirror on the opposite side of him.

His long black hair covered half of his face and he had pale skin that seemed as if it had never felt sunshine. His body was slightly plump and he wore the standard school uniform of a white shirt with blue stripes. He gave off a somewhat dejected air. However, faint glimpses of coolness and confidence could be seen in his blue eyes, allowing the reflection in the mirror to give off a calmer personality.

“This test should be able to assess the true condition of this body,” he already assumed that he was unlikely to possess Willpower. After all, this thing was related to his soul, but his soul had never undergone Willpower training. Therefore, it was impossible that he would have it. However, once his body had undergone certain modifications and the unconscious influence of the Soul Seeds, it was still possible that changes would occur later. Nonetheless, it would not necessarily be a high probability.

“I’m afraid of disappointing Instructor Hamm this time,” he knew that the instructor had high expectations towards Nonosiva.

When the blue line passed over his legs and moved closer to his abdomen and rose above his chest, Garen could see Aier baring his teeth and making funny faces at him from the side. Instructor Hamm had understood something from the female school doctor’s speech as a smile had appeared on his face.

Was there really going to be a surprise?

He had some doubts as this body had never undergone Secret Technique training. Although he was barely able to use certain techniques to release his destructive powers, this was still a regular human body at the end that could not even hear quiet words that were spoken from afar.

Chapter 778: Trouble 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Student Nono’s body has recovered perfectly. It’s almost the same as any other student that had not undergone surgery, his parameters are as normal as can be,” the female school doctor was also surprised.

“The scanning has reached the head. For the body, it has recovered to a certain extent and he should be able to take the test. Luckily it was just in time, or else C5’s class ranking would drop a lot,” Hamm smiled and nodded.

Then, the blue line finished scanning Garen’s head and finally stopped.

The results were automatically printed on a white sheet of paper beside the doctor’s computer.

After the ‘du du’ sounds of printing stopped, the female school doctor picked up the results with a smile and examined it.

“What’s going on?” the smile on her face stiffened.

Seeing the look on the school doctor’s face, both Instructor Hamm and Aier felt that something was wrong.

“What’s the matter? Dr. Lassa,” Instructor Hamm moved closer, hoping to catch a glimpse of the results.

“It’s written here, the Willpower…between Basic Level and Level 1?” the school doctor frowned. “It’s rare to see something like this…”

“Nono’s strength had passed multiple Level 1 assessments. It should be at Level 1. There is no doubt about it,” Aier frowned.

“Maybe it’s due to the fact that he was just discharged and his state is not fully stabilized. It should be normal. Maybe it’ll completely stabilize in a few days,” Instructor Hamm thought for a while and made a suggestion.

“That is quite possible,” the female school doctor nodded. “Then the conclusion is that Student Nono is completely restored,” she showed a smile.

Aier quickly gave Garen, who was still standing on top, an OK gesture.

Garen smiled and stepped down. Suddenly, he frowned and inserted his hand into his pocket. There was a slightly hot thing inside; it was the small Moonfang.

This fang was very important according to Nono’s memories. He had thus brought it here even for his medical check-up. To think that it would give off heat during the check-up…

“That’s it, go back and take a good rest. Tomorrow is the test for the Mech Simulation. Let’s see how much you’ve regressed. Aier is willing to accompany you,” Hamm laughed and patted Garen’s shoulder. “As for me, I won’t be coming, do your best! Don’t disappoint the academy that has helped you so much.” He did not know that the fact that he’d disguised himself as the academy’s fund and paid for Garen’s medical expenses had already been exposed to the students in front of him.

“I know.” Garen nodded.

“Alright, this is it for today. Go back and take a good rest.”

Those were the instructor’s last words.

*******************

Holding on to his medical report, Garen and Aier left the school infirmary and slowly walked along the huge plate-like building in the middle of the Blackboard Academy.

The afternoon weather was a little dim and gloomy as the sun had been blocked by thick clouds. The wind stirred up the dust and leaves on the ground.

Three blue, red and white planets were suspended in the sky, and they occupied a space of more than half of the entire sky. They peeked through the gap between the clouds.

Garen looked up at the three huge planets, especially at the red satellite planet which was as bright as the color of blood. He understood now that he was no longer in the previous world.

The number of people strolling around the academy was not low. Many were wearing communication devices that resembled earphones, either listening to music or playing on their personal computers. There were also those who were chatting, reading books or talking to others through their phones.

The number of students in Blackboard Academy was not low. There were students bustling everywhere, either passing by or stopping.

Garen was observing the environment of the academy while trying to get information about the feeling of Willpower from Aier.

And it was through this way that he found out about a troublesome matter.

“…recently, I’ve felt that the improvement of Willpower has become slower. In the beginning, it was at least the size of a hair but now it’s become a little tiny bit. I’ve been training for at least five hours every single day! It’s been more than a year and I’m still stuck in the Advanced Basic Level. I can’t break through the last level no matter what I do,” Aier grumbled, with his hands tucked behind his head. “Unlike you, a genius who had a Level 1 Willpower upon entering the academy. In such a short time, you’ve already passed so many Level 1 subjects. I wished I have your talent.”

“I don’t feel it anyway,” Garen tried to use vague words to answer.

“What do you mean ‘don’t feel it’, I want to grind my teeth and punch you!” Aier made a vicious expression. “Mediocre students like us don’t even know what to do!”

“Tell me the process and feeling when you train your Willpower, and let me see if I can give you some advice,” Garen smiled and answered.

“Fine, with the help of a Level 1 master here, the hopes of me being promoted rest on your shoulders!” Aier suddenly laughed. He started to explain from the beginning the ways he’d trained his Willpower. Including his selection of textbooks, the way he trained, the difficulties he encountered during the process, the direction of his breakthrough and so on, he explained everything to Garen.

From Aier’s perspective, Nono, who had broken through to Level 1, was an expert that was much stronger than him. In the academy, even Instructor Hamm, who was an expert that had once joined the elite troops, had only a Level 4 Willpower. The top students in the entire academy were only around Level 3. Among the Blackboard Academy’s lower graders, someone who could reach Level 1 Willpower in just a year after entering the academy would be the real cream of the crop. The average students were all struggling in the Basic Level like him. The better ones might be approaching this threshold. Only when their Willpower managed to reach Level 1 could they qualify to pilot Mechs. This was the starting point where the pilot could be ensured as compatible for piloting.

Garen listened carefully to Aier’s story and soon he had grasped the concepts of this Willpower.

The training for Willpower did not have a shortcut. It was something that needed painstaking efforts to accumulate bit by bit.

In the beginning, they had to choose a training method as a starter.

For the general training methods, if several students’ talents were about the same, then their improvement rates would be about the same, except for the effects they would achieve in the end. Those who leaned towards awareness would choose the ranged type of Mech for training, while those with fast reaction speed would choose to upgrade their Mech’s reaction speed, and the defensive type would increase the Willpower field of their armored Mech. This field would become a protective barrier that could protect the Mech when it reached a high enough level.

Those who favored attacks would choose the type of method that would increase their firepower or attack range. All these different training methods had different tendencies which would go in different directions.

Aier had chosen the most popular awareness type, which involved attacking from far away and was also the safest way to battle. He used a common training method on the market called <<Outbreak of Rain>>. When it reached the highest level, it could fire off all the firepower loaded in a short span of time and form a rain-like attack. Of course, that was only when it reached the highest level. Aier’s family had spent all they had to buy this training method, but there were only two levels which meant he could only reach Level 2. Aier planned to earn some money when he reached Level 2, which could be considered elite in the outside world. Trying to earn money then to buy the next level of training methods could be considered quite easy.

This was what most students would do. Aside for those students whose families were rich and powerful and could choose better training methods, eighty percent of Blackboard students could only do things this way.

Including the previous Nonosiva.

And what troubled Garen currently was that his situation was totally different from what Aier had said.

This body Nonosiva did not have any talents previously. He had also chosen the range type training method. According to the intensity level and awareness levels that Aier mentioned, Garen felt that Nono’s level of Willpower was only Middle Basic Level, which could not even be compared to Aier!

The previous Nono had relied on the white Moonfang to stand above the rest. The Moonfang had the functions of disguising the level of Willpower and helping to control the Mech.

Even his chosen training method was worse than Aier’s; it was the free training method that Blackboard Academy gave out: <<Blackboard Control>>. This was the lowest level training method that was given out for free on the market. The ultimate effect was to strengthen the Willpower without any additional effects.

In this one month’s time, Garen had roughly understood the situation revolving this society of Blackboard. A Mech Pilot was equivalent to those who practiced secret techniques in the Secret Technique World. Yet, they did not hide. They were in control of politics and they were the most powerful army. It could be said that the elites who graduated from Blackboard Academy would hold important positions in society for sure.

As compared to other industries, they were the guardians of the region. Under this kind of situation, those who aimed to become Mech Pilots were too numerous. This had led the society to lean towards prioritizing the industry of Mechs.

Once a Blackboard Academy’s student walked out, as long as they had reached the criteria for graduation, at worst they could be patrol officers. This was a standard position which held certain influences. Hence, the threshold for Blackboard Academy was pushed by the masses to become higher and higher.

“What an abnormal society…..” Garen had a mixture of feelings after understanding the situation.

No wonder Nonosiva had tried everything he could to squeeze into the Blackboard Academy and had even resorted to cheating.

He touched the Moonfang in his pocket. According to the things Aier said, he was vaguely aware that although this body had merged a part of his Willpower after recovery, he was still facing the same dilemma as the original Nonosiva; that was the fact that he only had Middle Basic Level Willpower. With this bit of Willpower, never mind controlling the Mech to fight with others, even controlling the Mech to slowly walk would be a huge burden.

As the two chatted, they arrived at the entrance of the student dormitory. The rooms here were designed for a single person and their conditions were very good. Aier patted his shoulders.

“See you tomorrow during the test, I’ll go back and take a rest first.”

“En, go on,” Garen nodded and smiled, watching Aier walking away.

Watching Aier’s figure walk away, he was soon blocked by the students going in and out of the dormitory. Garen began to worry about tomorrow’s test.

“I must try the training method for Willpower soon,” he muttered to himself.

Chapter 779: Analysis 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In one of the rooms in the school dormitory

A black-haired boy wearing the white-blue school uniform was sitting in front of his bed and facing his table. He was flipping through the pages of a book with the title <<Blackboard Training Method>> on its cover.

Garen had been reading this book for over half an hour.

Putting down the book, he rubbed at his tired eyes.

“This body is too weak… It can’t even do a little bit of reading, I must exercise as soon as possible,” he gently placed the book upside down on the table, leaned back and relaxed his waist.

“The book has roughly explained the situation about the latest training methods and introduced all the Blackboard training methods. It’s considered quite good overall,” Garen clapped this book that had been collected by the original Nonosiva.

“But the problem is a little tricky….” Garen gently stroked the cover of the book and fell into deep thought.

‘If the contents of the book conform to reality, then the only way I can access this world’s mainstream system is through the academy,’ Garen recalled the contents of the book.

‘The Federal laws, the Local laws, and even all the other laws and regulations which specify that the training methods for Willpower which are eligible to be classified at the Levels of at least Level One and above, cannot be circulated. Only some people with certain identities are qualified to train and view them but they still cannot be circulated. Only the academy’s students are eligible to trade and exchange the training methods, including purchasing and giving them away. Once a member of the general public is found practicing these training methods, they would be treated as felons directly and most of them would face the death penalty. This penalty is even stricter than the gun control in China on Earth.’

Garen rubbed the cover of the book, feeling the delicate cool surface.

‘The formal training methods classified by Levels can only be purchased by students that are qualified, otherwise, it is illegal and they will be apprehended by the government. The legal ways to practice the training methods are through the Blackboard Academy and twelve other academies. Other than them, no one is allowed to practice or trade the training methods. Without the academies’ permission to learn the training methods for Level 3 and above, the foundation for Willpower will be directly destroyed once discovered. Vicious!’

Garen was not someone who did not understand anything, he somewhat understood how this society worked.

Once the Willpower was totally destroyed, the victim would completely enter a vegetative state. This was a life worse than death as even their self-awareness would be totally lost.

“From how it looks, my identity as the best student of the Blackboard Academy is quite an advantage, although I still owe Instructor Hamm a large sum of money.”

Garen turned his head sideways and looked out the window. Through the window, he could see a large tree outside the dormitory. The tree was very tall and thick, and its leaves covered most of the gray sky, leaving only tiny gaps and dimming his room.

“This identity as a student must not be lost,” he decided on the direction he would take. “Otherwise, purchasing the training methods would become illegal.”

If a free legal identity that provided such an advantage was not well used, it would be totally outrageous. Besides, with the constant merging of his soul with this body, he had thoroughly integrated into this body with no side effects.

It was just that the original Nonosiva’s Willpower was only at Middle Basic Level, and no matter how powerful Garen was, it was impossible to turn it into Advanced Basic Level, not to mention Level 1. He himself was a cheater who relied on the Moonfang.

This was a tricky problem.

Garen recalled the training methods that Nonosiva had studied in the past.

“<<Universal Basic Willpower Training Method>>,” Garen pulled out a tattered booklet with a yellow cover from the bookshelf at the side.

“This is the basic training method Nono had used previously. Generally, all the students have used this basic training method booklet. The highest it can reach is Level One and only then can they start to choose training methods that are classified by Levels. Almost reaching Level 1 is the highest that normal people are able to achieve legally.”

The relevant memories flashed through Garen’s mind.

He moved a white tablet from the edge of the gray table’s surface and pressed down on its power button. A rotating Rubik’s Cube appeared on the screen and soon disappeared. A white window background replaced the cube, with all sorts of colorful icons on it just like an ordinary computer desktop.

“Welcome to the Blackboard client terminal,” a sweet female voice sounded from the computer. This notebook-sized tablet actually had a sound system that rivaled a home theater.

“Student c534 auto login complete, please select the entry option,” the female voice continued.

Garen quickly tapped on the icon of the training methods market.

Soon the screen displayed rows upon rows of small icons. Each small icon was a different training method, making people dizzy with the sheer amount.

He scanned from the top downwards and from left to right.

‘Six Flower Training Method’ ‘Master Carseland’s Personal Training Method’ ‘Aquamarine Training Method’ ‘Maxwell Collar Method’ ‘Laser Charging Method’ ‘Willpower Stream Training’….

All sorts of strange names appeared and every single icon there was beautiful, making people feel that there were no regular things on this market.

However, when Garen glanced at the left sidebar, it was indicated that this page contained only Level 3 training methods.

“Level 3 training method means that the highest attainable Level is 3 and these training methods have to be purchased layer by layer,” Taking a look at the prices, Garen was slightly speechless.

An ordinary Aquamarine training method was priced at a hundred and fifty thousand Universal Points. According to his observation in this one month, it was equivalent to three hundred thousand RMB on Earth and this was only the price for one layer; the price for Level 1. After opening it, there was a follow-up instruction that in order to get the Level 2 training method, he had to pay two hundred thousand Universal Points and two hundred and fifty thousand for Level 3.

“This market seemed to be linked to the entire federal market,” Garen pressed on other training methods. It seemed that the price for Aquamarine Training Methods was considered reasonable and low.

All of these were training methods that could reach Level 3 at most and each of them had their own strengths and advantages. There were also detailed descriptions of what might happen during different periods for people with different constitutions. They truly had excellent services.

Garen took a look at the transaction records below. Every user who bought Level 3 training methods would have their username displayed below. The username was not fully displayed though; only the last name was displayed.

Garen slowly looked through the Level 3 training methods market.

After the direction of the training methods was set, it would be difficult to change it, because the Willpower that developed according to the training methods had taken shape according to its development. Even if the person succeeded in changing their direction, it would be hard to reach a very high level.

And now that he had gotten Nonosiva’s body, on the surface he had chosen a Level 1 training method as his direction, but the truth was that it had not taken shape yet.

Because Nonosiva could not afford to buy any training methods that were classified by Levels.

Garen randomly browsed through the market’s catalog. After a dozen pages, they were all basically the same, just with slight differences.Never mind the outrageous pricing, some training methods even demanded that the identity of the buyer needed to have certain criteria. They were basically picky. Some were layered thickly with a merchant’s vibe; as long as it was convenient for the buyer, anything went.

After he had roughly looked through, he turned to the Level 4 training methods.

In the market menu that was opened, there were only a few icons to pick from.

‘Hurricane Roar’ ‘Cassis Hammer’ ‘Precise Aiming Device’

There were even a bunch of restrictions on the buyer. They had to be registered in the Federal Academies Union. According to the instructions above, the market for Level 3 training methods was relatively loose. The training methods on the market were also generally Level 3 at the highest. However, those who were able to reach Level 3, they were already considered the top elites even in the Blackboard Academy. The teaching staff was also mostly at this level. This was the accumulation of training for many years until they were so old. Most of the people were unlikely to ever reach Level 3 in their lifetime.

When he came to his senses, Garen proceeded to the Level 5 menu.

There was nothing in it and there was nothing after that too.

Exiting the training methods market, Garen entered his personal center and gave a bitter smile at the remaining Universal Units in his account: 9854.

“No wonder Nono’s room did not have even a single Level-classified training method. It’s all so expensive. This bit of money can’t even pay for a single Level-classified training method…”

Nonosiva had been a child from an ordinary family who had entered the academy with excellent results from an ordinary high school. His Willpower reached Level 1 and he received the opportunity to study in Blackboard Region’s Blackboard Academy by squeezing out other competitors.

Ordinary civilian students like him were numerous in the academy. Their only chance at getting Level-classified training methods was by entering the academy and received the academy’s exclusive basic training method.

Blackboard Academy’s exclusive basic training method was <<Blackboard Manipulation>> which could allow the learners to enter Level 1 and aim for Level 2, and it was the students’ openhanded benefits. Though this was the most common Level-classified training method which did not have any advantages and special abilities, it was the only chance for the civilian students to change their fates.

“What a brutal blockade,” Garen sighed.

He stood up and began the everyday exercise that recovered his body.

He pulled the curtains shut, switched off the computer and began to slowly move the fingers on both his hands to tap certain points on his body.

Each time, the tap was done using the sharpest point on his fingertips. The moment he tapped, Garen’s expression was as though he had gone through a very laborious work. Soon, after more than ten minutes, every tap caused his forehead to slightly ooze with sweat.

After more than half an hour, he slowly stopped and breathed out on the spot.

“If it wasn’t for the fact that I can’t practice any secret techniques, it would be impossible for me to resort to practicing this outer technique filled with loopholes,” Garen helplessly sighed.

In this one month’s time, he had tried practicing all kinds of secret techniques, whether it was the White Cloud Secret Technique, Black Water True Technique, original Waterbird Fist or Slaughtering Hand. He tried a dozen advanced secret techniques and the end result was the same as what he’d expected; there was no way for secret techniques to grow here because the structure of this body was fundamentally different from the structure of the creator of secret techniques.

So, all the secret techniques were useless here. He tried the higher level Living Secret Technique from the previous world. Without the rare materials he needed, he just gave up and forgot about it. The previous world’s Peacock Technique was stuck at the beginner level from the start until the end, and up until the moment he left, he still could not break through.

Under such circumstances, Garen could only keep checking and reviewing his body during the hospitalization period and create a new secret technique with loopholes everywhere for himself.

He named this secret technique <<Imprint of Steel>>.

Chapter 780: Analysis 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen did not dare to casually practice the common outer techniques at all and he only used this method which gradually strengthened his body through external stimulation, due to the fact that he did not fully understand the structure of the meridians and the genes of this body.

This outer technique used a special method to stimulate the muscles and meridians. Although he could not determine the core structure of the body, Garen was still able to understand the locations and functions of the blood vessels and organs clearly within a month.

As he kept on moving in his room, slightly gray sweat gradually oozed out of the skin of his body.

Only after an hour did he rest and walk to the bathroom mirror.

Hua.

He turned on the tap and cool water gushed out of it.

Garen took out a basin and filled half of it with water. He put a towel in and soaked it before wringing it dry and covering his face.

He savored the icy feeling on his face. After the towel was warmed by his body temperature, he removed it.

Turning off the tap, Garen then used the towel to wipe off the sweat all over his body.

Putting down the towel, he inadvertently noticed the reflection of his own face in the water of the basin. The face was different. Only those eyes, those dark blue eyes, were familiar, which he had seen when he had traveled to the first world.

Taking a deep breath of cold air, Garen felt the cool breeze blowing in from the side window and went to close the curtain.

There was the scent of baked bread wafting through the air, as well as the odor of dust accumulating in the dormitory together with the smell of ink from his notebooks.

There was a student on the phone upstairs; the sound of a faint, gentle laughter traveled down. Other than that, it was all quiet. There was the faint sound of the wind rustling leaves and the sound of car engines passing by.

“It’s all real….” Only now did Garen fully realize that he’d really arrived at another world.

“This is really the real world, not inside a game…” he lightly scrubbed the towel and watched as the water in the basin turned murky.

“Since when had seeking strength and becoming stronger become my instinct….” he hung the now clean towel back on the shelf. “Even someone as strong as Black Sethe, who was at a Demon King Level, ultimately perished in the space and time of the universe.”

Feeling the two rotating Soul Seeds in his mind, Garen’s tired spirit suddenly became motivated.

“Even if I am far inferior to the Army Level, never mind the Demon King Level, there is no shortcut for me to take. The only way is forward. There is no need to think so much.”

Shaking his head, he pushed aside these thoughts and began to think about his current situation.

“Let’s try the training method first.”

He changed to a black sleeveless shirt and trousers and sat on his bed.

Opening the Blackboard Academy’s basic training method booklet which was printed with <<Blackboard Manipulation>>, the clear writing inside reflected in Garen’s eyes.

‘The root of Willpower comes from the body. If the consciousness is the product of the brain, then the Willpower is the product of the entire body. According to this theory, the body can be divided into countless regions of Willpower like the regions in the brain. We are going to focus on the most central regions— the three main regions which include heart, lungs and stomach, the three viscera.’

Scanning line after line of text, Garen analyzed the booklet’s contents.

Slowly, he began to have a certain understanding of this world’s Willpower. According to the theory of Willpower, neurons existed in every organ in the human body and these neurons acted the same as the neurons in the brain. Their variety of functions were similar and in order to activate these neurons, a special field called Willpower was needed.

“Simply put, treat the body neurons the same as the brain and eventually construct something similar to a second brain in other parts of the body to become the source for Willpower and generates the second consciousness. The second consciousness is the Willpower….” Garen realized. “This theory is easy to understand.”

He looked down and continued reading.

The previous pages explained the general outline of this world’s humans’ nature. Now, it was the training for stimulation of the organs. The Blackboard Manipulation chose the stomach as the site for training. This was also the choice for almost all of the training methods on the market.

‘The center of the stomach is the central part of the body. Naturally, the special field will converge here. This place is also the easiest place to gather Willpower… Inside the human body, excluding the nerves and blood vessels, there is another invisible network that transmits energy. The middle of the stomach, the place between the ribs, is also the center of this invisible energy network…’

Next was the training of the second consciousness, which was the key to Willpower.

‘The second consciousness, which is the essence of the human instinct, comes from the depths of the human body. Before humanity learned to use words to know this world, before words were invented, humanity had been using this kind of instinctive consciousness to understand the world.’

‘It has no words and no symbols. There are only images and only a rough understanding of the world. This is why the second consciousness is also called the cognition of the body. This kind of cognition is an innate ability. Due to the fact that we learn languages and symbols, we are forced to use the text and symbols as a connection to the world.’

‘So, the key to training the WIllpower is to forget all the symbols.’

Below was a list of different ways, steps, and precautions to take note during training. More importantly, the noteworthy areas were marked with red lines and notes were written on the side.

Garen read them carefully and a general idea of Willpower was formed in his mind.

“The so-called Willpower is the purest consciousness that is not affected by any language, words or symbols. It’s not the brain’s consciousness but the instinctive consciousness of other parts of the body. This system of this world is quite mysterious….” Garen flipped through the contents of the training method and compared it to the progress of his body.

He touched the pit of his stomach. There was a feeling of some kind of cool breath there. He did not notice it previously but focusing on that place now, he felt something different.

It was like there was a nose there slowly breathing and moving. If he focused on it, he could feel something strange, just like there was a pair of eyes there but it was closed.

“This is the second consciousness?” Garen quickly read through the Blackboard Manipulation booklet. “Discard the thinking pattern that uses words and symbols and activates the cognitive thinking pattern. Why is the animalistic instinct of crisis gone from humans? It is because the second consciousness has been degraded by the system that uses words. Makes sense…”

He put down the booklet. A list of various drugs and equipment that could stimulate the body into a pseudo state of activating the Willpower was written above. Only a few methods were available for a single person to utilize.

Garen sat down cross-legged on the bed. He could clearly feel that above the pit of his stomach, there were traces of hair-like fine air currents circling there.

This was the Willpower that Nono had trained.

According to what was recorded, it was still the Middle Basic Level.

A training method that did not use drugs and equipment was very simple. It was to concentrate on the pit of the stomach and imagine the mind hidden in the pit of the stomach and not anywhere else. Imagine the mind in the pit of the stomach without eyes, ears, and mouth, and there exists only the sense of touch.

The method was simple but it was difficult to do it.

Garen could not adapt to this method. After a few tries and around half an hour wasted without any results, he put it aside temporarily.

According to the booklet, the first time training the Willpower had to be done with the help of the drugs and equipment, otherwise, the feeling could not be grasped. It could also easily affect the digestive function of the body, resulting in physical exhaustion.

He took the Moonfang from the pocket of the clothes he had removed.

Garen carefully inspected it in his hand.

There was a large crack in the middle of the Moonfang. The white surface was also covered in many small cracks, like a glass that was about to break. The texture which was supposed to be as smooth as porcelain was now rough and sharp.

He recalled one of the two methods that Nono had used.

Garen furrowed his brows and willed a trace of the second consciousness in the pit of his stomach to come out and headed towards the Moonfang.

Hiss….

There was a faint sound and the Moonfang suddenly lit up and slightly burned Garen’s hand. He nearly threw it on the bed.

“It can still be used.” Garen was a bit happy. “As long as it can still be used, taking care to not overload it should enable me to continue the disguise.”

He did not want the fact that his Willpower was not sufficient to be exposed right now. He had been enrolled into the academy as a student that had reached Level 1 Willpower. If his Willpower suddenly had a drastic drop, with a detailed investigation, the truth that he cheated to get into the Blackboard Academy would be discovered.

According to the laws and regulations, a light punishment would be kicking him out of the academy and he would never be admitted a second time. Other federal academies would also be notified. A heavy punishment meant that in order to recover the contents of the training method, they would cripple his Willpower and maybe even kill him secretly. In times of chaos, human lives were not a big deal for those who held power, especially those of people who broke the rules.

“There were only Level 3 training methods on the market and Level 4 was almost exclusive to the people in powerful organizations. Looks like I have to join a group and get a better training method using the orthodox way,” Garen made a decision in his heart.

However, it was all just wishful thinking now, as his Willpower was not even Level 1.

He began to test the function of the Moonfang. Inserting the Willpower into the Moonfang could produce an effect similar to increasing his Willpower. Putting it in the Mech Controller and insert the Willpower could achieve an effect that allowed it to control the Mech automatically.

This Moonfang was basically a universal amplifier device.

After studying the Moonfang for a bit, Garen continued the training method to train his Willpower. Sadly, he seemed to have no talent for it, which was to say this body was not gifted, very mediocre. After working hard for a long time, there was only a tiny bit of feeling. No wonder Nonosiva only had this bit of improvement even after enrolling in the academy for more than a year.

“Looks like it is necessary to find an equipment to help training the Willpower. Also, it would be better to try using the Moonfang to test manipulation….” Garen decided.

Chapter 781: Simulation Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Standing up and looking out of the window, the sky had gotten dark. The white clock on the wall indicated that the time was 19.56.

There were the sounds of cars passing by outside the window while other dormitories had gone quiet.

Garen stuck his head outside and looked around. There were barely any sounds.

“This time is the time when most students train their Willpower. It’s very quiet. At this time, there should also be no one using the Single Control Room and the Enlightening Room. After all, the Enlightening Room’s equipment to enlighten Willpower is only effective for those who are exposed to the Willpower training for the first time.”

Garen made up his mind and put on a clean set of uniform, taking the key with him. Looking in the mirror which reflected his face half-covered by his black hair, he felt uncomfortable and took a rubber band to tie it into a small ponytail. He combed at the stray hairs with his hand and now he looked more refreshed.

White pale complexion, high bridge nose, pink lips and eyes that gave off a bleak and languid feeling. This was Garen’s disguise or putting it in other words, saving his energy.

“This body is still young… its malleability is quite good,” Garen pulled back his hair and threw the dirty clothes into the automatic washing machine before opening the door and walking out.

Outside the door, there were lots of students passing by. There were sounds of chatter and laughter and occasionally the electronic sounds of unknown devices.

After the door was closed, Garen walked along the corridor to the exit of the dormitory building. The sky had completely turned dark outside. Not far away, the streetlights formed a line into the distance. Some students were talking under the streetlights.

Recalling the location of the Enlightening Room, Garen walked along the alloyed path leading to the outside. Soon, the dormitory behind him became smaller and the lights became dimmer.

Walking along the road fence, after following the electronic road signs around several corners and intersections, Garen quickly found the dark testing room.

The Enlightening Room was an independent region. It was called a room but it was actually a large area consisting of several Blackboard buildings.

The region was surrounded by a fence and there was a black staircase going upward at the gate.

When Garen arrived here, a male student was sitting on the metal stairs with his sleeves and pant legs rolled up, his head tilted down without saying anything. Garen did not know what he was doing.

Casually glancing at him, Garen passed by his side and crossed over the region’s gate.

‘Scanning,’ a muffled electronic sound came from above the door frame.

Garen paused and waited until the scan was over before going in.

The Enlightening Room was covered in yellowish light. Some areas had lights and some had not, and these lights divided the whole place into a few areas.

“Luckily, it’s open all day,” Garen walked into the first Blackboard building door and walked along the cold dim passage.

He randomly chose an Enlightening Room and pushed the door. It was empty inside except for a circular equipment in the center which looked like a large black stone.

Garen walked to the edge, took out his student card and swipe the card in the slot.

Beep….

In the center of the entire Enlightening Room, a white shaft of light immediately beamed down on the black stone equipment.

Garen arrived and lay down on the surface of the equipment following his memory.

‘Enlightening start…’

‘Scanning the brainwave….’

‘Scanning the body index…’

‘All parameters passed, starting enlightening…’

After a while, in the midst of the light, a dazzling bright white light as thick as a pencil suddenly dropped down between Garen’s eyebrows like a laser.

‘Please train according to training method….’ the mechanical voice continued.

Garen closed his eyes and began to concentrate in the pit of his stomach, visualizing the mind in the pit of the stomach.

The Enlightening Room was different from the room at the dormitory. There seemed to be a kind of force helping Garen to easily gather his consciousness in the pit of his stomach.

Not even ten minutes passed, he had completely entered into the training method state and treat the stomach as a second brain.

This kind of training was like waking up from sleeping. Garen felt refreshed after the sleep.

Looking at his surroundings, there was no movement. There was no sound outside in the corridor either. It seemed as though he was the only one in this entire region.

Getting up from the black stone table with a bit of anticipation, he recalled the feeling of the process when he went into training.

Closing his eyes, he only thought a bit before instantly entering the state of the training method that he imagined.

“The effect is not bad. It was said that the Enlightening in the Enlightening Room was the human body’s greatest progress. Did I make any progress?”

Carefully identifying the Willpower in the pit of his stomach, disappointment flashed in Garen’s eyes.

“Nothing has changed… Looks like this body does not have any talent.”

Getting up from the equipment, he tidied up his uniform before opening the door and walking out. The lights in the room behind him were automatically switched off the moment the door closed.

His surroundings were quiet except for the sound of talking and reprimanding from afar.

Garen did not bother himself with it. From Nonosiva’s memories, he knew that only the freshman who would come to this area once a year. It was vacant most of the time and no one would be around. This large area was vacant and not in use and was thus the ideal area for violence and dating. The previous Nono occasionally came here and saw such occurrences several times and had gotten used to it.

Following the corridor to the outside, Garen passed by a glass corridor on his right side and saw that a little girl was surrounded by a group of girls outside on the small garden. They were pointing fingers but Garen was not sure what it was. The light was dim and the corner was in one of the darker areas, so Garen could not see anything clearly.

He was too lazy to pay any more attention to them and immediately left the corridor. Among the girls there, the one leading the group turned back and looked at him. Although the person was very pretty and her figure was not bad, her eyes were fierce.

Those girls did not pay any more attention to him and continued talking to the one that was surrounded by them. They seemed to be shouting.

Garen exited the corridor and quickly left the Enlightening area. After the first Enlightening, it would be easier for him to enter the training method state. In the future, he would just come over once in a while to renew that feeling. There was no need to come here frequently.

“But this place is very quiet, it’s a very suitable location for training alone,” there were some things that were not suitable to train in the dormitory, especially when some of the necessary steps of the process included things like hitting training. This was the outer techniques’ most basic part. The noise in the dormitory was too loud but this place, on the other hand, was quiet. The monitoring was also lax and most of them were useless, making this place a very suitable training environment.

Looking at his watch, the time had exceeded nine o’clock. This meant that he had stayed at the Enlightening Room for more than an hour.

“There’s still time to go to the Simulation Room.”

The Simulation Room was located at the edge of the Enlightening region. He just had to follow a small path and turn a corner and he would be at the Simulation Room.

When Garen arrived, there were people coming and going. The students that still trained hard at night were not few. Some were sweating and stank, some were looking very sad, and some were pale; it seemed their energy consumption had been too much.

There were people who often stayed up late to train, and people who sought peaceful challenges and sparring also came here.

This place was divided into the free area and toll area. Nono had never gone into the toll area so he did not know what was in there.

Following the path to the free area, there were more and more people. Most of the students were coming out, regardless of gender. A lot of girls were looking untidy. In just ten seconds, Garen had already seen four or five girls mixing with more than ten guys coming out. Similarly, they stank of sweat and they had no scruples about their images.

Thinking about it, it all made sense. Having spent so much energy training, would they have the time to dress up? If they did not dress up, of the ten points, they would still get five points.

Walking down the aisle, the right side of the free area had a silver metallic door. It was oval and the door kept opening and closing. The students who came out occasionally were all clean and tidy whether they were males or females, completely different from the students who came out of the free area.

That side was the toll area.

Garen passed by the entrance of the toll area and took a look inside. There were beautiful silver boxes in the form of life maintenance pods arranged in two rows inside.

Garen did not take another look and headed inside at a faster pace.

Inside the free area were also rows upon rows of simulation devices. The Cockpits that were hemispherical were arranged in rows like black eggshells. The ventilation system on top was constantly making hissing sounds, sucking all the strong smells of sweat out of here.

The time now was not considered late. There were still a lot of people around.

Garen found a vacant machine and sat in it. He took out his student card and swiped it once before he put on the helmet before him and lay down.

It felt like surfing the internet at an internet café.

The sight before him was dark.

Di….

Instantly, a white line lit up. Following it was a rotating colorful Rubik’s cube icon.

‘Welcome to the Simulation Battle Platform, the student number ID number has been inserted.’

‘Loading the record….’ the electronic voice continued.

‘Mister Goof, please select your model.’

Garen already felt exhausted. He never thought that the previous Nonosiva would get a nickname that could make people so speechless.

However, immediately, a blue platform with a flashing red light appeared. On top of it stood three humanoid Mechs. One was white in color and the other two were red. Their structures did not look complex and precise and they also did not have any aesthetic sense. Apparently, they were some of the most common goods.

He randomly selected a red humanoid Mech: Kegus General Mech 1.

‘Kegus 1, long-range Mech, Armor Level 1, Fatal Point 3, Basic laser gun range 50 meters, Lethality Level 1, Mech Speed Level 2.’

‘Overall evaluation: Level 1 Mech (Free Basic Mech)’

“All of them are about the same, one has a thicker armor at Level 2, another has higher lethality, but this one has a higher speed. This is it.”

Ever since Buddha Mother, this was the second time Garen was in control of a Mech. Everything was quite fresh to him now.

‘Entering holographic simulation state….’

With a hissing sound, Garen felt that his brain was abruptly disoriented and his whole body had entered another environment.

In front of him was a circular glass window where he could see that the outside was a night sky full of twinkling stars.

A clear screen floated in front of him, it was a white window similar to the battle platform. Inside the window were rows of buttons and small windows. It was full of writings.

‘Reward 1000 Universal Units Challenge——Glow’ ‘Reward 200 Universal Units Challenge——Geruby’ ‘Death Match (Started) ——Naro vs Corduba’

‘Practice Match—unnamed’ ‘Practice Match—unnamed’ ‘Practice Match—unnamed’…

Chapter 782: Simulation Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were boxes marked by various labels. Among them, practice matches were for free and the number of users was also the highest. The space behind the words Practice Match was marked by Levels, which indicated the Levels of the opponents inside.

‘Please choose whether you want to open a room or join other users’ Battle Rooms’, the mechanical voice sounded again.

Feeling as if he’d really entered a Mech, Garen chose a practice match at Level 1.

‘Entering the Battle Room…Arena, rocky land…Weather, sunny’

‘Loading data…. Please wait for a moment’

After a moment, Garen saw that the circular window in front of him had brightened up. The dark starry sky was replaced by a clear blue sky and a huge white planet hung in the sky, emitting a slight white glow.

He quickly directed his Willpower into the interface that served as a controller for the Mech.

He suddenly became dizzy and felt like he’d been transported out of the Mech and now stood on a piece of red land. The ground was full of craters of different sizes without any sign of life. Other than the craters, all he saw was red soil. The surrounding was barren.

The ground that was full of craters seemed to have stretched to the ends of the horizon.

Moving his body, Garen felt as though he was immersed in a very sticky glue making it very hard for him to move.

He raised his hand with a lot of effort. Only then did he realized that his hand was a red mechanical arm. The surface of the Mech was reflecting a red glow due to the sun rays.

“This is the manipulation of Willpower? It’s almost the same as controlling my own body in real life… Such a realistic simulation technology!” Garen admired.

“Are you done adapting? Can we start now?” a female voice sounded from afar.

Garen looked up.

On the other side, a dark armored Mech was standing beside a huge crater. The Mech was like a muscular giant at six meters tall with a black ax in its hand. One look and anyone would know that it specialized in melee.

There were more than one hundred meters of distance between the black and red Mechs. Compared to the other Mech, Garen’s Mech looked like an unbearably thin child that had gone through a stunted growth.

“Let’s begin,” Garen slightly adapted to the movement of the Mech without the Moonfang’s support.

‘Practice Match begins, the loser will be penalized 100 Universal Units.’ the mechanical voice sounded again.

Garen was stunned, Universal Units were money, and it had to be paid even for this ordinary practice match?

Without giving him any more time to think, the black Mech on the opposite side suddenly sprinted and rushed towards him with a ‘peng peng peng’ sound. The black ax in its hand was brandished in front of its body like a shield.

“Another rookie,” inside the black Mech, Gladys calmly stared at the opposite red Mech, watching it slowly taking out a laser gun, disappointment in her heart.

Only by battling with experts could she improve and become stronger. This was Gladys’ motto. Although there were wins and losses, when she was confronted by a rookie, winning too easily made things meaningless.

“That name was right on point, totally a goof,” she looked at the name on top of the Mech’s head, “a melee Mech is closing in and yet he hasn’t distanced himself.”

The black Mech was approaching the red Mech at a very fast pace.

The distance was rapidly shortening.

50 meters, 40 meters, 20 meters, 10 meters…

Peng!!

The black Mech rolled to the right side and made a backflip, the black ax in its hand swiping out.

Chi!

Only then did Garen managed to lift the laser gun. Although he had made the lifting motion when he saw that black Mech coming, but his Willpower was too weak, causing his instruction to be delayed by a few seconds before his instruction was fully communicated to the Mech. It was too late when he finally managed to lift the muzzle to point at his opponent.

With a crack sound, the red Mech was split into two from the shoulder downwards causing a huge explosion to occur.

Garen’s sight blurred. Coming back to his senses, he had returned to the cockpit and outside the window was a boundless starry sky.

‘Battle ended, you lost. Duration of battle is 21 seconds. 100 Universal Units was lost. 9754 remained.’

Sitting in the cockpit, Garen recalled the brief battle just now. He finally knows the reason Nonosiva was unable to separate from the little Moonfang.

“The Willpower without the Moonfang was totally a target that cannot move. The time between the Willpower issuing instructions to the Mech receiving the instructions was at least five seconds. Five seconds. It was totally enough time for any Mech to sprint to the front and go for the kill. Replacing it with a long-range Mech, one shot can settle it.”

“Look at the remaining 9754 Universal Units, the common students did not have that much money. It must be what Nonosiva had gathered to buy training method. With the Moonfang at his side, even if it was at this Simulation Network, he could win more than he lost with some caution. This money must have been saved by him little by little,” Garen thought.

He looked at the previous battle records of Nonosiva.

The previously recorded battles filled up his sight, right beside the list was the time and date. Roughly looking through, there were at least hundreds of battle.

“Only arriving at the real Level 1 can the Mech be operated freely. Otherwise, it’s a motionless living target.” Garen judged the situation and took out the little Moonfang in his pocket.

Although there were cracks in it, once he took it out and hold it in his hand, Garen suddenly felt comfortable all over his body as though an electric current had spread all over his body.

At this moment, he felt that sitting in the Mech was a lot easier.

“Let’s try again.”

He randomly clicked on a Level 1 practice room.

Hiss….

‘Entering the Battle Room…Arena, rocky land…Weather, cloudy’

‘Loading data….please wait for a moment’

Similar to the environment just now, there were craters of all sort of sizes on the red earth. A Mech without the flight function could only pay extra attention to the craters on the ground. Once they fell into the crater, the battle was as good as over.

Garen looked across the distance.

A white slender humanoid Mech was standing there with two half-moon shields on its arms and within its hands were two silver machetes, looking quite beautiful.

“Another melee Mech?” Garen moved his body. This time the movement was no longer slowed down but pretty smooth.

His hands slightly flashed and two laser guns appeared in his hands.

A series of tips on the long-range shooting was quickly recalled in his mind.

Although he had always been a master at melee, he had also dabbled in long-range shooting too. As long as he took into account his opponent’s moves in countering long-range Mech, it would be alright.

“Let’s begin,” Garen said.

“Ok,” a male response came.

‘Practice Match begins, the loser will be penalized 100 Universal Units’ the mechanical voice sounded again.

Once the voice fell, the white Mech on the other side suddenly rushed here, not by using its legs but using the blue jet thruster behind its back. The speed was astounding.

Chi Chi Chi Chi!

Four laser beams shot out and directly hit the head of the white Mech in front. Even with this high-speed movement, the shot was still amazingly accurate.

Unfortunately, it was ineffective on the armored head of the white Mech that was made of an unknown material. The laser that was shot out only made a few red sparks on it.

Garen raised both his guns and retreated backward but the opponent was too fast. The speed was on a different level.

He could only keep changing the direction he turned. At the same time, his laser guns were shooting non-stop.

The red laser was actually not a real laser but the so-called high-energy beam. This kind of beam was also categorized by levels of lethality. His firearms were of the lowest levels and so without hundreds of shots, penetrating the armor of this opponent was definitely a pipe-dream.

Garen rolled and evaded the two machetes’ chops. In the middle of it, he hurriedly shot twice at the opponent’s waist. Sadly, it was still useless.

He suddenly understood that this opponent was an expert in using expensive protective Mech armor. High-cost Mechs could only be afforded by those rich second generations students. Together with their exclusive training methods, the combined effects were naturally not something that common Mechs could easily break through.

Shooting two more times accurately on the same spot at the waist of the white Mech, it was still ineffective. There was totally no damage that could be seen. The level of lethality was far inferior to the defense provided by the armor of the opponent.

Even if it was also a Level 1 Mech, there was still such a large gap between them. This was not the gap in Willpower but the gap in Universal Units that was thrown into their Mech.

“Too weak! Hahaha,” in the opposite Mech, a voice sounded, “Why are you so lame? Tell me, why are you so lame?” the other party began to mock him.

The machete abruptly accelerated and drew two silver line towards Garen.

The jet thruster behind the white Mech’s back spewed out even more blue flames and produced an instant burst of speed, flying straight towards Garen.

With a clang sound, a white line flashed by. The white Mech had rushed through the side of the red Mech. The silver line that was drawn by the machetes instantly cut off half of Garen’s torso. A little bit more and the red Mech would be split in half. Bursts of sparks came out of the red Mech’s waist.

The white Mech turned around. The jet thruster behind it burst out blue flames again and it pounced towards the opponent. However, it discovered that the red Mech had run away quite a distance.

“Still running? Die!! Stupid Prick!”

The jet thruster at the white Mech’s back spew out a large amount of flames and with a roar, the speed became even faster.

At this moment, Garen turned to the side slightly and incredibly avoided the white Mech’s rush by a few millimeters and swiftly passed by his side.

“Eh…” the white Mech was stunned.

Not only that, Garen lifted his foot and kicked forward.

Peng!

The huge force from the kick combined with the explosive instantaneous force from the jet thruster, and in front was a huge and deep crater….

Without any buffer to stop its momentum, the white Mech crashed into the crater.

It was followed by two laser beams hitting accurately into the opening of the jet thruster. Immediately, an explosion was triggered and the jet thruster was blown to smithereens.

Chapter 783: Test 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was a dull thud.

The white Mech crashed into the crater and rolled a few times. By the time he stood up again, he was already a complete mess, covered with red dirt from the ground.

Garen stood beside the crater and looked down, the white Mech looking at him from below at the bottom of the crater.

“F*ck you!! If you got the balls, then f*cking kill me why don’t you!” The white Mech suddenly went ballistic, spreading open his legs and pointing at his dick. “Come! Hit me here! Hit me!”

“Hit me, why don’t you! What, you scared?! Didn’t you enjoy tricking me just now!?” The white Mech spread his legs open and thrust at Garen. “You dare trick me! Impressive! Are you scared now? I’ll f*cking tell you, this won’t end…” Hah!!

Two lasers hit his dick precisely, and wisps of green smoke rose from it slowly. That place was weaker than others, as expected. The protective armor was nowhere near as thick as other areas.

The surroundings instantly fell quiet. The white Mech looked down at his crotch disbelievingly, and then raised his head again to look at Garen.

Bzz-bzz!

There were two more crisp sounds, and the smoke grew thicker…

“Aaaahhhh!!!!!” The white Mech exploded.

He pointed at Garen with one finger.

“Don’t let me f*cking find out who you are! Otherwise you’re dead! Dead!! You dare trick me! And you dare hit my crotch!! You…”

Bam!!

Two more lasers hit the same place, and the white Mech did not even finish what he was saying before he exploded with a bang, turning into a ball of yellow flame.

“So the weak point is at the crotch, huh…”

Garen looked at the flames beneath him calmly, not feeling much of anything at all. This practice match was not an internal thing in the school anyway, it was connected to the entire Federation’s main internet. Who knows what you are, but let’s see you try to reach the Federation Government’s military division. This simulated game was organized on a website by the military’s higher-ups, in order to make sure it was completely fair, and in order to choose talents from among the people, they were very strict about personal information privacy here. If they could not manage that much, those kids with powerful parents could easily find out their opponent’s information in revenge after getting their asses whooped, and then no one would dare to go for any practice matches anymore.

After winning, a Rubik’s cube abruptly appeared in front of Garen, and spun once.

‘Congratulations on defeating YourDaddy. You have obtained 100 Universal Units, please keep up the good work.’

‘YourDaddy has requested a rematch, do you accept?’

Garen’s expression instantly turned black…

With a smack, he immediately reached out and pressed ‘Reject’.

“What a sucker.”

Leaving the battlefield, Garen glanced around the room again. There were many, many rows of Battle Rooms.

Even that white Mech just now, he was not someone that the previous Nonosiva could have beaten in a million years.

Putting aside that the Mech’s weak point was at the crotch instead of the regular head and cockpit, the opponent’s Mech power was definitely not as low as Level 1 or Level 2, it would have been Level 3 at the very least. Otherwise, it could never reach such a high speed.

For a Level 1 Mech to reach the speed of a Level 3 Mech, that would require components worth at least ten thousand Universal Units, and more than one such component too. This was basically made of money. Normally, they would reach Level 2, tops.

There was also the opponent’s defense Mech system, a Level 1 Laser Cannon was nothing to it. This was an overwhelming difference in level, so it had to at least be Level 3 again. Its destructive power was slightly weaker, but that had to be at least Level 2 as well, just look at those twin swords that slashed off half of Garen’s waist with just a graze.

This fellow was obviously what they called a p2player.

From his memories, Garen could tell that Nonosiva had also encountered such rich players a few times before, and the result was completely predictable. Unsurprisingly, he was demolished, such an overwhelming pwning definitely did critical damage to his pride.

Garen went through Nonosiva’s previous memories, there was some information of how he used to fight left in the fragments. In this planet area of the Mother Planet Federation, Nonosiva’s original ranking was number 215433, at that was including his Moonfang. He was basically a nobody.

Garen casually chose another Level 1 practice match.

It was still the Crater Field, this map was very popular. This time his opponent did not try anything funny, they were also a standard Level 1 normal Mech, just like Garen. The opponent’s technique was not even as good as Nono’s had been, so Garen, with his powerful combat instincts, simply shot off a few rounds at one spot, and killed him in an instant.

After playing a few more rounds, Garen more or less got used to controlling the Mech. By the time Garen left the simulation system, it was nearly 11pm. Looking around him, he noticed that most of the people had left, but one quarter of the machines were still on. Evidently, some people were planning on staying here for the night.

Standing up from the simulator machine, Garen stretched his body. He didn’t feel too bad, there was nothing strange, except for the fact that he had used up too much of his spirit, and felt exhausted.

Leaving the Simulation Machine and returning to his hostel, he cleaned up half-heartedly and lay down to rest.

*************

Ding dong…. Ding dong…

There was the sound of the doorbell coming from the door.

Garen slowly woke up. This body did not have a very high quality of sleep, which meant he did not get a lot of rest.

“Nono, get up! It’s time to go for the official simulation test!” Aier yelled from outside the door.

Garen threw aside the covers and sat up in bed, rubbing his face.

“Got it! Be there in a moment.” Once he was slightly more awake, he quickly got out of bed and drew the curtains with a whoosh. The sun was already out outside, and he could vaguely see the entire Blackboard Academy — several buildings shaped like black boards — through the many trees.

“I remember Instructor Hamm mentioned that the simulation test today officially checks how we practically control the Mech’s regenerative abilities. If all goes well, I should be able to participate in the class ranking competition.” Garen recalled the information he got from before.

The bell rang again, and he walked over to open the door. Aier dashed in like a bullet.

“Hurry up! If we don’t go early, there will be a line until lunch. More than half the school is taking the simulation test at the seventh arena today.” Aier’s hair was plaited, his originally brown hair almost exceeding his chin, just like a girl. It was slightly better and neater than when he would randomly put some braids in his hair, Garen still did not know how he did that.

“What’s up with your hair?” Garen glanced at him. He walked to the washroom and began to wash up.

“My older sister did it for me, don’t blame me…” Aier said in frustration, yanking at his plait, his expression helpless. “Hurry up, why don’t you, I bet the instructors are already at the arena. Students from other schools and going through the test over at our school, they’ve taken up most of the arena, so it’s seriously nervous in there.”

“Got it.” Garen smiled, and hurried up.

After cleaning up quickly, the two of them took their stationary and rushed towards the seventh arena.

There were in fact a lot more students between the buildings suddenly. Other than their own white uniforms with blue stripes, there were also pure red uniforms and black-and-white ones. Evidently, the students from the other schools had arrived.

They reached the arena quickly, but there were already many people lined up around the door. Aier dragged Garen in through the side door, where Instructor Hamm and the others were already waiting.

Mina was there too, as well as a few other students who were also taking the test. One of the boys had white hair and a cold expression, giving off a very distant vibe.

“Just in time.” Hamm smiled as he walked towards them. “How is it? How are you healing?”

“Very well,” Garen nodded and replied politely, smiling. This Instructor Hamm had taken money out of his own wallet to pay the surgery fees, he truly was a good guy.

Hamm nodded. “There are five people taking the test today, the first in ranking is Fervale, no one’s arguing that, and the second place has been decided as well. Third place is between you and Cole. So on one hand we’re testing how well you’re recovering today, but we’re also deciding who’s coming in third.”

“My injuries might not be fully recovered yet…” Garen looked somewhat troubled, he did not really want to join any class ranking competition, he’d rather use this time to study how he should be training himself.

“You’d be representing the class in a competition for all the students in the entire year, everyone in the top ten will be awarded at least ten thousand Universal Units,” Aier reminded him quietly.

“Although I’m not fully recovered yet, but for the sake of the class’s honor, I will do my best!” Garen said loudly, thumping his chest.

Beside him, Aier held his face and turned away.

I really need money right now, I’m totally broke.

Garen was completely honest with himself, and did not blush or intend to change his mind at all. Instead, he stood next to Instructor Hamm with a calm expression, shoulder-to-shoulder with the white-haired young man, Fervale.

Thankfully only he could hear Aier’s voice, so the students did not look at him strangely.

Instructor Hamm patted Garen’s shoulder hard, looking comforted.

“I wasn’t wrong about you! Good luck!”

“Mm!”

To Garen, this was merely a trifling matter. Back when he was in the Secret Technique World, he already had no qualms in the bullying the weak from a position of strength, remember how Duskdune Shura was chased away by him?

They waited with Instructor Hamm beside the arena for a while, and soon enough a protective barrier rose around the arena soundlessly.

“Fervale, you go first.” Hamm looked at the white-haired boy.

“No problem.” Fervale had no expression at all, he looked very reliable. He walked towards the arena entrance on the right, there was a grey warehouse attached to the back of a black board building.

Not long after he went in, there was the buzz of an engine from the arena.

A pure white humanoid Mech walked out of the warehouse entrance. It was six feet tall, and had sharp scythes on its arms like a mantis. It looked slightly similar to the dual-blade Mech Garen had fought, but it did not have the blue flame propeller on its back.

‘Let the first round of the simulation tests, begin,’ a sweet robotic female voice spoke.

After two crisp whooshing sounds, the white Mech’s two scythes abruptly sliced towards both sides, and the entire machine began to dash forward. The blades swept back and forth, waving left and right, slicing through the air crisply.

It looked more like a living person than a Mech, when it raised its dual blades and used those blade techniques, it looked unnaturally alive.

“Fervale’s Mech is overall rated at Upper Level 1, he’s achieved the Level 1 standard in most of his subjects, and has a very balanced skillset.” Instructor Hamm nodded, satisfied. “Add that to his own close combat training, which makes him more mobile and slightly faster than others, and that means trouble for his opponent once he gets close.

The students around him could not help but nod upon hearing that.

The blonde girl in second place, Sara, spoke as well.

“None of us have any objections to Fervale being first place considering his techniques, this test is just a formality. If nothing unexpected happens to Nonosiva, the three of us will be representing our class.”

The others had no objections either. There were more than fifty people in the class, and the first three had been tried and tested against them all, most of the classmates had fought the top three before.

Compared to the top three, it would be considered impressive for the others to have one or two subjects at Level 1, after all they had only been studying for one year. All subjects at the Level 1 standard was already the minimum requirement for graduation, it was about the same as a practical entry-level Mech pilot, the only difference being actual experience.

To normal students, this was the difference between heaven and earth.

Chapter 784: Test 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen knew very well that this difference was like someone who had nearly completed all their credits within one year of university. Or someone taking the Gaokao and having at least 600 marks after the first year of high school.

He observed Fervale’s sword technique closely. There was a faint rhythm in it, which meant that he had evidently reached beginner-level, so he could properly deal with both offense and defense. Seeing as he was just a teenager, this was indeed remarkable.By observing like this, Garen could also more or less figure out where the martial arts development was in this world.

After Fervale came down, the second-placed Sara went up next.

She was a long-range shooter, a long-range target in the shape of a Mech rose up in the arena.

There was nothing much to see there. At five hundred meters, she scored three out of ten hits, with an accuracy rate of 30%. She also landed two out of ten hits when the target was moving, but she did not land any hits when both the target and herself were moving.

Garen calmed down instantly, there was nothing to see here at all.

“Very good! As expected of Sara, your movements are very smooth, and you could even reach such a high accuracy rate at five hundred meters away!” Instructor Hamm clapped, looking comforted.

The other students also applauded, all smiles.

Only then did Garen remember that they were just year one freshmen, most freshmen could barely even walk smoothly. It was already quite impressive to be able to control a Mech to shoot so smoothly with just your Willpower. She could even hit a target five hundred meters away without computer assistance, even though her accuracy rate was slightly on the low side.

“Last one, Nono, go!” Hamm smacked Garen’s shoulder.

Garen nodded, and walked towards the direction of the warehouse.

Sara met him from the front.

“Good luck!” She smiled at him kindly. Looking at him closely, she seemed to be slightly surprised at his uncharacteristically clean and neat look.

“Thanks.” Garen nodded politely.

Entering the warehouse, he found that it was dim and cool inside, with three Mechs standing in a row inside. There was an automated machine arm inside, attaching some components onto the Mechs.

Garen glanced at the three Mechs, they were all the standard White Swan Mechs, all purely white. These were the Blackboard Academy’s traditional Mechs, very balanced in all the stats, known for their high level of stability.

All three were white humanoids, so Garen just randomly chose one and stepped into the elevator.

Amidst a whir of movement, the black elevator brought him up to the Mech’s chest and stopped there.

With a ker-chak, the Mech’s chest opened automatically like a flower bud, revealing the control cabin inside.

Garen jumped inside directly, and the Mech’s Protection Panel closed automatically behind him.

He put on the control helmet, and a panoramic view immediately appeared in front of him, he could see the view outside, and there was a row of options beneath him that he could only see with the helmet on.

‘Please choose your Weapons Mod’

There were three mods, one long-range, one short-range, and one defense.

Garen tapped the long-range icon, after all, Nonosiva had always been using the long-range Mech.

Two more options leaped out of the long-range option, namely Twin Pistols and a Mono-Pistol

He chose Twin Pistols.

“Loading weapon mods…”

With a clacking sound, the whole Mech gave a slight jolt.

‘Loading complete. You may begin the test now.’

The Mechanical voice spoke again.

Garen activated his Willpower, inserting it into a small round hole in front of him. He waited until he felt that he had completely merged with the Mech before he tried to move.

After five whole seconds, the Mech moved slowly, and took one step forward.

“My Willpower doesn’t work at all…” Garen sighed, and took the little Moonfang out of his pocket rather helplessly, putting it on the right side of the control panel.

The Moonfang seemed to have some attraction power, it stuck tight to the control panel as soon as it was placed there, and rapidly began to glow with a white light.

Garen instantly felt a numbness like an electric current flow through his body. The sense of delay from before disappeared utterly.

“I still have to rely on this thing.”

He took a deep breath, and watched the Moonfang’s condition carefully. Last time, Nonosiva’s Mech stopped moving because the Moonfang suddenly failed, and it nearly resulted in tragedy. Now it seemed that he had used the Moonfang too much, causing it to overload.

Controlling his body, Garen strode out of the warehouse. The world instantly brightened as the sunlight outside his eyes, unnaturally bright, and even slightly piercing.

The contents of the test were some basic movements, and then a set of standard battle skill simulations.

Garen chose the Twin Pistols, so his simulation contents were not unlike Sara’s.

A Mech target rose up five hundred meters away.

Garen stood at the warehouse entrance and raised his two guns, releasing the safeties. These were not laser guns but guns with metal bullets, so they had some rebound.

Bang bang!

After two gunshots, the target in the distance lit up, which evidently meant that he had hit them.

That was two consecutive hits, and it raised a slight murmur of surprise from the surrounding students.

Garen glanced sideways and saw that even Instructor Hamm looked surprised, so he decided to tone it down a little. To him, someone who was already a peak-level martial arts grandmaster, he had extremely precise control over his body. Hitting a target five hundred meters away was a piece of cake, after all, the target was a five-meter-tall Mech.

The second time, Garen purposely pressed the barrels down.

After two more gunshots, he did not hit anything.

There was a murmur of pity from the side.

Garen took some time to glance at the Moonfang, the white light on it was twinkling, unlike during the online simulation battles last night. After all, he was driving a real Mech now, so it definitely took a lot more effort.

He did not move much, and shot off the remaining rounds calmly.

In the end, he landed three out of ten hits, just like Sara.

After that was the moving target.

One hit.

When he had to move with the target, he also missed all the shots.

In the last bit, when he had to move with the target, Garen watched in terror as the Moonfang began to emit smoke, the twinkling light growing more and more urgent. He knew that after it was damaged once, the Moonfang had also become extremely fragile. In the past, such movements would not be any problem whatsoever.

“The test is over.” Instructor Hamm’s voice came in through the barrier.

Only then did Garen quickly stop moving, and began walking towards the warehouse slowly.

By the time he walked to the spot in the warehouse where he was supposed to park his Mech, the Moonfang’s white light had already dimmed down. It looked like it was at the end of its tether, and was scalding hot to the touch.

Garen took off his helmet, and lifted his hand to see the time on his white watch.

“Approximately eleven minutes, perhaps slightly longer. The Mech can’t move too quickly, even if I maintained the same slow pace as I had in the end, I can probably only last for fifteen minutes max.”

“Looks like I have no choice but to be a long-range shooter.” Garen felt helpless, he still needed to be a long-range defensive shooter, because that only required very simple movements, and did not involve complicated movements with his whole body.

Picking up the Moonfang that was still burning his hand, Garen got out of the cockpit, and stepped onto the elevator.

Aier was already waiting for him in the warehouse below.

“Not bad!” Aier patted Garen’s arm with a laugh.

“It was only okay,” Garen smiled.

He was still worried about the Moonfang, he did not know how long it would take for this thing to recover.

“Nonosiva, would you like to fight a match with me?” A calm voice came suddenly from the warehouse entrance.

Garen and Aier looked up to see Fervale standing at the warehouse entrance, looking their way.

“A match?” Garen frowned. “I’m not interested.”

Fervale was slightly stunned, it did not seem to occur to him that Garen would reject him so decisively.

He had also seen how smoothly Garen was controlling the Mech, he had achieved Sara’s results with relative ease, and had evidently not used all of his power. That was why Fervale grew interested, but he did not think that the other party would reject him so directly.

He was not very good at speaking, so he also could not think of what to say there. Normally, once he asked, he would rarely ever get rejected. After all, his family background and his own excellent performance made the other students in his class unable to reject him.

After a pause.

“Fine, then,” he said calmly after recovering. “The person you injured that day, some people from his family are at the staffroom now. Instructor Hamm pressed down that incident that day, but I think it’s not over yet. You be careful now.”

“Thank you.” Garen had thought about that himself as well, but now that Fervale was warning him as well, he began to pay more attention to it.

In actuality, it was his acting up last time that got the opponent spooked, that was why his opponent just froze there, and was finally hit by his retaliating shot. Half of his body had been burned up, and he nearly lost his life as well. It was all thanks to the wonders of medical technology that he got out of the hospital one month earlier than Garen.

If Garen was still paralyzed in bed, perhaps the other guy might let him go. But now that he had somehow left the hospital good as new, the other person was probably going to try something else.

Walking out of the warehouse with Aier, Fervale left the arena directly, walking towards the other arena, probably in order to watch how the students from other schools fared in their ranking tests.

Garen greeted the instructor, and seeing that most of the other students had scattered to watch the other matches, Garen found an opportunity to walk with the instructor alone.

“Instructor Hamm, I wanted to ask, how’s the family background of that student I accidentally injured last time?”

Instructor Hamm did not look particularly surprised.

“Did they find you?”

“No, Fervale just reminded me there, so I wanted to know more about them,” Garen replied honestly.

“That student’s name is Corlan, someone in his family is an instructor at the academy, with decent ability, I guess. Don’t worry, I’ll help out with this matter, after all it was all just an accident, nobody meant for it to end that way,” Instructor Hamm lit a cigarette and spoke after taking one puff.

“Thank you, Instructor,” Garen nodded, even though he was inwardly not bothered.

Leave the instructor, he split up with Aier, and took one round around the arena, watching the tests in the other arenas.

The Mechs were engaged in intense battle, their movements quick and fluid. Their techniques and skills were no lower than what Garen understood as third- or second-rate combat skills, and there were many complicated and precise movements as well. But most of these were undergoing a higher-level test.

Even so, he had garnered a clearer understanding of this world.

Although he was a Secret Technique Grandmaster, and had been at the peak of his era, the martial arts skills here were pretty decent as well, and they could develop into something even greater. Some of these combination skills, and all those powerful combinations of cold and hot weapons, created all sorts of strange effects. Without an understanding of how the opponent’s weapons worked, and if they used peak-level combat skills, perhaps even Garen could fall to such an opponent at his current level. After all, his body was way too weak, nowhere near as powerful as he was in his previous lives.

After taking one round, he went back to the dorms directly, and began to train diligently.

Right now, his biggest problem was that his power was not his own, and came instead from the Moonfang. Should he be discovered, that would be in violation of academy rules, and he would be guilty of lying to the administration. They might even disable his Willpower altogether.

Chapter 785: Hope 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The days passed one after the other.

Before he knew it, a week had passed with Garem just consistently practicing this exact training regime. This body was indeed very average in quality, in a normal academy, he would probably be considered a normal student, but in the Blackboard Academy, he would only be at the very lowest level.

If it were not for the Moonfang, he probably would not be able to survive in the academy at all. After all, students with low marks had to pay extremely high tuition fees, it would be way beyond the means of an average-income family like his.

So even though he did not want to use the Moonfang, in order to come into contact with the main power source and powerful entities in this world, he had no choice but to keep up the lie.

His training over the past few days had shown him just how average his body was in quality. After one week, his Willpower had only risen a tiny bit, and if he did not sense it carefully, he would not be able to tell anything was different at all.

He was still impossibly far from the Level 1 standard.

Because his talents were too slow to progress, Garen had no choice but to look for another method to upgrade himself. And the first thing he could think of was his special Ability’s potential points.

Fwah….

The rain poured down outside the window, blowing the branches of large locust tree into a slant. The raindrops fell onto the surface of the leaf, onto the windows and the glass, making a pattering sound.

Garen sat beside the table in the hostel, with a laptop in front of him. It was playing clips of Mech battles, but although Garen’s gaze was trained on the clip, his attention had actually wandered to his attribute pane.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 0.6, Agility 1.1, Vitality 0.4, Intelligence 1.3, potential power 0%. Soul limit 40.’

‘Willpower — Middle Basic Level’

‘Attribute — Void Pursuer’

‘Soul Seed — Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, Holy Phoenix Demonic Book.’

‘Secret Technique — Imprint of Steel: increases one’s physical strength and vitality.’

“My Strength has recovered a little bit through this training, it went up by 0.1. My Vitality went up by 0.1 as well. Not bad, considering I don’t have potential points.” The truth was that Garen had been keeping an eye for anything that could contain potential points a long time ago, but unfortunately he had not discovered anything while he was at the hospital nor after returning to the academy.

This terrifying quality of his, even slower than a snail, had completely worn away his patience. If he continued upgrading himself at this pace, he would probably need at least more than ten years to reach Level 2 or 3.

He could not bear having to waste so much time.

“Looks like I need to gather information about this world’s research on the human body, medical studies, and the like. Reorganizing my secret techniques is one thing, but the ultimate power of the secret techniques is really far from the Mechs in this world, it would be best if I could learn about this world here, then absorb and integrate that knowledge. I forgot to do that in the previous world, and in the end I used secret techniques to destroy the entire world’s power system. That’s very disadvantageous towards my gathering my Soul Seed, I was basically retreading old roads.”

Garen mused it over, and came to a conclusion.

To him, normal secret techniques had brought him as far as they could go. The Soul Seed level had already surpassed normal secret techniques, and reached a brand new level. This level absorbed other sorts of understandings, and in turn gathered into different Soul Seeds.

“Secret techniques can only be temporarily used for self-defense, if I want to reach a higher level, the only way would be to absorb the strengths of this world’s power system, perhaps that can bring me up to the next level.” Garen hesitated for a moment, looking at the torrential downpour outside.

“I’ll just make a trip to the flea market here then.”

It was still early, just slightly past two in the afternoon. Since he did not have class in the afternoon, Garen stayed in his dorm to rest and train his “Blackboard Manipulation”, which meant that he had the free time now to check out the flea market near the academy.

The market had a collection of all sorts of small-time merchants and peddlers, creating a small market where they bought and sold. They bought some small items from the students of the academy, and sold them off at a profit.

For example, they would trade in some upper-level students photocopied notes, their training comprehensions, or small components made by the maintenance students, even the scrap metal taken out of the academy warehouses. Anything that could be used or not was thrown here for sale. As long as it had something to do with the Blackboard Academy’s Mech pilots, it was worth a considerable sum of money.

Likewise, these merchants would also bring in materials from outside, or transport some specific items for some students, in a mutually beneficial arrangement.

Sometimes, some of the merchants were even the academy’s own students.

**********************

As usual, Corlan was waiting for his younger brother at the school entrance so that they could go back home together.

After he accidentally sustained critical injuries in the Level 1 test last time, he heard that his father had already settled this matter, and the other side was also punished accordingly, so he let it slide. He had also returned to his regular life, chatting over the phone with his girlfriend, going racing on the streets with his buddies after class, playing Mech simulation battles, and training at night.

The heavy rain pattered at his feet, water sliding down his umbrella, almost forming a veil of water.

“Cor, shall we go back together?” a red-haired boy waved at him and asked in the midst of the shuffling crowd at the entrance.

“Nah, I’m waiting for my bro,” Cor smiled. “Weren’t you guys supposed to go play cards? Are you still going now?”

“My pops asked me to get something all of a sudden.” The red-haired boy leaned in closer. “Oh yeah, I saw that freshman from your test last time today.”

“Oh?” Cor was slightly stunned. “Isn’t he in the hospital?”

“Looks like he’s all better now, I don’t know when he got discharged,” the red-haired boy said casually. “What do you plan to do? You just need to say the word.”

Cor’s smile faded slowly, but he did not say anything.

“You’re at the top of our class, third in the second year! If you don’t retaliate after a freshman sent you to the hospital, wouldn’t just about anyone be able to come mess with our Class b1?” the red-haired boy said angrily.

“The matter of the surgery fees has been settled, so that means case closed,” Cor said simply after calming himself down. Glancing at the red-haired boy who still looked like he had something to say, Cor smiled again. “Alright, go play your cards!”

“Fine fine fine, you sure are generous, the case is closed, just as you said.” The red-haired boy looked at him admiringly. “I sure respect you, if it were me, I wouldn’t stop until I killed that…”

“Alright, alright, hurry on,” Cor interrupted him, patting the red-haired boy’s shoulder. Only then did the boy walk away with his umbrella, still ranting loudly.

Watching the boy leave in the rain, Cor’s smile faded slowly.

He kept remembering the situation that day.

“That shot… was it a coincidence, or…” He could still clearly remember the moment he was shot.

That shot was practically impossible. It was a textbook pose, but the shooter was nearly laying sideways on the floor, the barrel barely moving. It completely ignored the delay caused by the rebound, ignored the slant caused by the difference in position, and he did not even aim, he barely just flinched.

And even then, he could hit Cor’s cockpit precisely.

“Big Bro,” a similarly calm voice interrupted his thoughts.

Cor came back to reality, looked at his younger brother in front of him, and smiled.

“Let’s go, time to go home.”

His younger brother Caus was the top seat of the first year Class c2. He had short cropped blue hair and wore gold earstuds, his body tall and strong, with a faint scar on his right cheek. That was a mark left behind from a brawl in high school.

Caus stood beside Cor, and was one whole head taller than his older brother. He cocked his head slightly, greeting two girls as they passed by. Even when he smiled, he gave off a ferocious vibe.

Cor walked in front and Caus followed behind him. For a moment, neither spoke.

When they went past the main academy gates, Cor suddenly stopped and turned around.

“You don’t have to mind my business, this matter is settled.”

Caus instantly smiled widely.

“I know, Bro, I don’t plan to mess with the guy, do I?”

Cor frowned as he looked at his younger brother, and could not tell if he was lying or not. His little brother had always idolized him ever since they were young, treating him as his standard for everything. This time he had gotten seriously injured, went into the hospital, and nearly died. It would be weird if Caus did not do anything.

“Forget it, let’s go back.”

He turned around, flagged down a levitating cab, and darting inside.

Caus smiled very brightly.

“I’ve been rather busy with some troublesome matters myself as well, so I don’t have the time to bother with your stuff. I’ll do as you say.” He ducked into the cab as well, but no one saw the ruthlessness in the depths of his eyes.

*********************

The flea market

There was a rectangular silver rain cover beside the academy, blocking off the heavy downpour outside.

Under the cover, there were many small trolley stalls set up there. There were even more merchants with their wares on the floor further inside, and some people had even hung up some cloths beside the cover at the academy’s outer wall to form small stalls. It was a sea of colors inside, with all manners of items inside.

It was raining heavily, so even the usually crowded market was relatively empty, with just a few students and outsiders wandering around the stalls, mostly merely window-shopping.

Garen mingled in with the crowd, and examined each of the stalls one after the other.

As long as there was anything with potential energy within five meters of him, he could be able to sense it. But he had been here for over a dozen minutes, and walked past a dozen stalls, and still he did not sense even the tiniest hint of potential energy.

After walking past a small cart, Garen’s gaze fell slightly onto something on the cart.

“Come come come, look at the newest Butterfield Butterfly Steel Piece, it’s perfect as a Mech’s buffer piece, it’s just two hundred points per piece,” the cart owner instantly greeted him passionately. “Just put one of these where the wear and tear are the worst, and you’ll surely be able to buffer it perfectly.”

Garen glanced at the cart, there was a row of white things that looked like garlic hanging on it, strung up into circles. He had no idea what they were, but there were many metal and wooden bottles arranged underneath it, as well as other small knick-knacks.

From Mech components to feminine skin care products, or even man-made crystal jewelry and small snacks, there was practically everything you could ever want or need.

The cart owner was an older man in his forties, his mouth flapping endlessly without pausing even for a second. After greeting Garen, he caught the attention of three or four more customers, and for a second there business seemed to be booming.

Garen’s gaze swept across the cart, but he still could not find any hint of potential energy. Feeling slightly disappointed, he prepared to leave.

But suddenly he seemed to remember something, and he abruptly looked back at something beside the stall.

Chapter 786: Hope 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was a small white stone, just about the size of a thumbnail, mixed in with a plate of other randomly-colored stones. There were more than just white stones in there, there were yellow, black and red stones as well. The white stone was completely inconspicuous among them. But Garen’s gaze was still fixed onto that one stone.

“It’s a bit like…” He was not very sure either.

He reached out his hand to pick up that plate of pebbles. In the black, palm-sized stainless steel plate, there were seven or eight stones just like that one.

“These are the Rainbow Stones from the Thousand Island Region, fifty units for one. The differently-colored stones will emit colorful sparks when rubbed with a hard object, they’re mostly used in chemical experiments to make Glowing Light R,” the cart owner immediately began to explain the origins and functions of the stone to Garen when he saw that Garen was interested.

Garen knew that as well, the Mother Planet Federation was currently split up. Each of the territories was divided into regions, and different regions had different specialties.

“Dazzling Light R? Do you mean that special combustible fuel that only high-level Mechs could use?” He searched his memory for that information.

“Yup yup, that’s the one. You interested? I can give you a discount, you can take this whole plate back for just two hundred units.” The cart owner waved his hand nonchalantly, acting as though he was just trying to clear his stock even at a huge loss.

“A hundred units.” Garen held the plate in his hand, and felt a jolt in his shock in his heart. Once he made his conclusion, he offhandedly returned an offer.

“A hundred units?!” The cart owner’s expression immediately turned exaggerated. “I wouldn’t even be able to break even with a hundred units, a hundred and eighty at the least!”

Garen nodded.

“I can only do a hundred units.”

Perhaps the cart owner had never met someone so decisive when shopping. On the other end, someone was asking him about a mechanical component, that was a treasure worth five hundred units, he could earn a lot from that. After doing some calculations, he decided that these stones were just the most common item from the Thousand Island Region, and he had bought them at only five units each. Eight stones were worth only forty points, so it was a pretty good haul if he could sell them at a hundred units.

He waved his hand.

“Alright, alright, a hundred units it is. I’m only selling it to you because you were honest, remember to stop by again next time…”

“If you have more of these white stones next time, I can buy them in bulk for twenty units each,” Garen said, picking up that white stone with a smile. He seemed to be in a very good mood.

The cart owner immediately paused, and appraised Garen carefully. “You sure?” he asked.

“Of course, I can give you my phone number,” Garen said with a nod.

“How many do you want?” Seeing that this could be a big deal for him, the cart owner hurried calmed down the other customer, and began to discuss the prices face-to-face with Garen.

“At least a hundred or more,” Garen replied bluntly. “And I might need more later.”

“A hundred or more…” The cart owner licked his lips, and was thoroughly intrigued. If he bought in bulk, he might even be able to lower the price. If he bought one for four units there and sold them for twenty each here, then he would earn sixteen units for one stone, and 1600 for a hundred!

He immediately felt immensely pleased. 1600 units was equivalent to his profits for a month. This one deal could earn him what he used to earn over a month.

The cart owner’s eyes began to shine, and his expression grew gentler.

“Are you sure you want more than a hundred? What if there are even more than that?”

“I want as many as possible, but I don’t have enough funds for now, three hundred might be my extent,” Garen said calmly. In truth, he was also overjoyed inside.

If he was not mistaken, this white stone actually contained parts of the White Peacock Stone!

He had not found any antiques or potential points, but he somehow managed to find a stone containing traces of the White Peacock Stone. This gave Garen a complicated, indescribable feeling.

That was the White Peacock Stone, the most basic necessity for training the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. He could not make any progress in the last world just because he could not find this item, and now he had accidentally discovered it in a flea market.

Such a precious material was being used as fuel? What a waste of resources!

According to the knowledge in his memories, the combustible parts of the White Peacock Stone were the most useless parts. The true essence lay in what was left behind, to think that they sell the shell and toss the pearl over here.

“Less than three hundred but more than one hundred, right? No problem!” the cart owner agreed heartily. “When do you need the stock? I can bring it in for you within two days.”

“The sooner the better, naturally,” Garen replied.

Tossing the white stone in his hand, the smile on his face grew more natural.

The cart owner also had an irrepressible smile on his face, with his connections, it was ridiculously easy for him to get these stones.

******************

Garen continued to take a few more rounds around the flea market, but he did not discover anything else, only the impure White Peacock Stones he had found by accident at that cart.

Returning home from the flea market, Garen immediately darted into his dorm room with that stone, and hung up a ‘Do Not Disturb’ sign on the door.

Pinching the stone, Garen sat cross-legged on the bed. The curtains were drawn, it was still raining heavily outside.

Closing his eyes quietly, Garen sank into his spiritual space.

In the pitch-black space, the two basketball-sized Soul Seeds were spinning on their own, floating in the middle like two bright light orbs, one blue and one green, both unusually eye-catching.

And behind the two Soul Seeds, he could vaguely see two tiny lights, the size of fireflies, floating there.

Garen reached his consciousness over, and touched the two dots of lights lightly.

He swept over the red light, this was a Living Secret Technique seed with the metal attribute, it required training deep in the ore mines. He could not accomplish that at all now.

The other blue one was the Hellfrost Peacock Technique he had practised before. Ever since he stopped being able to make progress with it and left that world, this seed returned to being a Living Secret Technique seed, floating quietly in the depths of Garen’s soul.

Once his consciousness touched the blue light, in an instant, an icy blue mist spread over his consciousness.

Waah! Waah!

The cry of a phoenix that sounded like a child’s wailing rang in Garen’s ears.

The waves of blue mist from the Hellfrost Peacock Technique instantly spread out from his head.

Sitting on the bed cross-legged, a hint of deep blue flashed past the bottom of Garen’s eyes, waves of invisible blue mist spreading out from the depths of his soul, expanding inside his body. That was a sense of deep cold, icy and slow, starting from his head and moving downward, going past his neck, his chest, spreading towards his limbs.

“Only Living Secret Techniques can completely ignore the difference in worlds, and the difference in bodies, this is a powerful martial arts made from the most basic of rules… It’s a shared principle that can be used in any world!”

The same words were repeated in Garen’s heart.

Waves of blue mist that could not be seen with the naked eye extended to all parts of his body.

A dot of blue light was beating and twinkling lightly on his chest, brightening and dimming, as though it was breathing.

Garen’s whole body was trembling slightly, this body was still different from the other ones, after all. Its basic genetic structure was different, but that was okay. No matter what structure it was, the Living Secret Technique was itself alive, so it could grow accustomed to a human’s body, slowly absorbing nutrients to grow into the secret technique system most compatible with the user’s body. Even if there were a thousand seeds given to a thousand people to train with, those thousand people would end up with a thousand different Living Secret Techniques.

Garen’s whole body was so cold that his shivered, his skin growing whiter and whiter. It even had a trace of blue to it, and there was even a light layer of white frost on his hair.

After nobody knew how long, the cold creeping up on his body finally retreated slightly, and only then did Garen recover, his gaze landing on his Ability’s attribute pane.

There was a new icon on the secret technique pane.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Grade one elementary level (Total of five grades, with three grades of derivative grades, a total of eight grades) Every time the practitioner reaches the next level, their blood and veins will be purified, and they will slowly approach the Hellfrost Peacock body type, finally becoming the ultimate form, the Hellfrost Peacock King, with Army Level being the limit.’

“As expected, it is very easy to enter the elementary level.” Garen opened his eyes, raised his hand, and looked at the white stone in his hand.

Sensing the power pathways spread like dense spiderwebs in his body, he felt the wisps of cold energy flow tightly down these three-dimensional paths, like the tubes in the most precise piece of equipment.

Garen moved slightly, and a wisp of cold air immediately rushed out of his palm, precisely piercing into the stone in his hand.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s first grade was very easy to reach, but it did not do much other than lowering his body temperature. This time it was different, he had the White Peacock Stone, even if it was merely an impurity, this stone naturally contained a material very similar to the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s bloodline, so it had the effect of speeding up the Peacock Technique.

Sitting on the bed, Garen watched as the white stone in his hand melted rapidly, and collapsed, turning into a small mound of white powder in his palm.

“This is a Living Secret Technique, only someone who owns a Living Secret Technique seed may truly practise this secret technique,” Garen was slightly thoughtful. He felt the material seep into his palm like water, and then it was rapidly split up and absorbed by the countless cold energy inside his body.

After all the material had been split up, Garen felt as though his Peacock Technique had improved a little.

Glancing at his skill pane, he saw that there was a new blood-red explanation symbol behind the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s strange ice-blue peacock icon.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Grade one elementary level, grade 2 completion at 12%.’

“There’s 12% completion in one tiny impure stone, not bad…” Garen carefully stored the white ash into a small bottle and capped it properly. This was the distilled fuel for a high-level Mech, if he gathered enough of it, he could also sell it for money.

In the next two days, he still calmed himself down and trained properly every day. The effect of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s first grade was very minor, and it had no effect at all on his Willpower. Garen guessed that they would help each other to some extent at the higher levels.

Every night he would persist with joining a few simulation battles, so that he could understand the ways Mechs fought in this world.

After going on like this for so long, he began to build a reputation for himself in battle, and he had also risen up to the top 150,000 in the Level 1 area. After winning more than ten battles consecutively, he earned more than a thousand Universal Units. Therefore, simulation battles became Garen’s only method of earning money quickly.

Chapter 787: Family 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the scarlet-red Crater Field

Two hundred meters apart, two red Mechs were dodging and shooting at each other madly. White and red lasers missed each other by hairs, most of them landing on the ground and creating many burnt black marks.

The Mech on the left was a standard red humanoid, wielding two guns. It looked very average, and was the most basic Mech model.

And the one on the right was a completely different Mech, a large red spider, not humanoid at all. The spider’s front four legs had four laser cannons attached to the outside of its joints, and its many digital compound eyes gave off a chilling effect.

“Let’s call it a day here.” The humanoid Mech stopped shooting suddenly, avoiding a laser beam as thick as an arm, and standing still beside a crater.

“We still can’t decide a winner,” a helpless voice came from within the spider. “How many times have we fought since we met the day before yesterday?”

“Fifteen times, this is the sixteenth,” the humanoid Mech replied.

“Fine, sixteen… I really wonder, what kind of a person are you inside?” The person inside the spider sighed. “Forget it, I’m going offline too, the money this time is yours.”

“Thanks.”

“No problem.”

With a whoosh, the red spider abruptly distorted, and disappeared from where it stood.

‘Congratulations, you defeated Kanar. You received 1000 Universal Units, please keep up the good work.’

The voice came from the system.

Only then did Garen recover. Staring at the spinning cube in front of him, he chose to exit the map.

For the past few days, he had been training the Hellfrost Peacock Technique on one hand and getting to know the online battle skills on the other. But after messing around aimlessly for some time, he had somehow actually encountered a true fighter.

Kanar, a long-range shooter using the spider model Mech. He was more than just strong, he could control four shooters and aim them as he pleased at his enemy, and he could even properly use the crisscrossing lasers to have them reflect off each other, reaching angles that he would have never been able to shoot.

The first time they met, Garen nearly lost badly, but thankfully his basics were also very strong. After they had gotten accustomed to each other, the two of them began their intense opposition. Garen’s precision was terrifying, no matter how his opponent changed directions, he could still track him down quickly. Even with the Spider’s mobility and leaping, his accuracy was still over 50%. But his own mobility was too low, he only ever moved in a small range.

And the Spider’s shooting was more reliant on its unexpectedness, and was even stronger in its strange and highly mutable high-speed movements. After Garen took a few small losses, the two sides were engaged in a deadlock.

They had fought over ten matches consecutively over two days, with equals wins and losses, but Kanar the Spider knew that this was in fact his loss, because he was using a specialized model whereas his opponent was only using the most standard Mech model.

Garen exited the map, and returned to the selection room where everything was like a starry sky.

He glanced at his remaining Universal Units: 12560.

This was the result of his labor over the past few days, although there were wins and losses, he still won more than he lost. Unless he met those completely irrational outliers, who had terrifying levels of Mechs or Willpower, he would not lose.

He tapped opened his ‘friends’ panel, and there was only one name inside — Kanar. They had bonded over their battles, and added each other as friends. But now Kanar’s icon had turned grey, he had evidently gone offline.

“Last match.” Garen glanced through the whole Level 1 battlefield, and pressed the sort by ranking option. “Let’s see how far I am from the peak-level fighters.”

Suddenly the room changed with a whoosh, and after it settled quickly, several new rooms appeared in front of him.

Suddenly he saw a room opened by a vaguely familiar ID, the room name was: ‘Dobe if you got the balls then go 1-1 with me!’ and the username with it was ‘YourDaddy’.

“This guy still hasn’t given up,” Garen laughed. After he tortured this person last time, he would always open up a room and waste money to keep it there.

This idiot was somehow one of the frontrunners in Level 1, that was evidently a result of the overwhelming advantage from his powerful specialized Willpower and the Mechs he bought with money.

If he hadn’t tricked him last time, Garen believed that it would have been hard for him to beat that guy. Be it in Mechanical power, weaponry, or defense, he was no match for him. If he had not destroyed his opponent’s propeller back there and let him fall into the crater, Garen probably would have no other way to finish him off.

Plus, Garen was not going into the practice match rooms anymore now, he went straight into matches with rewards of at least 1000 units or more, otherwise, he would not be able to earn at all.

He glanced at his watch terminal, it was three in the afternoon, and there was a missed call from that shop owner over there.

Garen was slightly happy, that must definitely mean that the White Peacock Stones were here. He dialed back quickly, and after some ringing, an old man’s head appeared on his watch screen.

“The things are here, when are you coming over to get them?” the cart owner uncle said excitedly as soon as he saw Garen.

“Straight to the flea market?”

“No, come to a rented house beside it, we’ll exchange the goods and money on the spot,” the uncle shook his head. “We’d be too obvious in the flea market.”

“Sure.”

“The place is at the building next to the gazebo by the right main street.”

Turning off his watch, Garen stood up and looked around him. There were not many people online to battle at this time, most students were at class.

The classes here were not that different from the previous world, the lecturer would drag on and on, talking about nonsense for half a day. Garen went for a few classes and then decided to play hooky, no one cared about your attendance here, as long as you could pay the fees and reach the final standard required for graduation, it didn’t matter even if you didn’t attend a single class.

Leaving his position, he picked up his school coat and walked out.

When he left the simulation room, a few people who had been sitting up behind him got up at the same time. They exchanged a glance, and then followed him quickly.

By the time Garen left the simulation building, it was already nearing the evening outside, the sunlight was slightly dimming, and it was not too hot.

Garen went against the flow of the crowd, walking towards the school gates. When he passed the school gates, some students dressed in white uniforms with silver linings just happened to walk out of the school gates at the same time, their expressions somber. They got onto a silver levitating car, with teachers from the school waiting at the gate especially for them.

When Garen walked past this group of more than ten students, he felt hints of killing intent, and he grew serious.

“These people have all taken life and seen blood.”

He retreated to a side, mingling in with the crowd of regular students who were gathered to watch, and observed this group as they quickly got into the car.

Some people were discussing the identities of these students in low voices.

“They’re the elite students.”

Someone mentioned the answer.

“The best students of the academy, huh… I heard that not only do they not need to pay school fees, they even get a salary from the academy every month, and a considerable one, at that.”

“Well, duh, their powers are all Level 2 and above, they’re our Blackboard Academy’s most elite forces, usually it’s the teachers from the inner circle that teach and tutor them.”

“I heard that the elite students are students, but they’re also the academy’s central forces, wonder if that’s true,” two boys were chatting softly not far from where Garen was standing.

“It’s true, apparently there are even Level 3 and above elites among these students, they’re really powerful. An elite fighter who has an overall ranking of Level 3, if armed with a suitable Mech, could take several dozens of us, no problem,” another girl replied determinedly. “My older sister is an elite student, she gets a salary of at least 50,000 units every month, it’s more than enough to handle our household expenses. She can also choose any academy lecturer she wants to tutor her, but she needs to spend a certain amount for that.”

“That’s already really good! Normal students like us can’t even meet lecturers like that, okay?” the boy from before said jealously.

“But they have certain responsibilities too, the school’s true firepower is actually them. They will only step down if the actually enter the military or when they turn thirty, or when they become instructors end up serving as the administrators in other areas,” the girl explained in detail.

Garen got a little closer to these people, he wanted to listen more carefully. It was not just him, many of the other students were gathering, listening to the girl’s explanation.

“But usually the elite students wouldn’t go out on missions, the police are enough to handle most regular incidents, only special cases would require these powerful Level 2 and above elites. Something must have happened outside, that’s why they’ve been mobilized.”

“I heard there was a fatal riot in East Star City, this incident involved a lot of people, I wonder if they were mobilized for that,” someone said from among the crowd.

“Should be,” the girl nodded, “my older sister has moved out, she’s part of the first batch of elites, and this is the third batch. I wonder what happened, for them to mobilize three teams of elites.”

“Could it be that other regions are attacking us?”

“How could that be? Our Blackboard Region is one of the strongest regions out there, we’d be the ones attacking others.”

Garen stoppedd listening there, turning around and darting out of the crowd. He watched as the elite students’ levitating car flew off slowly, rapidly leaving the academy gates.

Only then did he walk towards the place he was supposed to meet that uncle.

“I had better get the stones first before anything else, this body is too average, and I can’t find potential points. Perhaps my only hope of improving this body lies in the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.”

The academy was located in the central area of Blackboard City, other than the huge mountain wall behind it, the other three sides were all busy streets and markets, with huge swathes of bustling shops in the central business district. Honking sounds came from the flow of never-ending traffic.

There were many outstation tourists wandering the walkways, as well as a few residents who lived nearby, and the occasional students from Bloackboard Academy. Whenever these students passed by, the people around them would always give them a glance.

Garen mingled into the crowd, his black hair tied into a ponytail behind him. Afte.

There were mostly tourists from abroad walking across the sidewalks, and a few residents who lived nearby, as well as a couple of Blackboard Academy students mixed in between. Whenever these students passed by, the people around them would also glance at them a little longer than usual.

Garen mingled with the crowd, his black hair tied up into a ponytail behind his head. After he cleaned up and looked neater, he gave off a calm and quiet aura, not very handsome, but soothing to the eye.

Chapter 788: Family 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beep beep… Beep beep…

Suddenly the Terminal on his hand started beeping. Garen raised his hand up and looked at it to realize that Nono’s father Rondo had sent in this month’s living allowance, which was about a thousand Universal Units.

He frowned.

Nonosiva’s family wasn’t wealthy to begin with, and they still had to support his monthly living expenses after paying for his semester’s tuition fee. This placed their family in straitened circumstances to the point where his brother and sister had to give up on going to school to reduce their expenses. All of these had to be done in order to support Nono studying in Blackboard Academy.

One could say that the family had placed all of their hopes onto Nono. His parents scraped by and were very reluctant in eating meat at all and had to eat processed food most of the time.

After pondering for a while, Garen walked towards specific location and gave Nono’s father, Rondo a call.

The phone was instantly connected.

“I can only give you this much. Nono, you should try and cut down your expenses. I’m at my limit…” Rondo’s tired and old face appeared at the end. His eyes were filled with blood vessels and he hadn’t slept from the overtime he had done for two straight days. He did so much to squeeze out his son’s living expenses and even gave away all of his salary. The company wasn’t bringing in money lately so he couldn’t do much more than he had already done. He had no choice but to let his wife handle the housing expenses and the monthly medicine required for his grandmother’s illness. All five members of the house needed to eat and dress, and the financial stress was making him feel stretched to his limits.

Garen didn’t expect that Rondo would think that he was asking for money. Judging on this, it seemed that Nonosiva wouldn’t have called home unless he required more money. This was probably why his father felt so hopeless.

He looked at the pale and tired Rondo inside the monitor. Although he wasn’t his real-life father, Garen felt touch by his actions and hence, he decided to repay them for taking over his son’s body.

He opened his mouth but he wasn’t able to say the word ‘dad’. Afterall he was much older than him.

“I don’t need money and I have enough here. You don’t have to credit me any more Universal Units in the future, so you can save it for yourself.” he took a breath before explaining it to him.

“You don’t need money? Your academy’s expenses are huge. How are you going to survive without money?” Rondo opened his mouth wide as he looked very surprised. “Don’t worry about it. Your brother has recently started working and has gotten this month’s pay. I plan to send his money to you tomorrow but I guess I will credit it to you now.”

He immediately called someone else on the phone and soon Garen’s Terminal beeped again and another three hundred Universal Units had been credited. The payer was Baylon, who was Nono’s brother, Lon.

Garen sighed as he recalled his brother Lon, who had to find work to support his brother’s living expenses in the academy. Frankly speaking, he was rather moved. Nonosiva’s academy life wasn’t considered luxurious but it was at least comfortable enough to not worry. At the same time, he enjoyed his peers’ respect and worship as he was able to pull out eight to nine thousand Universal Units, which was an unbelievable feat. On the other hand, his family members were very reluctant in buying any necessities and would eat the cheapest processed food available. It had been so bad to the point where his brother had to stop going to school and start working to support his living expenses.

He was able to recall his attitude towards his family members from his memories.

It was embarrassment, hatred and zero urge to return home.

He had been embarrassed that he had such a poor family and had even started to hate his family members. As compared to his peers, he didn’t dare to attend most of their gatherings as the expenses were ridiculously large. The same could be said for any outing as well as his training methods, which had been provided by the academy free of charge. Meanwhile, the majority of the students would purchase a training method that would best suit them from outside.

Under all sorts of comparisons between himself and his peers, he eventually resented his family members and wouldn’t contact them unless he needed money.

His family was also one of the reasons he was lonely in the academy. Hence he was good friends with only Aier and Mina. However, these two who lived in the academy didn’t know of Nono’s family’s situation.

“Don’t worry about it,” Garen explained. “I’ve found a way to earn money and train myself at the same time so you don’t have to worry about my living expenses anymore. It’s true.”

Rondo was still very skeptical over all of this.

Garen then used his terminal and credited two thousand Universal Units back to him.

“Take this money and the additional one thousand as my support to the family. Don’t let Lon work and send him back to school.”

Rondo was stunned, and his face in the terminal stopped reacting for a few moments. Nono, who had always been requesting money from the family, had decided to send money back to them?

“Nono… you… you’re not up to something bad are you…?”

“Of course not!” Garen replied with confidence. “Don’t worry about it. I really have found a job inside the academy that is able to give me a small sum of money and I can train myself at the same time.” he immediately sent another thousand back to his brother Lon.

He had earned tens of thousands of Universal Units from the battlenet alone and this money was just money from a few rounds of competition. Even the thousands of Universal Units that he’d credited to them had just been his bonus.

Even though he still needed money to buy the White Peacock Stone, he still planned to credit more back to the family.

“Don’t worry about it. I really don’t need you to credit me any more money,” Garen assured him once more.

Only then did Rondo start to believe his story.

“Don’t let your part-time job affect your studies,” seeing that his eldest son no longer required support from the family, he felt worried and much more relaxed at the same time, because he had budgeted the family’s expenses to the bare minimum in order to pay the Blackboard Academy’s expensive tuition fees and Nono’s huge monthly expenses. If he were to be able to save this amount of money, his family’s situation would be greatly improved.

“Alright I shall hang up first. Give Lon a call.”

“Alright. Take care of your health and study well,” Rondo started nagging.

“Understood.”

Garen hung up as he had already arrived the place where he’s supposed to meet. While he stood by the street and waited, he made a call to Baylon’s personal terminal.

It only beeped once before someone immediately answered the terminal.

“It’s Lon’s brother from the Blackboard Academy!” “Let me see! Let me see!” “His brother is in Blackboard Academy?! How amazing!” “My cousin brother is only from the Swordfish Academy and he threw himself out there every day.”

“Baylon, since your brother is from Blackboard Academy, when do you plan to introduce him to me?” a girl’s voice could be heard.

Baylon’s face was shown on the Terminal and he looked very proud as he looked at the Terminal. There seemed to be quite a few of people around him. There were youngsters of his age and even the voices of adults as well and it was quite noisy.

“Brother, why have you called?” his voice was very soft and he still gave off the timid vibe. “Also… Did you just send me some money…?”

Garen frowned slightly.

“Who permitted you to work outside? Go back immediately! Our home doesn’t lack that little money of yours,” his tone was very oppressing and this scared Baylon to the point that his face turned white.

“The money I’d sent you just now is from my part-time job. You need to go back and prepare to go to school now! Remember to bring the leave procedure with you!” since he had taken over Nono’s body, he decided to repay his parents in his place.

“But… but…” Baylon was so timid that his sentence was broken off by Garen before he could say anything.

“No buts. Go back to school now, we don’t need you to work just yet,” Garen said with a stern face. Baylon was only thirteen years old and was still in high school. If he were to stop studying now, it would be impossible for him to go back in the future.

Although Baylon was on the verge of crying, he was still chided by Garen who wanted him to go study once more. He didn’t expect Baylon to man up and fight back. Although it was just a small refute, Garen could see that Baylon liked to be around these workers and he really liked it there.

“If you don’t feel like leaving, then you should work a part-time job after class just like me,” Garen suggested. Seeing Baylon crying, he still insisted on him giving up his job. “If you need money in the future you can just tell me. I have quite an amount as of now. Don’t worry about it.”

“Oh.. okay..”

“Alright, I’m hanging up now,” with a click, the terminal was switched off. Garen raised his head and looked at the car owner uncle was currently walking towards him. Garen was standing at the blind spot of a small street with very little people around, and he seemed to not have realized Garen yet. As Garen was about to walk over and greet him, he suddenly sensed a faint sound and a gust of wind that was coming towards the back of his head.

Without any hesitation, Garen instantly turned around and by utilizing his powerful rotational force, he used his elbow to hit the person approaching from behind.

Boom!

He hit a student’s head, one who was also wearing the Blackboard Academy’s uniform. He had a black cloth in his hand and it seemed that he had been attempting to cover Garen’s head with it.

After being hit in the head, he took a few steps back dizzily and couldn’t even recover from it.

The other two men didn’t expect things to turn out like this and growled as they planned to attack him directly. Both of them threw a punch towards Garen’s head.

Garen gently moved to one side to allow the fists to pass through his original spot as he struck with his right knee. With a resounding thud, one person fell to the ground.

With his fist in the air, the other man started to sweat as he saw his friend fall to the ground.

“This guy is trained!” the guy who had just recovered shouted. “How…” Before he finished shouting, he felt a sensation in his stomach as he took five to six steps back and could no longer stand.

The last man stared at Garen as he sweated. He wasn’t sure if he should retreat or attack him.

“Who told you to ambush me?” Garen asked calmly. Although this body’s physical attributes were still weak, he could easily deal with these few fellows just based on his experiences in martial arts alone.

If one were to use all of his force during a fight, his momentum would be at its peak and he wouldn’t be able to change his attack afterward. While this provided enough power, one could easily find its flaw when it was avoided and the opponent could be easily dealt with afterwards.

“Ah!!” the last man shouted as he turned around and ran away. However, he didn’t manage to run too far off before Garen bent his knees and made him fall to the ground.

Garen grabbed their wrists, looked at their terminals and kicked them once more before leaving the area.

By then, a lot of bystanders had already gathered and even the car owner uncle looked at him in shock as he gulped and looked back at the three students.

“Ignore them. Let’s move to a new spot,” Garen gestured his hand.

“Alright.”

Chapter 789: Hint 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The deep green field spanned to the horizon. Black metal pieces and white rubble could be seen scattered everywhere. Some of these pieces and rubble were stabbed into the ground while some of them were laying by the bottom of the hill.

The evening red sunlight gleamed on a black metal piece which was about three meters tall from the west, casting a shadow on the small green field.

The sky was dyed red and layers of red clouds could be seen in the sky as well.

Between the layers of clouds, a black shuttle battleship slowly descended. Its hull, which spanned a few thousand meters, cast a huge shadow onto the ground.

The battleship looked like a torpedo ship. It was entirely black and had holes similar to that of a beehive. The wings at the back were slowly expanding as green flames spewed out from the bottom as a propellant.

Pew!

A humanoid Mech was ejected from one of the beehive-shaped holes. The Mech was black and both of its arms were heavy duty Pulse Guns while it had a shiny black circular shield on its back. Both of its shoulders had a red stripe on both sides. Overall, it looked like a firefighter.

After the humanoid Mech, which was about four meters tall, came out of the battleship, a group of similar Mechs flew out as well. From afar, they looked like a swarm of bees that had just left their hive as they flew down.

Among them was a slightly larger Mech. It landed gently on the largest stone and scanned the surroundings through the red beams shooting out from its mask.

“Keep the battle under thirty minutes. Be wary of our surroundings!” a young man’s voice came from within the Mech.

“Understood.”

The Mechs that had a Blackboard symbol on their backs started to spread out. Twenty of them started to search the area.

Blue flames burst out behind the Mech’s legs as it moved about the field.

After a while, a signal came from one of the Mechs.

“I’ve found something! There’s a hole here and someone is hiding inside! He’s severely injured.”

“It’s him?! How did this happen? Send him to back immediately!”

After a few minutes, a Mech dragged the dirty youngster back into the battleship and the remaining Mechs returned back to their respective beehive-like holes.

*************

Inside a dim small room.

Garen gently opened up the big sack in front of him. Inside it was filled with White Peacock Stones of all sorts of size. He took one out and weighed it for a moment before placing it into another sack in his right hand.

The uncle sat in front of him as he watched Garen analyze the items quietly.

Garen took out the stones and weighed them one by one before placing them into the sack on the right. Garen’s expression was calm as he did so at a moderate pace.

Suddenly.

Garen held onto one of the stones tightly and frowned.

“This… isn’t the stone that I wanted, right?”

The car owner smiled as he immediately took away the stone from Garen’s hand, “I must have made some sort of mistake… Hehe.”

Garen scoffed as he continued to check the remaining stones.

In no time, Garen found a few more counterfeits. The car owner’s face turned worse over time as beads of sweat started to appear on his forehead.

“Have you mistaken it again? Why have you made so many mistakes?” Garen glared at him. “It seems like you’re not interested in trading with me.”

“I wouldn’t… It’s unavoidable to make such mistakes with so many stones… You’re looking at two hundred of them!” the car owner started to wipe away his sweat as he said so.

“There’s a total of two hundred and fifteen of them. I will take them all for one thousand five hundred,” Garen put away the last stone and offered calmly.

“What? A thousand five hundred?” the car owner was stunned. “Didn’t we agree on…”

“I didn’t agree that you were allowed to put in some fake ones,” Garen butted in.

“But a thousand five hundred for this many… These cost at least four thousand!” the car owner started to sweat even more.

“Four thousand?” Garen laughed. “You can sell all of them if you can find someone who’s willing to pay that much.” he casually leaned against the sofa as he looked at the car owner.

“Aren’t you breaking your promise?” The owner started to panic and stood up.

“Promise? I had planned to keep my word if you didn’t mix in some fake ones. You can’t blame me for lowering the price once you’d done so,” Garen’s expression was calm. “Furthermore, your items are worth at most five points each. My price is more than just good enough. I’m fine that you’re not willing to sell it to me because I can always find another merchant to buy from.”

The car owner calculated for a while and came to the conclusion that he would be selling each at 7 points for one thousand five hundred. He would still profit as his buying price was four points. It was just that he wouldn’t be earning as much as he expected. Just as what the opposing party said, no one would be willing to buy such a huge quantity except for this student in front of him.

He gritted his teeth as he’d thought that the student in front was a black sheep of a rich family. He didn’t expect him to slash the price to the point where he wasn’t earning good money from this trade.

This guy was good…

He looked up and stared at Garen, who was sitting firmly and seemed to be very confident as he wasn’t panicking at all. He was about to go rough on him but recalled that he had some martial arts experience. Furthermore, he was also a Blackboard Academy’s student…

This student was very smart as he didn’t slash the price to the point I would outright reject him. It would be reasonable to slash the price when a fake stone was discovered. He, a blackboard student, looked like he was tight on his money. Perhaps I could…

“I can sell you these for a thousand points,” the car owner was determined.

“Oh?” Garen was stunned as he didn’t expect the opponent would say so after being at a disadvantage. “What’s your condition?”

“I wish to team up with you,” the car owner sighed as he said softly. “You’re a student at the Blackboard Academy. With your social status, I wish to work with you to obtain some rather special intel from within the academy… It’s a win-win situation.”

“Intel? What kind of intel?” Garen was stunned as he didn’t expect the fellow in front of him would have such a motive.

“Intel of celebrity students inside the Blackboard Academy,” the car owner said seriously. “Frankly speaking, there’s practically no one inside the academy who lacks money. It took me a long time to find a suitable partner and I hope that we can try it out. You have to understand that every outsider is very curious about the situation inside the academy. Furthermore, we can raise the celebrity students’ reputations once we reveal their information. They would be able to obtain more power and this would be very beneficial to them.”

“A very good thought,” Garen nodded. “However, other people would’ve thought of it since you’re able to. Why do you think that there hasn’t been any leak for such a long time? Have you thought of this?” he smiled as he stood up while carrying the huge package that he had sifted through a while ago.

He then used his Watch Terminal and sent over a thousand Universal Units.

“Here’s the thousand points that you suggested. I have to go for now. Thanks”

The car owner was stunned by Garen’s words as he realized what he meant from the hint displayed on his Terminal. As Garen was about to exit the place, he immediately stood up.

“Hey! Can you tell me your name?”

“Nonosiva. I will find you once more when I need you.”

“I’m Kendall! What’s your number?!” the uncle quickly followed up with another question.

Garen looked at him and threw out a series of numbers. Although he was slightly dumb, he was able to make the right decision.

***********

After returning to the dorm, Garen immediately hung the do not disturb tag, pulled his curtains shut and started his training.

He switched on the light and poured all of the rocks onto a big piece of paper. Garen then took off his shirt and sat in front of the stones.

“With so many mixed grade White Peacock Stones, I should be able to break through the second level, right?” he was looking forward to it.

Technically speaking, he had yet to practice a pure Living Secret Technique. In the Totem World, his journey had been interrupted and he’d taken a stray path and learned the Evil Technique instead. In the Vampire world, his Living Secret Technique had always been capped at the first grade.

He didn’t expect that this world would have the precious ingredients that his Living Secret Technique required. Furthermore, it was treated as trash here and was completely worthless.

“This is the difference between this world and the rest…” Garen sighed emotionally as his mind immediately went into the records of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

The first five grades of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique were the foundations used to change his physical attributes. Only the final three tiers were considered the realm of mastering the basics. One could only enter the last three tiers after the seed of the Living Secret Technique had sprouted. With the practitioner’s physical condition as the foundation, it could produce a unique technique that would be considered the strongest for Nonosiva’s body. Hence, it was called the Derivative Level and he would be qualified for it once he had mastered the foundations.

“I wonder what will change when I enter the second tier,” Garen slowly shut his eyes and gently pressed onto the white stones in front of him with his hands.

Inside the room, a cold breeze started to flow out from his body as his skin started turning blue.

On the other hand, the stones in front of him which was in contact with his hands started to crumble into dust. Quietly, the stones turned into a pile of white dust and as more dust was formed, Garen’s hand turned even bluer than before.

The air inside the room turned cooler as cold winds kept revolving around Garen. A layer of ice started to form on the surface of the green cactus placed by the window.

As time passed.

Garen focused on the changes in his body.

At the moment the impure White Peacock Stones had been absorbed, he’d felt that the coolness in his body had gone into a frenzy as it kept pouring out from his hands and absorbing the pile of white stones.

A huge amount of viscous substance was absorbed into his body and was immediately swallowed by the cold blue lines. As the freezing lines kept swallowing the impurities, they became thicker, from the thickness of a hair to the thickness of a chopstick, and then the thickness of a finger.

These freezing lines kept circling within his body and a layer of frost formed from where ever it had traveled.

Chapter 790: Hint 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat on his knees. He felt that he was on the verge of turning into an ice sculpture, as the majority of his body had been covered by an extreme cold.

Crack…

Finally, the last impure White Peacock Stone turned into dust.

Countless icy blue lines on Garen’s palm, which couldn’t be seen with the naked eye, slowly melded into his palms.

He stared at the Skill Pane upon which he’d finally seen a change.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique of unknown origin. First grade learned, Second grade progress at 12%.’

The progress amount started to change.

The rate increased over time as his progression of 12% raised to 15% at an increasing rate.

16%… 18%… 22%… 30%… 45%… 69%… 92%… 100%!!

The moment it reached one hundred percent, Garen could clearly see the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s icon on the skill pane turn muddy for a while, and it looked totally different as it became clear again.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique of unknown origin. The second grade, Heart Reformation. The heart shall reform with the blood of the Hellfrost Peacock as the basis to enhance the overall quality of the body. Time required to reform: two months and fifteen days.’

‘Third grade’s progress is 24%.’

Garen looked at the changed icon with satisfaction as he recalled the reason he had been unable to upgrade the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. There were two requirements to enter the second grade. The first one was an extremely cold environment which was impossible, as even the cold storage wasn’t even cold enough to fulfill this requirement. Naturally, the second requirement was the White Peacock Stone.

Although he wasn’t able to fulfill the first requirement, he could absorb a large amount of White Peacock Stones, melting them in the process to forcefully simulate the unique environment. This was the reason why he had absorbed so many impure White Peacock Stones. Even so, it had only amounted to this little progress.

In comparison, these two hundred plus impure White Peacock Stones were equivalent to twenty plus pure White Peacock Stones. Garen only needed one to enter the second grade and the remaining had been used to simulate the extremely cold environment.

“It’s a success,” Garen clenched his fist as he felt the coldness around his body. The seed of the Living Secret Technique had absorbed the contents of the White Peacock Stones and had started to sprout inside his body.

“Two months and fifteen days should be the time required for the Hellfrost Peacock Technique to completely reshape the heart. I wonder what effect it will bring after a complete reformation?” Garen was very eager.

This was the traditional path the ancient Warlocks had taken.

He stood up and took another shower as his body was now covered in a layer of faint blue viscous fluid which gave off a faint stench. It was the body’s expelled impurity from when his body was going a transformation.

After bathing, he changed into a clean uniform before sweeping the impure White Peacock Stone dust into a bottle he had prepared earlier on. The dust completely filled the big bottle, which was as tall as a typical water bottle.

“These remains are high energy fuels and can be sold for money.”

Garen cleaned everything before resting on his bed, in which he dozed off into his dreams.

Beep… Beep…

His Watch Terminal started ringing, which woke him up from his sleep.

He raised his hand and looked at the Watch Terminal to find out that it was a call from Aier.

Garen pressed a button to allow her access.

Aier’s face appeared on the monitor.

“What are you doing, Nono? Took you a while to answer my call.”

“I was sleeping. What’s the matter?” Garen yawned since this body was but a commoner’s body. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s reformation would require time to do its job and it wasn’t something that could be hurried. The strain from the frost and the absorption of the White Peacock Stones had completely exhausted this body.

“Do you want to go and see Mina?” Aier softened her tone. “I’ve met his cousin sister today and I heard that something has been going on in Mina’s family, which was why we couldn’t see her on the battlenet.”

Garen recalled the female friend who had sat together with him, who had also kept visiting him when he was undergoing his surgery. She was considered one of Nonosiva’s two good friends.

“When do you want to go?”

“Tomorrow. The qualifier match officially starts the day after tomorrow, though you guys will definitely be summoned before the competition.”

“Alright.”

After confirming the time with Aier, Garen switched off the Terminal. He tried to call Mina but to no avail, hence he called Instructor Hamm to enquire the location and time for the qualifier match, along with the time and location to gather before the competition. After memorizing the details, he decided to adjust his current state.

“Should I try out if there’re any changes to my training method?”

After breaking through the second grade of Hellfrost Peacock Technique and changing his physical qualities, Garen guessed that it would have a positive effect on his Willpower training.

He sat on his knees on his bed sheet once more as he tried to enter his training method once more.

Unfortunately, there was no change and his progression was still as slow as a snail.

After spending half an hour, Garen got out of the training method. He then switched on his laptop and opened up the news station.

‘… Regarding the interview with the Royal Academy’s team lately, Maria Academy has sent out the first seat Suanna who holds the title of Zero Gun to welcome them. These two academies between districts have a very good relationship as they share the same view on many topics. They have also signed a technical exchange transaction document that spans across multiple districts. It’s still unsure if the cooperation between the Royal and Maria districts would put on some pressure on the alliance between Blackboard and Aurora…”

Garen looked at the news’ video. Within a luxurious golden flying ship, a few guys and golden-haired girls in black skintight bodysuits interacted with one another as they posed for the reporters’ pictures.

Maria Academy and Royal Academy were Blackboard’s neighboring districts’ powerful academies which held a lot of power. There were three major districts near Blackboard, and the ones that possessed the most lands were Royal District and Maria District. The smallest among the three was the Aurora District and there were also seven to eight small districts. With the strategy of befriending the distant and attacking the nearby districts, Blackboard Academy had allied with the Aurora district. This had obviously put pressure on the Royal and Maria District.

“Rumor has it that Maria and Royal Academy are different from Blackboard. They’re using the standard academy training regime, which is completely different from the survival of the fittest regime here,” Garen recalled the relevant information in his mind. According to the record, the Blackboard Academy was considered an irregular type. It was still fine for the typical students but it would be survival of the fittest for all of the elites. They would use the elimination method by throwing all the elite students into very dangerous missions to train them. The ones who survived would be considered the strongest elites.

On the other hand, the majority of the academies would act in a peaceful manner as their members would be imaged as protectors. There wasn’t much competition among the students as well. However, in comparison to Blackboard, it was much harder to be admitted into those Academies.

Garen changed the station.

The top of the monitor showed that this was the second station of Blackboard. The Blackboard District was very huge, so huge that it was a big as a few provinces on Earth. Hence, it was natural that they had multiple stations.

The second station was displaying some sort of recruitment advertisement. He changed the station once more to an entertainment channel where it was advertising a robot for homes, an intelligent flying car, a fully automated full body massage chair and even imported man-made adult dolls from the outer districts, which looked exactly like humans.

Garen went back to the news station.

After the local news, it showed the live footage of the chaos in a city. The female reporter, together with the cameraman, was squirming within the crowd.

‘The chaos features Sir Black Star Diofie who will be officially participating in the investigation. The Blackboard’s Foreign Ministry spokesman Kreis has officially announced that they would fight back as best as possible against this chaos. They will sweep all the terrorists that endanger the society’s order and the safety of the citizens off the map!’

The reporter squeezed herself through the crowd while reporting with difficulty.

Garen noticed that the reporter had mentioned a name.

“Black Star Diofie?” He knew this person. He was the Blackboard Academy’s strongest first seat, who possessed a powerful Mech which was called the Black Star. He once had an outstanding result during a battle outside the district. He had managed to take out thirty-five Special Mechs and six destroyer battleships, turning the tide of the war on his own.

One had to realize that the Mechs he faced weren’t normal Mechs. All of his opponents were elite pilots. It wasn’t something to be proud of when one destroyed thirty-five normal Mechs, but it was a different story as he’d taken out thirty-five elite pilots.

All pilots who were crowned elites were at the very least level two and the stronger ones were level three or even level four. The differences between skills were drastically far apart between levels.

As Garen listened to the news, he started to understand how the world around him worked.

Within the Mother Planet Federation, conflicts between districts increased every day and the war to conquer all would eventually happen. Hence, every academy was trying to nurture the strongest elites. The separation between districts could no longer be reversed and civil wars had been going on endlessly. If there was a ceasefire on this side, a war would occur on the other end. With the Light of the Sky’s System, which was floating in space, all nuclear weapons of mass destruction, radiation guns or strategic weapons had been disabled. However, small-scale conflicts were unavoidable.

As he gently pressed onto the computer’s monitor, Garen stared at the news without any expression. War occurred in this district and continued in the other. Many people had died or had been severely injured everywhere and the Blackboard District just had to increase the construction investment for the civilians.

Such was the current state of news, where their countries were peaceful and prosperous while the civilians from the outer districts couldn’t even afford a proper meal.

After that, it started to report on news regarding the outer planet district, where they were still trying to establish a connection with the other outer planet districts.

As the Mother Planet had fallen from within, all alliances had decided to isolate them and the communication between planets had been completely cut off. Tens of planets had turned into independent empires. It was fortunate that there were outer forces which tried to infiltrate them, or else the federation wouldn’t even have joint forces to fend off the outsiders.

The other neighboring countries that tried to infiltrate the Federation had lost all their battles against them, and they even had a few small planet countries taken by the Federation. It was unclear what standard had been used between the planets, but they would always work together to fend off their common enemies when crisis befell them.

The Galactic Alliance had waged a war against the Finites. It was so chaotic that they literally ignored the chaos on this part of the district.

If this continued, the first thing Garen had been reminded of was the state during the Three Kingdoms Period. It was the same as now, as the Princes had segregated their own lands. Some attacked, some defended and some formed alliances. There were also many feudal princes everywhere.

Chapter 791: Qualifier Match 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he was watching the news in his dorm, someone knocked on his door.

Garen switched off the tablet, stood up and opened the door.

Aier walked in with a rather angered look on her face.

“What happened to you?” Garen felt strange.

“It’s nothing. It’s just that I’ve got a clear picture of Mina’s condition back at home,” Aier closed the door as he sat down and poured himself a cup of water. “What were you doing? Why is there a strange medicine stench in the room?”

He frowned as he looked at the messy dorm. There were still papers left on the ground, which had previously been used to hold the stones a moment ago. There was still a little bit of remaining White Peacock Powder on it.

“Let me clean it up,” Garen rolled the papers on the ground and threw them into the dustbin. He then went to take a cloth and wiped the powder clean from the ground.

Aier watched Garen bustling about as he leaned onto the sofa and continued speaking.

“Mina’s family had failed their business investment and had lost a huge sum of money. They now owe a huge amount of debt.”

Garen recalled the girl who kept visiting him when he was admitted to the hospital. Although he didn’t have all of Nonosiva’s memories, he wouldn’t forget people who had treated him well. From his point of view, he could see that Mina was truly being friendly towards Nonosiva. There was no intention and she really just wanted to be friends.

“How much does it affect her?” he pondered for a while before asking.

Aier sighed as he was not surprised by Garen’s calm tone. Nonosiva had always been like this, quiet and introverted. For him to ask this much meant that he was very concerned with the topic at hand.

“It may affect her tuition fee next year.”

“Tuition fee…” Garen nodded. The Blackboard’s annual tuition fee was seventy thousand. It might not be a lot for the wealthy students but this amount was astronomical to the typical households. Seventy thousand was the entire income of a typical family for a year and there were many families who couldn’t even earn that much.

“I’ll think of something when I get back,” Aier stayed silent for a while before speaking once more.

“What idea can you come up with? Where’s Mina? What does she have to say about this?” Garen poured himself a cup of water, sat down and drank it.

“What else can she do? She plans to head out and work to earn her tuition fee for next year. There was another girl who was in the same situation as her. It was her junior and her family wasn’t well off as well and decided to work outside so that she could afford to study. The job was introduced by her junior.” Helplessness was written all over Aier’s face. “Before I came to your place, I’d visited her and she looked very tired and had lost a lot of weight.”

Garen nodded.

“Don’t get hasty with Mina’s situation. I may have some idea.”

“You? What idea can you have?” Aier’s voice was raised by a few octaves. “You yourself owe the professor at least a hundred thousand.”

As he noticed that Garen didn’t seem anxious in the least, he started to feel uneasy about the whole thing.

“You’re being impatient,” Garen shook his head. “Impatience won’t solve anything and will make everything worse.”

“Yes… I’ve lost myself…” Aier himself realized that he had lost his cool as he lowered his head and tone.

“It’s exactly because I’m a hundred thousand plus in debt that I have to think of a plan on my own…” Aier broke him off before Garen managed to finish speaking.

“Whatever. I’ll go home and tell my dad about it and hopefully he has some useful idea. You should take your time to rest.” Aier didn’t wish to speak further as he stood up. “I’ll go first.”

Garen watched as he stood up and slammed the door as he left. Afterward, he stood up, didn’t say a word and just sighed. There was currently social unrest as the state of the economy was heavily dependent on the policy of the government. With the policy being changed every now and then, this sort of scenario would surface every once in a while. This was the current state of the world where the people had no power and could do nothing but to stand around and be butchered.

**************

The Blackboard’s qualifier match was being held in the shadow underneath the huge battleship. This shade was Blackboard Academy’s safest place.

A silver circular light beamed down from the battleship above. From afar, it looked like a very fine silver gauze that could barely be seen. Inside the silver gauze was a huge circular arena that spanned thousands of meters in diameter.

The white arena had been segregated into a lot of divisions, and each division was surrounded by robots that constantly maintained a protective barrier. Teams from every faculty started to pour into the arena.

The teams walked in one by one as the cheers from the student spectators could be heard in all directions. There even were family members and students from other academies who came to witness the match. Cheers came in waves and there even were holograms of fireworks as well.

“The current teams that are entering the arena are the teams from year B2. The top three representatives are surprisingly all women and by comparison, there was only a male competitor who barely qualified. This year seems even more one-sided…”

The broadcast was filled with passion as it excitedly introduced each qualified teams.

Other than Garen who stood among the class C5 members, there also was Fervale and the second-ranked Sara who stood straight. Fervale, as the first ranker, stood slightly in front of her and these three didn’t stand out so much among the other outstanding contestants from other classes.

“Look at the class in front of us on the right,” Fervale suddenly whispered. Among the cheers from the crowd, his voice went directly into Garen and Sara’s ear through the communication device. “Be cautious of the black-haired woman in the middle.”

Garen and Sara’s gaze shifted towards where he’d mentioned and in the middle of the three-man team of that class, a black short-haired woman was patting a fragile looking fan with long pink hair on the shoulder as she talked to her. She seemed very relaxed and an unparalleled confidence could be seen through her gaze. Her hair was thorny and by her hand gestures, she seemed to be very bold and gave off a vibe of extreme confidence.

“That girl is Merseus, one of the top two in year C. I lost to her last year and didn’t last one minute against her,” although Fervale said this calmly, a glimpse of dissatisfaction could be seen in his gaze. However, no one really knew he was angry or sad as he didn’t express himself a lot.

“Merseus’ melee Control is at least Level Two and she is a very powerful opponent. Both of you are ranged shooters so be careful to not let her get close to you,” Fervale cautioned.

“Understood,” Sara and Garen nodded.

Garen had tested his combat capabilities without the Moonfang and he knew that he wasn’t even qualified for a level 1. With his actual skill, he could only run with the Mech but couldn’t evade any incoming attacks. Compared to the real elites, he was extremely weak.

His strengths were actual combat outside the Mech but he was a complete novice in the Mech. Although he had experience in controlling the Buddha Mother, this world seemed different as the spiritual control was totally different than of the Buddha Mother. In this world, Willpower seemed to be the will of every single cell and was related to the cells’ biofield.

Garen wondered if his Willpower would improve he increased his Living Secret Technique, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique to a certain level. However, the current him was still very weak.

With his current condition, his opponent, Merseus was considered a very powerful foe.

“Other than this person, there’s another person who is considered the strongest in our year C,” Fervale was telling them the situation inside the arena. His household held some incredible amount of power and he naturally had all these intel on the enemies. In order to raise his year’s overall rank, he decided to feed his team members the opponent’s information to slightly increase the chance of winning.

“His name is Bally Visalia, but everyone calls him Bally. He hasn’t arrived yet but that man is extremely powerful so you have to be extremely cautious against him!” Fervale started to look frightened even by just mentioning his name.

“Powerful?” Sara squinted her eyes. “How powerful is he?”

Fervale glanced at Sara, “Bally has a nickname called the Mech Grinder. At least half of his opponents have had eighty percent of their Mech’s body ground to dust with just his hands. His weapons are a pair of high-speed arc saws and have torn apart at least ten Mechs, killed three and heavily injured twelve people during the academy’s entrance exam.”

Huff…

Sara inhaled a mouthful of cold air. While the arc saw was incredibly powerful, it required a lot of energy as well. With two arc saws, a standard mech model could only last half a minute. This meant that the person who used this sort of weapon was either crazy or very confident with himself.

“Bally and Merseus…” Garen understood that he was determined to obtain the champion title during this competition. As a new student, he had his privileges where being the top three of a faculty would allow him to be admitted to the academy’s elite teams. He could also win a good amount of a hundred thousand Universal Unit as a reward or at least ten thousand Universal Units for placing in the top ten.

Rumor had it that one could even order a custom mech as a reward if one was placed first.

To have a personal Mech, especially the unique ones where it could be controlled by Willpower, was something very luxurious. Practically every Mech in this world was made with the biomechanical nuclear as the core, which could tap into a person’s Willpower. It was a very advanced technology.

Hence, even a Mech of the most basic model would cost at least a hundred thousands Universal Points.

Most importantly, the first placed would even be awarded a Mech Control Certificate. This certificate was as powerful as the other international certificates where one could legally own their own Mech, which was equivalent to a Pilot’s certificate.

What troubled Garen was that his Willpower was still too weak. Without the Moonfang, moving would be incredibly hard and the Moonfang was obviously not suited for a drawn-out battle.

“I can only end the battle quickly,” he was very determined.

“Now let’s welcome the representatives of the class C5. Among year C, the most promising student and top five student is Fervale, the class’ first seat…” it was their turn to go into the arena. Fervale led the way while Garen and Sara followed behind. The trio wore a unique red competition uniform as they walked on the black carpet, entering the circular arena through the entrance. Students of the same class shouted from both sides and there even were people whistling endlessly.

Chapter 792: Qualifier Match 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At these times, the class would see everyone as their classmate. They would unite and cheer on the three with sincerity, and as the rank of the class increased, the students would be treated better. For example, with every increment in ranking, their tuition fee would be discounted by ten percent. Hence their ranking would affect their tuition fee. If they were ranked third, then they only had to pay for thirty percent of the original tuition fee. If they were ranked first, then they only had to fork out ten percent of the original tuition fee and also receive permission to use the privileged facilities in the academy. These unique facilities were only opened to the talented students and hence were used as a means to intensify the competition among the students.

The strong would become stronger and the weak would become mediocre if they didn’t put in more effort.

As Fervale walked on the aisle, he looked very calm and casual. On the other hand, Sara felt a little uncomfortable; after all this was her first time in this situation. As for Garen, he acted in such a way that he was slightly uncomfortable as this would suit his identity and family background.

Compared to the cheers towards Merseus, the three of them didn’t stand out and the only ones cheering were their classmates. The cheers could only heard from their back as they walked past.

The crowds on both sidelines were like boiling water as they started to release their negative emotions.

“Arello! Arello! Arello!”

“Bally! Bally! Bally!! Shred him!!”

Their supporters started cheering loudly.

The areas that spanned less than two hundred meters on both sides were spacious black fields, which was filled with students shouting everywhere.

Two teams walked on the black carpet.

The leader in front of the team in front of them was a muscular man with yellow spiky hair. He had a scar that propagated from his right lips as if someone had tried to slit open his mouth to the right and it looked rather brutal.

The team in the middle was lead by a blue-haired man who had a pair of silver earrings. With a faint smile on his face, he looked very seductive with his fit body, He too had a faint scar on the side of his face, giving off a wild vibe.

Fervale turned his head around and looked at his team members behind him.

“Caus Arello should be ranked number three in terms of strength for our year. He’s better than me and his strength is currently unknown. Rumor has it that he’s the strongest challenger against Bally. As one of the first seat that appeared out of nowhere, he basically has no reputation.”

He looked at the two of them by his side. Sara’s fear could be seen in her eyes and while Garen looked very calm, his fist was clenched ever so slightly, which was a sign of him losing his cool.

“Nono, you have to be careful. Arello is the brother of the trial member you’ve injured. He will most likely target you during the competition.”

Garen nodded without saying a word.

As the contestants entered the arena, they entered into their designated sections.

The whole arena was separated into sections by huge amounts of Source Mechs and the schedule of the match was decided by the previous ranking.

Garen and the other two were in class C5. After their previous class’ seniors were promoted to class B, they had left them the rank of thirteen, which was neither low nor high. However, only those who were in the top ten were able to enjoy the tuition fee reduction and special facilities.

There were a total of fifty-six classes in their year and it was undoubtedly difficult to be in the top ten while competing against these elites.

The sweet sounding female broadcaster started to arrange the schedule for all the elites.

All classes would be arranged according to their previous rankings during this qualifier match. Two teams would go against each other and the winner would proceed to the next match. This elimination process would continue until the final match.

After broadcasting the rules, while waiting for their opponents to arrive in the arena, each competitor was put under their respective coaches’ care and arrangement, who escorted them before the competition started.

Instructor Hamm stood together with the Mech battle class’s teacher Wesson as they talked to the three of them one last time. They were standing by the wall that separated the arena into a square box. Instructor Hamm didn’t seem to be fazed by the loud noises and staff walking past them as he patted Fervale’s shoulder firmly.

“Fervale. Remember your key moment! Your attack is smooth enough but as a melee Mech, the only thing you have to take note of is to get close to them. Since your marksmanship isn’t bad as well, I suggest you can fight in both close and long range so that you can fully utilize your advantages. If needed, you can throw the gun away and focus on melee combat.”

Fervale nodded.

“I understand.”

Hamms softened his grip and turned to Sara.

“Sara, you’re best at shooting a moving target while moving. You will be fine as long as you do this. I know you couldn’t utilize your full strength during the trial, but I hope you can give it your all now as this isn’t just for the class, it’s for you yourself!”

“I understand,” Sara nodded her head as she tried to calm herself down.

“Lastly, Nono,” Instructor Hamm stood in front of Garen. “I know that your body hasn’t fully recovered yet and you’re not at your best. Don’t feel burdened by this. You have a lot of potential and you’re as good as Sara when it comes to shooting. Perhaps you can fight in a style similar to hers.”

“I understand, Instructor,” Garen nodded as well to show that he was prepared.

“Come have a drink!” the nutritionist behind Instructor Hamm came forward as he passed the nutritional drinks to them. He then pulled Fervale, who was about to drink the water to a side as he personally coached him. It was very obvious that he had placed all hopes onto Fervale.

Garen and Sara then sat quietly in their seats as they waited for their schedule to be broadcasted.

Soon the schedule was released.

“Class C6 will fight against class C5. the opponents will be chosen freely and the time of the competition is…”

Soon it was their time to fight. While the schedule was slightly delayed, C5 was still a class that ranked at the front.

After finishing the schedule announcement, the first match had officially begun.

A lot of huge monitors appeared in front of the crowd, which were at least ten meters tall. They were placed in all directions so that the spectators knew of the situation inside. What was shown on the screen were the minute details of the situation and the scene within the arena. Everything could be clearly seen as the protective barrier was transparent.

The whole setting was similar to the ancient Colosseum as the nobles, students, instructors, and even family members shouted passionately. As if it was a concert, some people had even created huge banners with some students’ names on them.

Bam!

The first gunshot was fired and the battle had begun.

Suddenly, the whole arena was filled with excitement as countless pink light effect petals slowly descended. A levitating metal stage, which was the referee’s seat, was placed underneath the battleship. There were dozens of referees and they were all designated to their respective battles.

The first match of the students had officially begun.

Garen listened quietly to the loud cheers which came in waves as he looked at the two black and white Mechs on the big screen.

“Every Mech is the same and the only difference between them is their colors,” Sara, who was sitting beside Garen whispered.

“Now that we know who our opponents are. What plans do you have to fight against Class C6?” she seemed rather anxious as she tried to find a topic to talk about.

“There’s none,” Garen shook his head. “We just need to perform as usual.” What he said was the truth. Although his Willpower was much stronger as compared to the original Nonosiva, his strength was dramatically reduced without the Moonfang.

The most important thing to him for this qualifier match was the hefty monetary reward and the qualification to be enlisted as an elite student, which was the ticket for him to enter the core of the academy. Once he had enter successfully, he would be able to know the academy’s true strength.

Furthermore, he wouldn’t be able to obtain upper-level training methods without being a part of the strong ones. As a precaution, the highest training method that could be bought in the market was only level 3. One would require solid backgrounds to obtain a level 4 training method, which could only be bought by the military. This meant that this world’s strongest power was monopolized by the strong ones.

“If we can be ranked in the top three individually, then we will be able to be of great help to Mina by reducing the tuition fee and I would be able to repay Instructor Hamm for paying my surgical fee,” deep down, Garen understood. “In addition, I will be able to become an elite student by placing in the top three. I will gain support from the academy’s higher-ups and become a disciple of a professor inside the academy. My social status will definitely change instantly and my family’s condition will improve greatly. Rumor has it that the family members of the elite students are so well taken care of that they get to enjoy a huge bonus annually. In addition, they would definitely become a Field Level Officer if they were to enroll in the military. According to the Blackboard’s arrangement, the elite’s family members will be continued to be taken care of even if the elites have passed away.”

Everyone who lived in Blackboard district would want this kind of valuable resources.

However, Blackboard was very strict towards this as they would choose their candidate through an elimination process. They even had a system to calculate the mortality rate of the elite students and at the same time, there was absolutely no loophole for favoritism and fraud.

During the past few days, Garen had done his research on the family background of the student that he’d injured. They’d bought out all the faculty instructors and a few general instructors to dismiss the application for surgical expenses at the regular meeting. One of the instructor’s identity was an elite student alumnus.

Boom!

Suddenly a huge explosion forced Garen back into his senses.

The victor was already announced between the battles of two Mechs in the huge screen as the Black Mech raised up his Long Rifle and bowed in all directions.

The other white Mech was lying on the ground as smoke oozed out from its body. The pilot was dragged out of the Mech by the personnel and placed onto the rescuing machine as it sent him away. His condition was unknown.

The screen then clearly gave out a headline, detailing the condition of the injured.

Broken bones on both legs, a hole pierced through the abdomen and a portion of the intestines were plunged out. His head was drenched in blood and was currently in a coma. No one knew if he’s dead or alive and he looked seriously injured. Perhaps his life would be in danger if he wasn’t treated properly.

The students who didn’t study in Blackboard gasped as if they’d seen the cruel side of the Blackboard Academy.

Garen understood well that it wouldn’t be weird to have a few dozens heavily injured elites when thousands of elites were participating in the competition. Afterall, there even were injury incidents from the other academies. The Academy believed that one could only release their true potential when they were placed in a life-threatening condition.

Chapter 793: Qualifier Match 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The matches began one after the other.

The highlights of the many competition areas kept flashing past the large screens, and at the same time, above the entire arena, there was a white anti-gravity warship. There were countless statistics about the wins and losses in the many arenas on the ship, as well as the scores between the different streams and classes, and the way the matches were going.

Garen watched the arena in front of him for a while, but it was not that interesting. They were all very standard shooting, or textbook examples of fighting. Although it looked very smooth, they were not actually very strong in true battle.

He glanced at the stats projected on the suspended screen.

‘Bally: 1 win. Merseus: 1 win.’

This meant that both of them had already completed their battle. To be able to finish off their opponent in such a short time showed just how strong the two of them were.

The time passed by slowly, and finally, the announcer’s voice reached them.

‘Fervale from C5 vs. Carrie from C6.’

Beside him, Fervale stood up. As Instructor Hamm encouraged him on, he walked straight towards the entrance to the arena that had automatically opened up behind him.

Not far away, their classmates sitting in the audience stands all got up and looked their way. Mina and Aier were also among them, looking at Garen, but when they saw that he was still sitting in place with no intention to move, they sat back down as well.

Amidst the chaotic arena surroundings, they could only vaguely hear their classmates’ cries of encouragement. That little bit of motivation was drowned out by the other sounds.

Garen sat quietly in his seat, one of his aims was to obtain top three in the qualifier match. If he wanted to get the true high-level training methods for free, he had to join the academy’s elite squad. He knew this world very well now, the way to the top was held in the hands of those in power. If he wanted to obtain information about the power system here, the best way was to join a faction with sturdy influence and roots.

He heard the voices rising and falling around him, there was the commotion in the distance, and the surprised cries nearby.

Garen’s heart was completely calm. According to Instructor Hamm’s intel, if all went as expected, the top three this year would end up being a race between Bally, Caus Arello, and Merseus.

***************

“I think our Grade C has the competition in the bag this time. Bally, Caus, and Merseus, these three should be the main candidates for first place. The competition is actually just a match between the few of them,” a young man sitting on Grade C’s seat at the adjudicators’ table said with a laugh.

On his right, a woman with red eyes and a ponytail looked down at the match below. The woman wore a Digital Monocle over her eye, with large amounts of statistics and information flashing across it. When she heard that, the woman pressed the lens and straightened up.

“Teacher probably made us come this time so that we could observe Merseus and Caus, to see which one of them was better suited to join us. Although they’re about the same in skill, their family backgrounds and personalities require a certain degree of deliberation as well.”

“Actually, some of the other candidates are pretty decent too, but the only ones whose overall abilities reach Level 2 are just the three of them. Even if the other excelling students have parts where they’ve reached Level 2, that would still only be for a subject or two, their overall power would not have reached a fundamental shift yet,” the man said, observing the other matches casually.

“But we can’t say that for sure either, what if there’s a black horse somewhere? Look, Verna and the others are also looking at the students this time, I bet they’re aiming for that Bally.” The woman’s gaze moved to another side.

There was a bearded man dressed in white, who was cleaning his teeth with a toothpick as he nonchalantly read the suspended display board.

The man glanced at them, and twisted his mouth.

“That guy’s a wild animal, he hasn’t given up since you beat him up last time. All he does every day is fight, how much of the academy’s resources has he used up on Mech repairs alone?”

“Exactly, if only everyone was like Angecena.” The red-eyed woman nodded slightly.

“What, you mean if they were all traumatized by you like he was?” The man gave the woman an odd look.

Not far away, at the adjudicators’ table on the other side.

Verna noticed that the two of them were looking his way.

“It’s that woman!” His expression grew rigid. “That crazy bitch is here too…”

“One of the three Level 4 Elites, Red-Eyed Medero. In the internal battles, many of her opponents sustained permanent disabilities thanks to her, and she has several tens of thousands of people’s worth of blood on her hands. She looks like an inconspicuous female student, but she’s a terrifying executioner who’s even more violent and bloodthirsty than our group,” a bespectacled male student said from behind Verna.

“That’s the woman that even First Seat Black Star once said stands the highest chance of inheriting the title of Black Star next.” When Verna saw that woman’s gaze move over to him, he felt as though someone had poured ice down his back. But in order to protect his male ego, he had no choice but to act wild and reckless, completely fearless. And he also took a toothpick out to clean his teeth…

“Be careful, in Medero’s faction, her teacher Simis is the vice principal. They’re one of the academy’s three main factions and have deep-rooted power. Recently, their influence in the school has been expanding, Vice Principal Simis seems like she might be planning to fight for the position of principal. The principal is getting on in the years now, there’s a high chance that their faction can win it,” the bespectacled boy reminded him softly.

Verna accidentally stuck the toothpick into his gum, and the pain made him sweat profusely, but still he maintained his tough-guy act. Sensing that the red-eyed monster over there was still looking at him, his heart began to bleed…

“Those monsters come here every year to grab the fresh blood, but you were just unlucky that you happened to bump into Red Eyes, who you offended before.” The bespectacled boy had also noticed that Verna’s mouth was bleeding, and he instantly looked sympathetic.

“As expected of Verna, you’re hard on others, but even harder on yourself. The toothpick drew blood, and you’re still completely impassive.” In the distance, Red-Eyed Medero looked impressed. “Back then, I let him go precisely because I admired this tough-guy style of his, our academy needs more hard-headed people who fight to the bitter end.”

The man beside her instantly looked at her strangely.

****************

“Nonosiva from C5 vs. Bankar from C6.”

Before the match, Garen stood up, watching Fervale walk down with a calm expression. His opponent from the previous match was the other side’s First Seat, the First Seats always fought each other, that was the academy’s unspoken rule.

The other guy did not cause him much trouble, both were experts in high-speed movements, and they collided after zipping around for a bit.

Fervale’s specialty was close-distance combat, so without using up too much energy, he used some of his basic sword techniques. From amidst the cold light, there was a shot of white light, as he had also managed to secretly prepare his Laser Cannon in the middle of the high-speed combat. That one shot landed on the opponent’s cockpit. The C6 students from last year were very impressive, and managed to get very high positions, but the freshmen this year were nowhere near as capable. Their First Seat could fight with fluid movements, but that was the extent of it.

After winning with relative ease and getting off the stage, Fervale patted Garen’s shoulder.

“Be slightly more careful, and you can win.”

“Got it.” Garen nodded, and walked towards the tunnel entrance behind him. As per usual, Hamm hugged him and instructed him softly, telling him not to panic no matter what, and what he should do.

“Nono! Good luck!!” He looked at the stage, and suddenly heard two voices. They were barely noticeable amidst the many cheers of the crowd, but Garen could still tell instantly that they were Aier and Mina.

He turned around, and waved at the two of them.

“Go! Cream ’em!”

Instructor Hamm pushed Garen lightly with a smile.

Garen gestured ‘ok’ behind him, and quickly entered the tunnel.

He wanted to use this Qualifier Match to test himself, just how far could his power when he merged his battle awareness with the Moon Fang.

Walking into the tunnel and into the Mech Room, he saw several pillars of white light shoot out from the inside, hitting the surface of the Mech.

This was a white humanoid Mech, it had square pieces of armor on its shoulders, and also two armguards on its arms and forearms. There was a spike like a fang coming from its chin over its shoulder, and like a cicada, the spike kept curving downwards and extending to his crotch. It seemed to be there as a protection system to help out with defense.

“This is one of the academy’s standard issue Mechs. A standard Level 1 Mech.” Garen looked at the humanoid Mech, five meters tall, with satisfaction.

Beep-beep. Beep-beep.

The reminder message beeped. He did not delay any longer and got onto the elevator. Rising with a whirr, he jumped out and into the open cockpit at the Mech’s chest.

Smack smack smack!

There were several sounds as the lighted control panel was powered on. He put on his helmet, and looking at the 360 degree view in front of him, the surround control system lit up with many small green LED lights and spinning model screens.

“Blackboard Model 1 Mech, activating…”

A deep digital voice spoke.

“Stat Mod, running…”

“Weapons System, running…”

“Power System, warming up…”

“All systems, final check.”

Garen put both hands onto the control panel, and placed the Moon Fang on the edge of the panel to his right, taking a deep breath.

“C534, Nonosiva, take off!!”

Psst!!

The huge Mecha abruptly shot out, flying out with a trail of blue flames coming from its back. It followed the pitch-black Launch Tunnel out into the outside world, like a white bird spreading its wings.

*******************

Kar slid out of the launch tunnel lightly, landing on the arena’s alloy floor and finding his footing. The Mech’s padded feet muted his footsteps on the floor.

The pitch-black humanoid Mech held two pitch-black short swords in its hands. Using his family’s special short sword fighting techniques, Kar could beat all the others and stand here as a representative of his class, facing the other classes. This was already a symbol of his strength, or so it seemed to him.

Listening to the rise and fall of the cheers and angry shouts outside, Kar felt as though that was the glory that rose up for his sake.

“Standing in an arena like this sure gets the blood boiling…”

He felt slightly self-intoxicated, felt his body begin to burn slowly from top to bottom. His condition was unprecedentedly good, and he was already one of those rare competitive fighters, the more high-pressure a situation was, the better his condition would be.

Soon enough, the opposite arena wall opened up automatically to reveal a tunnel, and his opponent’s Mech also slid out lightly, landing steadily. The opponent had chosen two Laser Cannons that had come with the Mech, the pitch-black barrels as large as a bowl. With one long and slender white cannon on each side, it did look somewhat gruesome.

“Let the match begin!” the mechanical voice spoke.

“Heh!” Kar activated his Mech abruptly. His overall power was Middle Level 1, so he rushed straight at the opponent, his Mech moving along a somewhat difficult S-shaped path.

But he had barely gone a hundred meters out when the opposing cannon barrels suddenly lit up with two beams of white light. Kar felt his scalp go numb, the two white light cannons were aimed at exactly the place where he would land.

“How is that possible!!?”

Brr!!

Two lasers precisely hit the same spot, the black Mech’s cockpit, with an eerie sound, and blew through the Mech’s defensive armor in almost an instant.

Bam!

The black Mech exploded, and the safety system shot Kar out just in time. He flew out high, and was intercepted by the medical robots around the arena.

Chapter 794: Qualifier Match 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kar’s disbelieving face was still lingering in the rescue cabin.

He had no idea how he lost, but the battle was already over.

“Battle complete, time taken, five seconds. Winner, C534 Nonosiva,” the mechanical voice announced directly.

The white Mech Garen was controlling stood on the spot, not moving an inch, the two Laser Cannons on either side of it smoking slightly from the barrel.

Sitting inside the Mecha, he was completely calm.

He glanced at the Moonfang beside him, it was not really stirring. It had just flashed with a little white light just now, but now it was completely quiet again.

“Try to reduce piloting and battle times as much as possible, settle it quickly.” This was Garen’s plan.

In the first match, Kar was given an instant KO.

This shooting technique that concentrated the two Laser Cannon shots in one split second was wholly reliant on Garen’s powerful battle experience and his piloting precision. Using the Moonfang’s control as the main element, he tweaked it slightly, and achieved such a powerful offensive effect.

This instantaneous battle also attracted many gazes straight away.

***************

Beside the arena

“The rascal! To think he has such a trick up his sleeve.” Instructor Hamm could not keep the smile off his face. “Twin Laser Cannon Concentrated Fire, this is a Level 2 Laserfire Control technique, at the very least! I never thought that he would reveal such a hand out of nowhere like that. And he fired while his opponent was moving so quickly, too.”

Fervale’s expression was solemn as well.

“Very impressive, even I would have a hard time against that hit.”

“His combined powers are already approaching Level 2, just with that alone,” Sara could not help but say with envy. “Given that it wasn’t just a coincidence.”

Nonosiva had always been quiet, and was unknown in his class. No one would have expected him to have such a powerful skill.

“Shouldn’t we be happier the stronger he is?” Hamm laughed out loud, and patted their shoulders. “Go on and prepare for the next round.”

In the audience stands

Enviously, Aier looked at Garen’s Mech, standing in the arena after having killed his opponent in an instant.

“That guy’s actually this strong? How come I never knew?”

Mina’s mood was improving for once. Although her face was still somewhat pale, she was still genuinely happy for her friend’s win.

“This is the first time the freshmen are showing off their true power in battle, and this was his progress so far this year. Who knows, he might actually be able to get that tuition fee exemption. Nono had been exceptional ever since he took the entrance exam, it’s perfectly normal for him to have improved like that.

She was also very tempted by the tuition fee exemption, after all, that would save her a large amount of money. Right now, her family had practically stopped paying for her tuition fees altogether, her father was deep in debt and on the run, while her mother drowned herself in her tears all day long. It was hard for them to even live, they relied on her to work part-time every day and bring back just enough money to make ends meet.

When Aier heard that, his expression turned guilty.

“I misjudged him. Later I’ll apologize to him properly.

They lost two out of three matches, so Class C6 gave up and entered the loser match-ups.

In the second round, they fought against Class C8. Just like in the first round, Fervale finished off his opponents easily. He seemed to have been triggered by Garen, so he just rushed up and immediately hacked around, his sword unnaturally swift, fierce, and precise. Within a few strokes, he had already chopped the opponent’s First Seat into sticks, and victory was his.

As for Garen, he still used the same Twin Barrel Concentrated Fire, but this time the first Concentrated Fire missed because they were too far apart. His opponent nearly closed the distance, but the second hit still landed at close distance, and the result was the same as the first match. His opponent was frustrated that they could not use any of their moves at all, other than running, they could not show off any other skills before their cockpit was insta-killed. The opponent that came down was a pretty little girl, who fell face-first into the female instructor’s arms and cried her eyes out.

When Garen walked out of the Mech tunnel, he was still as expressionless as ever. The Moonfang could control the Laser Cannon Fire easily, but the Concentrated Fire skill was a product of his own refinement. If it weren’t for the fact that performing too excellently would seem unnatural, he would have finished off his opponent with the very first shot.

The third round, the fourth, the fifth…

The matches went on and on, but Garen barely used any energy at all.

And he had also figured out the rhythm of the Moonfang’s usage, if he was just using it normally, for a duration of fewer than fifteen minutes, there would be no problem. And once he approached the fifteen-minute limit, it would grow hotter and hotter. This thing seemed to be the core component of some high-level instrument.

As the matches continued on, the opposing classes of the same level also began to understand Garen better.

He faced several opponents consecutively, but not once did he shoot more than three times. He would always finish off his opponent within the first or second shot, even the First Seat of C5, Fervale’s performance was outshone by his.

After defeating more than ten battles in a row, Class C5 was solidly placed in eighth place. If Sara had not lost a few matches, they would be unbeaten now.

And Garen, after beating several opponents in a row, finally met an opponent that could not be defeated in one hit that afternoon.

‘C534 Nonosiva vs C1153 Cassardin.’

The mechanical voice spoke.

When the voice spoke, be it Garen or Fervale, their hearts both gave a little jolt.

“No, wait! Cassardin is Class Eleven’s First Seat! Why would they have the First Seat placed third!” Instructor Hamm started yelling, getting out of his seat abruptly.

Beside him, Fervale gripped his fist tightly, lowering his head slightly.

“Isn’t your First Seat Nonosiva, who’s been hiding in third place?” a sarcastic voice said from beside them. It was a young man with a thin face, looking at Instructor Hamm with arms crossed in front of his chest and a cold gaze.

When he heard that, Fervale’s head went even lower.

On the other hand, Garen sat quietly by the side, leaning on the wall, closing his eyes for a breather.

“Besides, it’s just an unspoken rule in the academy for the First Seats to face each other, it’s not compulsory. It’s up to me how I want to arrange it,” the thin-faced instructor said calmly.

“Pillbo!” Hamm glared at him angrily. “What are you thinking!?”

“What am I thinking? Hehe…”

The thin-faced instructor, Pillbo, gave a low laugh.

“I’m warning you! Don’t mess around!” Hamm yelled loudly.

“Warning me? Hah!” Pillbo laughed coldly. “You’re as naive as ever, Hamm.”

“Nono’s overall level is close to Level 2, he might not necessarily lose even when fighting the opponent’s First Seat,” Fervale interrupted suddenly.

The First Seat had to be at least Upper Level 1. Fervale seemed to be having a harder time winning sometimes, and it was not always as clear-cut as Garen’s matches, but that was also because his opponents were stronger. And Garen had always been fighting their second or third seats.

This time, however, he was facing the First Seat. Now, this would really be troublesome.

Hamm hesitated.

“No problem, I can handle this,” Garen replied calmly, opening his eyes.

He had always been facing garbage opponents, so he wanted to really fight once as well, to test just how strong he really was. Otherwise, there was no point in him fighting nothing but trash that died in one hit, no matter how many shots he had to fire.

“Be careful! That Pillbo is really heartless and cruel…” Hamm looked at Garen worriedly.

“It’ll be fine.”

The mechanical announcements began again.

Garen stood up, this time he was fighting as the First Seat. Once the match-up was announced, the audience on this side of the arena all started watching.

For a First Seat to face a Third Seat, there was nothing to say except that Garen’s earlier performance was extremely eye-catching. The match-up this time garnered a lot of attention as well. Slowly, as more and more classes got eliminated, the audiences behind these classes began to shift their attention to the opponents who had defeated their classes, hoping a new opponent would appear to take them down.

‘C534 Nonosiva vs C1153 Cassardin. Let the battle begin.’

Garen sat in the cockpit, looking at the black Mech opposite him carefully. It was used Twin Pistols, just like his previous Weapons System.

Before the starting call even faded, his opponent had already darted out with a whoosh, not to approach him, but instead moving at high-speeds to the right.

It was a very strange movement, they would pause occasionally, and sometimes take a small leap back. It seemed rather floaty and completely irregular.

Brr!

Garen’s Twin Cannons fired simultaneously again, the shot ringing out abruptly, aimed straight for the black Mech’s head control system. And then… for the first time, he missed. The black Mech tilted its head slightly, and the shot just brushed past, without causing any damage whatsoever.

“Eh?” Garen’s heart grew serious, he had definitely felt 90% confident in that shot, it definitely had a high accuracy rate. But somehow it had missed.

The opponent was still constantly moving irregularly, and two gunshots shot out with a whooshing sound, but Garen dodged those as well.

Compared to his moving techniques, the opponent’s shooting techniques were easily seen through by Garen.

“Should I try again? Is it a coincidence?” Garen pressed down the uncertainty in his heart.

Ka-chak, the twin barrels moved slightly, and a white light rose in the barrels slowly.

Brr!!

Two rays of white light drew out two white paths, shooting straight for the opponent’s body like a bolt of straight lightning.

And then… they missed again.

The lasers bunched into one, and shot past from under the black Mech’s hips and crotch, hitting the protective barrier behind it. It caused a series of ripples and then vanished.

“It’s not a coincidence…” Garen’s heart gave a jolt, and he watched the opponent’s steps carefully. “These steps…”

****************

“These steps… Gehrs Dance Steps… It’s the Gehrs family’s Level 2 avoidance steps…” a solemn-looking middle-aged woman said softly in the audience, looking down at the arena from among the seats for external family members who were here to watch. “To think that young Gehrs from the Gehrs family has such an ability.”

“As expected of a First Seat, every First Seat has Upper Level 1 power, even the weakest ones would have one or two aspects that have reached Level 2,” a white-haired old man beside her said while nodding. “We did right in coming to Blackboard this time, to think we could even witness these Dance Steps in such a low-level competition.” His expression was nostalgic. “I remember back then, Gehrs Zeno had used these steps to defeat the twelve elites from the East. These Level 2 steps are merely the rudimentary basics.”

“That is true, it’s already very impressive for young Gehrs to have such power at this age.” The woman nodded. “But his opponent is a pretty good choice as well, I saw the replays of the match just now, he’s very good at controlling the Laser Cannon fire, and his grasp of timing is not something just anyone could do.”

Chapter 795: Battle Situation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stared at the Mech opposite him quietly. The Panoramic Mirror allowed him to see how the opponent kept moving in an irregular rhythm. These waves were completely arrhythmic, to the point where it seemed that his opponent could barely control this rhythm themselves. It was a very strange feeling.

“So these are this world’s medium-high Mech techniques, huh? They are indeed unique.” He observed his opponent’s movements carefully, as for the occasional laser attack, it was completely useless. He just needed to turn lightly to dodge them easily.

“One more time.”

Garen tried to raise his hand.

Brr-brr!

Two Laser Cannons shot at his opponent, one after the other, drawing out two long white lines.

He did not concentrate their power this time, and had instead fired off the two shots separately. The black Mech opposite was immediately slightly flustered, it used those strange steps to avoid the first shot, but could not completely avoid the second shot. The shot grazed its waist pretty badly, and wafts of green smoke began to rise from it.

Garen glanced at the time. Even including his observation time, it had only been eight minutes, so there was still a long time until the Moonfang’s limit.

Brr-brr! He fired off two more consecutive lasers, each locking down one of the two sides that the black Mech had to move in. This time, Garen put more precision into his aim, the first shot hitting the opponent’s right leg, while the second ones brushed past the black Mech’s waist again.

He could vaguely hear that person’s cursing from opposite him.

“So this is the power of a First Seat?” Garen provoked his opponent unhesitatingly, his voice transmitted through the Mech’s external speakers. “Or are you saying you’re the weakest of the First Seats?”

“Don’t get cocky!” a furious voice said from inside the black Mech.

Brr!

This time the two lasers were concentrated into one, shooting straight for the enemy.

But the black Mech actually did a strange twist, and those eerie steps appeared again, allowing it to somehow dodge the Laser Cannon shot that was as thick as an arm. At the same time he also raised his arm to fire back two shots, even while performing those strange steps, his firing technique nearly hit Garen as he tried to avoid it.

Garen was slightly surprised as well.

“I can’t properly predict how the opponent is moving, so it’s harder for me to avoid him as well?” It was his first time encountering such a thing since he began training his secret techniques.

Actually, his martial arts style had always been fearless. He did not really emphasize avoiding, and was more likely to just bulldoze over his opponents with overwhelming power, completely obliterating his enemy. For something like this to happen, where he could not avoid his opponent properly, was undeniably a fresh new thing for him. This way was not very similar to how he used to fight, and he could also tell from the opponent’s Dance Steps that these techniques of his opponent’s were definitely more than just that, they seemed to be the basic version of an even higher-level fighting technique.

“Interesting. But I should still end it quickly, no matter how strong your dodging is, you still need to have the capability to use it.” Garen never wasted time, so he shot two more separate lasers at his opponent. The black Mech was grazed in the arm and the thigh again.

Every time he shot separately like this, Garen was basically standing still on the spot, but with every shot, he would merely twist slightly to avoid the opponent’s attacks.

Because the more places the black Mech got damaged, the quicker its degree of mobility decreased. His strange Dance Steps seemed to require a lot out of his mobility, and once that decreased, his avoiding skill deteriorated drastically as well.

“It’s over.”

Looking at the stage, that white-haired old man spoke softly.

“The Gehrs Dance Steps may be impressive, but young Gehrs is still not strong enough to unleash its full potential. These Dance Steps are based on irregular Willpower waves, and automatically tend to choose the best means of escape to avoid any threats. It can only unleash its full power at the Upper Levels高级.”

“But it’s already impressive that he can achieve this much at this age,” the stern-looking woman said with a nod beside him.

Suddenly there was a loud cry of surprise from the other arena, not from one or two people, but from several hundreds or even thousands of people at once. Many people abruptly got to their feet while looking at the stage, their mouths slightly open, as though they had seen something very surprising.

“That is…!” The white-haired old man moved his gaze away, and looked at the screen showing the Grade B arena on the other side. It was broadcasting the match from a special arena.

“The Spear of Victory!” The stern woman’s face had a rare expression of surprise. “Level 3 Willpower, Violent Heart’s final technique!! That Mech… could actually consecutively unleash it twice in an instant! What an unfathomable genius!”

“The Spear of Victory gathers a large amount of violent high-pressure electricity all around it, and it has a very powerful interference effect on Gaussian electromagnetic weapons as well as metallic weapons. In close combat, it could even drastically distort the opponent’s electric field and Willpower. It’s known as a super powerful killer move among close combat Mechs!” the old man said in a low voice. “For a Grade B, second-year university student to be able to reach the peak of Level 3 Willpower, and for them to be able to train the Violent Heart to the very peak, they must be a peak-level prodigy. Blackboard Academy, your reputation is not a lie.”

*************

In the Grade B match arena, two Mechs, one black and the other white, were currently facing off by moving at extremely high speeds. The black Mech was holding two extremely sharp and terrifying spears that sparkled with a great deal of blue electricity tightly in both hands. Countless bolts of electricity twined and crackled around the spears, to the point that the spears’ original material and color had been completely covered up, as though the two spears were made completely of electricity.

“Die! Gordo.” An icy cold male voice came from inside the black Mech.

“The Spear of Victory… only proves that your Willpower is strong enough! If you want me to die, you’ll have to make me!” A similarly icy woman’s voice came from the white Mech opposite him.

Clang!!

The two Mechs collided at high speeds, one holding spears while the other wielded a sword. The huge white sword slashed the electric spears mercilessly, and the friction between them emitted a piercing metallic screech. Instantly, the electricity began to shoot down the sword’s blade fiercely.

**************

Garen fired off two more shots, breaking off the black Mech’s two arms, while he heard the cries of surprising coming from outside at the same time. Instantly, he knew that something had happened outside, and distracted all of the audience’s attention.

But the black Mech was still being stubborn, he had no intention of giving in at all. His arms had been broken off, but he was still dashing at him at high speeds.

“How stubborn.” The two cannon barrels beside Garen lit up with white light again.

Clack…

Suddenly the white lights went out. Garen seemed to hear some tiny noises beside him.

“Hmm?”

He looked at the Moonfang on the counter abruptly, and saw that the Moonfang was twinkling continuously with a white light. It looked extremely unsteady.

He tried to move his Mech a little.

“Shit! I can’t move! What happened? It’s only been ten minutes!” Garen’s heart gave a jolt, and he knew he was in trouble. The whole Mech had somehow frozen completely.

Opposite the Panoramic Mirror, the black Mech was running at him madly. The Mech used the remaining half of its right arm to hold an alloy dagger to its body, the sharp tip of the dagger piercing straight for the middle of Garen’s cockpit.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

As the black Mech drew closer, its steps became heavier and heavier.

Garen was still trying to move the Mech with his Willpower. But not only was the Moonfang unable to help him control the Mech right now, it was even obstructing him, so much so that he could not even move the Mech however he tried.

“Damn it!” A sheen of sweat broke out on his brow, the black Mech in front of him was drawing closer.

Twenty meters! Ten meters! Five meters!! Three meters!! Two meters!!

“Move, damn it–!!!” Garen pushed his Willpower hard.

Whoom!!!

There was a loud, dull sound.

Everyone stared, wide-eyed and slack-mouthed. Instructor Hamm and Pillbo opposite him stared, wide-eyed and slack-mouthed. Even Fervale looked slightly surprised.

On the arena, the black Mech had collapsed into a pile in front of the white Mech. He had been tripped by a small crater in the ground that had been created by one of his own shots. The whole Mech fell to the ground, and there were many small bolts of lightning crawling all over the surface of the Mech. The black dagger also gave up, falling to one side. The whole Mech could no longer stand up, sprawled in front of the white Mech.

“Winner: Nonosiva.” The sweet mechanical voice spoke again.

Garen sat inside the cockpit, watching the white Moonfang’s white light blink continuously. He still could not control the Mech, evidently something had gone wrong with the Moonfang’s usage time again.

After the black Mech collapsed on its own and victory was decided, Garen still waited for more than a minute before he felt the white Moonfang recover again.

Sitting in his seat, he could not help but wonder at how close that was.

Under those circumstances just now, if his opponent really had pierced the cockpit, it was very likely that he would be seriously injured again, and he would have lost the match. With his body the level it was right now, it was not likely that he would be able to avoid that hit quickly, and the final result would likely be a loss for him, plus critical injuries so he would not be able to continue battling. If it came to that, forget the top three, he would not even make top ten.

When the two of them left the arena and came out, the instructor from the other side, Pillbo, left in a rage, whereas the pilot of the black Mech stared at Garen with a complicated gaze.

“Why didn’t you finish me off?” he asked coldly.

Garen looked at him and did not reply, leaving straight away to go to his class’s personal area.

That pilot was just a black-haired young man with an ambitious expression, but in the end, he merely stared at Garen’s back without saying a word.

Once he came back to the resting area, Instructor Hamm came right up and slapped Garen’s shoulder hard, his expression absolutely delighted.

“Great job! Who knew you’d improve this much!”

“It was all thanks to your teaching,” Garen replied with a laugh. But he was still sweating inwardly from that scare from just now.

He glanced at Fervale who was sitting at the side, expressionlessly. Fervale just sat there quietly, without uttering a word. He must still find it discomforting that his position as First Seat was taken away.

It was break time after that, so Garen made an excuse to go to the toilet, so that he could check the Moonfang in his hand.

The crack in the middle of the Moonfang was getting larger and larger, it looked like it was had grown by another half of its original size. Maybe that was the main reason why the Moonfang failed just now.

“Looks like I have no choice but to shorten my battle time further…” Garen decided in his heart. The Moonfang’s time limit as he tested it before was fifteen minutes, but evidently unexpected accidents might happen. In order to minimize such accidents, the best way would be to reduce his battle time as much as possible.

Chapter 796: Battle Situation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the following battles, Garen and Fervale continued to defeat their opponents instantly, and the matches slowly reached the middle stages. Most of the classes had been defeated, and soon there were only ten classes left, they advanced to the Winners Bracket.

And five stronger teams were decided in the Losers Bracket playoffs as well, so they had the right to challenge opponents in the Winners Bracket.

Class C5, Garen’s class, had just about managed to squeeze into the end of the Winners Bracket. After Sara lost four matches consecutively, they were in ninth place. Their ranking was basically held up by Fervale and Garen.

“I have disappointed you.” Sara was in a very bad mood.

Instructor Hamm did not say anything, he merely patted her shoulder.

“It’s alright, sort yourself out, and just do your best in the finals tomorrow. You’ve already reached this point, it’s already better than our class ranking before this,” Garen comforted her.

“You don’t need to say it, I understand.” Sara’s head was lowered, her expression pale.

Fervale stood at the side quietly, the successful consecutive wins had helped him recover some of his confidence.

The sky was growing dim, and after a whole day of matches, the participants and the audience alike were exhausted. They announced that the matches would continue on the second day, and the whole arena retired for the night.

Garen politely refused to go celebrating with Instructor Hamm and the others, walking out of the arena on his own. He walked towards Aier and Mina, who were wandering around the sidelines.

“Congratulations!”

“Congrats to us all.” Garen exchanged a glance with Mina, smiling.

“Nono… What I said before was… a little impulsive…” Aier apologized in a tiny voice, his face red as he fidgeted.

“It’s okay,” Garen waved his hand. “Come, let’s go eat first.”

Mina said with a smile,

“Why don’t you come to my workplace to eat? You’ll be giving us business, and the food there tastes pretty good too.”

“Sure.”

Garen did not really mind where they would eat.

He walked with the two of them, and also got to understand the many different interesting things that happened in the arena today. He had been focused on preparing for the matches, so he missed many of the other match-ups, but Aier and Mina did not. They had always been choosing and watching the other matches through the display screens.

According to the two of them, in this year’s qualifiers, the ones who were most favored in Grade C were Bally and Merseus, who plowed on through their matches. And that Caus also only lost one match, due to an accident. These three were commonly recognized as the strongest in Grade C.

The first two were especially considered prodigies among prodigies, they had at least Level 2 overall power at such a young age. They were only seventeen or eighteen, but they were already equivalent to those experienced pilots who had been training most their lives, this was the terrifying difference in talent.

Compared to them, the other Grade C students at average levels, students like Aier, were still struggling to get a few subjects to Level 1. They had not even come into contact with most of the subjects, much less participate in actual battles. Only those who had reached Level 1 in all the compulsory subjects would have reached the minimum requirement to join actual matches, because these subjects were the most basic aspects of controlling Mechs.

Now, Grade C was divided into stages here in the arena. Bally, Merseus and the others were in the first stage, having reached Level 2 standards overall. Caus, and the dark horse that defeated him were at the second stage, they had basically reached overall Level 2 power, which meant they had at least one or several subjects at Level 2. The difference between them and Bally’s group was that they had not yet achieved Level 2 in all subjects. Garen believed that he was at this stage as well, as were Fervale and that black Mech pilot he had defeated a while ago. After that, Sara and the others were at the third stage, people at this stage could use the Mech to batte smoothly, but they only had very basic moves and techniques, there was nothing particularly outstanding about them. It depended on who was familiar with the movements, or who was thinking brightly, there was very little difference between them.

Take Garen’s Concentrated Fire Laser Cannon technique for example, that was a Level 2 technique. To Level 1 fighters, that sort of technique meant that they would be one-shotted, it was the same for those opponents who weren’t good enough at dodging.

But when it came to guys with Level 2 overall power, there was no way they could be defeated in one hit.

“So your next opponent might not be someone you could defeat so simply, using your Concentrated Fire technique.”

Mina told Garen solemnly as the three of them sat in a coffee shop’s sweets corner.

Garen nodded, of course he knew that, but that was not his problem. His main problem was his Willpower, if he had enough Willpower, he could use his own fighting skills when it came to Mech combat. But now his Willpower was too underleveled, his actual Willpower was not even at Level 1. He could not even control the Mech fluidly, in other words, this body of his was in the same grade as Aier, Mina and the other regular students, or perhaps even worse. He had to rely on the Moonfang just to get into this qualifier match, which was full of prodigies.

It must be said that Blackboard Academy was a huge force that controlled several provinces, several thousands or even tens of thousands of students joined the school every year. This ranking competition chose the elites from among these students and had them battle each other.

“But having reached this placing, our class has definitely improved. Now we just need to keep steady and we’ll have succeeded.” Mina was very optimistic, even if they were in ninth place, they could still get a ten percent exemption off their tuition fees, and they could even use some special facilities or locations that were restricted to the top ten. These benefits were shared by the whole class. With these benefits, they could also earn a little extra outside. All of this evidently cheered her up greatly.

“It’s hard to keep steady as well, the ones who lost towards the end were all very strong elites,” Aier sighed beside them. He was a frank person, because he had said some mean things to Garen before, he had been apologizing all the way, and now he was back to normal.

“I heard that there was once all the classes in the Losers Bracket chose to challenge one ranked class, and then they wore that class down so they could kick them out and take their place. You need to be careful of that,” Mina nodded.

Garen had naturally also investigated information like that before, so he just nodded nonchalantly when he heard that.

With his combat experience and battle awareness, plus he had more than just the Laser Cannon in his arsenal, he just needed to be careful of the Moonfang’s time limit. Everything else was negotiable, as long as he did not get caught with his pants down like just now.

“Relax, I’ll do my best.”

Just then, a group of students sauntered in from outside the coffee shop. They all wore Grade C uniforms, and had fierce expressions. As soon as they came in, they started looking around, as though they were looking for someone.

“Where’s An Yixuan?” the boy in the lead, about eighteen or nineteen years old, asked loudly.

The coffee shop fell silent for a while, a few of the waiters in charge of sending food and drinks stopping in panic.

“I’m An Yixuan.” A young boy with a cold expression stood up in the corner, staring at these newcomers calmly.

The boy in the lead immediately walked over, surrounding the table with his group of people.

“Come, let’s go out for a chat.” Their voices instantly became smaller.

The others could not really hear it, but seemingly because Garen’s body had achieved the second grade of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique and improved his senses somewhat, he could vaguely hear a few words here and there.

“Next… match… surrender… or else…”

He could still understand the gist of what they were saying.

“An Yixuan is one of those few students in the Winners Bracket that has no influential family background at all,” Aier leaned forward and explained in a small voice. “I bet those people want him to concede the next match. Nono, you have to be wary of this move as well.”

Garen frowned.

Watching the group surround An Yixuan as they walked away, he could vaguely hear that they seemed to be tempting and threatening him using the way his family would be treated at work.

Most of the students in the Blackboard Academy were either rich or powerful, they all had special family backgrounds, and a web of influence that spanned the whole Blackboard Region. In other words, they just had to go back and tattle a little to their families, then they could already threaten the lifestyles of regular families. This was the result of great social inequality.

The other side was evidently using the influence of this inequality to tempt An Yixuan into purposely losing the next match. This was a deal, but it was also a threat.

He raised his head and saw that both Mina and Aier were looking at him somewhat worriedly. Instantly, he smiled slightly, showing a hint of calmness.

“It’ll be fine, don’t worry. I’ll deal with it properly.”

All three of them came from families at the bottom of the rung in the academy, even before, Mina was not from a particularly rich or famous family. This was the main reason the three of them ended up together. Watching An Yixuan get pushed out by a bunch of rich and powerful heirs now, they felt a sense of pity and sympathy.

But there was nothing they could do.

According to their normal paths, a student like An Yixuan would have been enrolled in the school due to his excellent results. His tuition fees must be a heavy burden on his family, and even if he was sure to find a high-income job after graduating, it would still be unlikely that he could join the Blackboard Academy as an elite. As a graduate, however, it was very likely that he could join the government or military pilot teams. If he were to offend these powerful people now, it would be really hard for him to progress later.

“Won’t the Academy do anything?” someone asked softly.

“It’s not that they don’t do anything, they’re allowing this on purpose. The Academy’s higher-ups believe that family background is also part of someone’s power, if someone could overcome that with their own talent and IQ, that would mean they are truly a prodigy, and then the Academy would truly prioritize them as a talent.”

“But what if they went overboard, and the students they had been raising for so long were accidentally destroyed by assassins?”

“The higher-ups have eyes on us, they have limits. I don’t know what the limits are, though, I just heard that from my cousin who’s in the Elites.”

Garen and the others listened to their discussion from the side, Aier and Mina feeling pretty bad about it.

Some cakes and bread arrived at their table, as well as some specially-made fruit plates, but the three of them only ate a bit before they realized they had no appetite. These were all man-made foods, after all, not natural, and upon hearing those words, they grew even unhappier.

Some calls came from Garen’s Terminal, they were all from the class. Instructor Hamm asked where he was eating, and whether he wanted to go out to karaoke to relax. Garen rejected him. His younger brother called to say he had seen him on TV, even if it was just a flash of his name through the match broadcasts, that was still enough to make him extremely excited.

And then that younger sister who wad rarely ever seen actually called him, asking him about how the matches were, as though raring to show off to her friends.

Throughout that meal, Garen never stopped receiving calls, and was actually busy for once. It took a long while before the calls finally slowed down.

Chapter 797: Blue Narcissus 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the south end of Blackboard City

Inside a small bakery somewhere.

“Lon, your older brother is actually from Blackboard Academy, you never told us!” In the adorable, pink-themed shop, a girl with pink hair wearing a white apron whined loudly as she pulled Lon’s hair.

“Owner, I told Shirley and the others a long time ago, don’t blame me!” Lon was also wearing a white apron, his long hair tied up. He had silky smooth white skin, and even his figure was like a girl’s. Overall, he gave off a strange sense of androgyny. He was also wearing black-rimmed glasses, so seen from afar, he did not look out of place among the group of young girls at all, he looked as simple and sweet as the rest of them.

“Is that right?” The pink-haired girl immediately turned around to look at the other girls in the shop, and some of the other young boys and girl instantly turned away guiltily. They were all younger than the shop owner, so the girl owner treated them as her younger brothers and sisters. The relationships between the workers here at the shop were all very pure, because they were all pure-minded people. In fact, the shop owner made sure of that when she picked them.

“It’s like this, Owner. Lon told us the last time when he was making a call, we all heard it,” a bespectacled pretty boy said in a small voice. “But Lon’s brother rarely contacts him, so he slowly forgot about it…”

Of course they had not forgotten about it, the truth was other than the pure Lon, all of them had noticed from the way Lon described him that Lon’s older brother, Nonosiva, actually looked down on his younger brother a lot. Although Lon clumsily tried to say good things about his brother, but Nonosiva’s arrogant, unfriendly, and domineering image slowly appeared in their hearts. So they would naturally avoid mentioning this topic to Lon.

“At first we thought that since there were so many people in Blackboard Academy, Lon’s brother would only be a normal student there at most, but to think… That guy does have the right to be haughty,” a girl with curly blonde pigtails said softly beside them.

“But Lon works so hard every day, and wears himself out just to earn money for his brother, then he still has to go to class at night as well. Despite all that, his brother doesn’t even care enough to ask, doesn’t that just make you sad?” another girl said quietly.

“Forget it, don’t say any more. If Lon hears you, he’ll make a fuss again.” The two girls looked at innocent Lon, and could not help but sigh inwardly.

“Fine, fine, Blackboard Academy and whatnot are too far removed from us, we had better stay realistic.” The pink-haired girl clapped her hands loudly, “Alright everyone, pay attention. My younger brother and his friend are coming over to help in a bit, they’ll be interning for the holidays. They’re both middle schoolers, about the same age as you, so I hope you all get along nicely.”

Whoa…

The workers all gathered around her in an instant.

“The owner’s younger brother? Is he as good-looking as me?”

“He might be a very cute little boy. I mean, look how pretty Owner is.”

“I wonder, what kind of a guy is he? It’d be troublesome if he had a bad temper.”

“Daisy, we’re counting on you! Conquer him with your charms!”

Seeing that all the workers were gathering curiously, the pink-haired girl put her hands on her waist happily.

“Relax, relax, my younger brother and his friend are all nice people, especially that brother of mine, he’s a ridiculously gentle guy, so don’t you guys bully him instead.”

“Really…”

“Do you have pictures?”

“Here?” The pink-haired girl took out a color photo, but it was instantly snatched away. “You’re asking for a beating, Jasmine!”

A girl with a silver ponytail ran off with the picture, giggling, but she was immediately surrounded.

“Let me see…”

She took the photo and shook it a little, looking at it.

The picture showed a short young boy with a shy smile. He was not particularly handsome but he did have some good-looking features, and his messy black hair was being mussed up even more by the shop owner behind him.

There were some words written in black pen on the bottom right corner: loos cover.

“This is Chironese, it means my beloved family. Oh my, Owner, how touching~~~”

Another boy grabbed the photo and read it out loud.

“Ah, do you wanna die!?” the pink-haired girl was instantly embarrassed.

Lon stood beside them, smiling. There was not a single customer in the shop, but everyone was having fun together. This was a very warm and comfy feeling.

He had also seen the boy in the picture, he looked very gentle, so he must be someone who’s easy to deal with.

**********************

Blackboard Academy

In the Grade C dormitory area.

Garen had just inserted his Identity Card into the door lock and opened the dorm door with a ka-chak when suddenly something twinged in his heart. It felt as though something had activated slightly, that indescribable feeling surging from his heart, and yet he could not identify the source.

He stood at the door quietly, his hand gripped the doorknob as he stayed completely still.

“This feeling… it’s so familiar…” he murmured softly.

Ka-chak.

There was the sound of the opposite student’s door opening behind him.

Garen was instantly shocked out of his reverie, and he tilted his head slightly to look behind him. The boy staying opposite him was making a call through his Watch Terminal, talking as he walked into his room.

He also pushed his door and walked inside, closing the door behind him. The footsteps of the students passing by, their chatter and laughter, the sound of the levitating car’s engine outside, he blocked all of it outside.

“Could it be… has that started?” He turned on the air-conditioner, took off his coat, and tossed it onto the chair. Then he lay down on his bed, facing upwards, as he slowly began to reminisce.

When he chose this body back then, it was mostly also because there seemed to be some strange energy around this body. Now, it seemed that his initial decision was starting to take effect.

He thought about it carefully. This feeling was very familiar, but not very clear, even Garen could not quite tell what it was. He thought about it carefully in bed for more than ten minutes, but he still could not figure it out.

Sighing, he sat up again directly, and began by starting his daily training method practice.

Glancing at the attribute pane, it seemed that his attribute was already beginning to change today.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 0.7, Agility 1.2, Vitality 0.5, Intelligence 1.4. Potential power 0%. Soul Limit 40.’

“All the stats have increased by 0.1 in average, not bad.” Garen nodded, satisfied. “I just wonder how much the second grade of the Peacock Technique will help enhance this body. If all my average stats could increase past 1 point, that would be the best. Then, with my combat experience and techniques, even if I’m facing someone like an armed special forces officer, I would still be able to protect myself.”

When powerful secret techniques reach their respective levels, they would bring the practitioner different degrees of changes. Some would be positive, others would be negative, and yet others would be completely harmless and meaningless.

And the Peacock Technique was the second grade of the elementary level, as the second grade of a Living Secret Technique, he did not how much it might change this body.

Garen looked at the secret technique and other skill attributes closely as well, and something had changed there as well. There were now skills related to Willpower there.

‘Willpower — Middle Basic Level,

(Training Method: Blackboard Control, the free training method from Blackboard Academy, weak training effects, advancement speed would be twelve years/level)’

“Now the training method has finally also become a Skill, looks like it’s because I have a better understanding of the training method in this world now, that’s why my natural ability could form an understanding of it as well.” Garen was thoughtful.

“If I can make it into a Skill, that means I can power it up using potential points. But the problem is this world does not seem to have anything like potential points at all…” Garen frowned slightly again.

Ding-dong…

Suddenly, the doorbell rang.

Garen glanced at the time, it was already past ten at night, who could that be?

He had just left Aier and Mina, if it was anyone else, they would surely call him on the Watch Terminal first.

The bell only rang once, and then it was quiet.

Garen stood up and walked to the door to open it.

The door cracked open, but there was no one outside at all, just a letter on the floor. On the white envelope, there was one line of words: To Nonosiva Lin.

Garen picked up the letter and looked around again. Two chattering students walked into the dorm, but there was not anything suspicious other than that.

He closed the door again, and brought that letter back to his bed, where he sat down.

“Could Nonosiva have some special personal connections in this world? Or could it be…” Garen tore open the envelope, and pulled an unsigned letter out of it, opening it gently.

‘Dear Nono, for the second match tomorrow, we hope you will admit defeat of your own accord.’ And then there was a picture of a blue narcissus.

Garen saw the more words through the back of the paper, and flipped it over to see.

‘Rondo Lin, Vice Section Manager, Negotiations Section, Commerce Department, Jusang Interregional Investment Company.’

‘Amy Lamda, Vice Section Manager, Warehouse Section, Operations Department, Jusang Interregional Investment Company.’

“So that’s what this means?” Garen touched the paper, and instantly understood.

“Nonosiva’s parents are both just very normal, average workers, these Sections and Departments and whatnot, they’re telling me this is the price of my throwing the match this time… Not bad, the carrot and the stick… How effective.”

He knew that such a change in positions would make a huge difference to the whole family. The position of Vice Section Manager would at least double their annual income, and if both of them had their salaries doubled at the same time, the whole family’s economic situation would be drastically improved. This was the unrefutable carrot the other side was dangling in front of him.

In this kind of Academy, faced with peers who could change his entire family’s fate with just a few words, no wonder the previous Nonosiva ended up so withdrawn, sullen, and had such low confidence. This was not the kind of pressure a teenager should have to withstand.

“Well, how should I settle this matter?” Garen held the letter, and began to think.

He was really taking it seriously, according to the way competition was supposed to go, the second match of the finals tomorrow should be the second match of the Losers Bracket challengers. In other words, the other person was an elite from the Losers Bracket who wanted to exchange these conditions for Class C5’s position in the Winners Bracket.

This did not quite match Garen’s previous plans.

“And to ask for an exchange with something like this, it’s still lacking…” Garen did not really mind throwing away matches, as long as he achieved his goal, such means did not matter. It was just that the other person was offering too little in exchange, so it was not worth it.

Beep-beep… Beep-beep…

Suddenly his Watch Terminal began to ring, someone was calling him at this time.

Garen raised his wrist and glanced at it. There was no incoming number, just the picture of a bunch of deep blue narcissuses. He waited for a brief moment, and then he quickly turned on his laptop. After a pattering of keys, he picked up a data cable and connected it to his Watch Terminal, and only then did he accept the call.

“Hello, we are the Blue Narcissus. May we know if you’ve received the letter?” As soon as the call went through, a raspy woman’s voice spoke through it.

Garen glanced at a software he had invented on his laptop, the wavy line on it rose and fell slightly. He turned back.

“I received it, but with my capabilities, your offer is too low.”

“??” The other person was taken aback, she had not expected Garen to say that so directly. Anyone who could make it past the Qualifiers was undeniably all talented and arrogant individuals, if you wanted them to lose on purpose, they would surely not take it well. But this time, Garen was actually bargaining with her calmly.

Chapter 798: Blue Narcissus 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What?” when Garen did not hear the other person’s reply, he prompted her to continue.

“It’s just slightly unexpected. I did not anticipate that you would be able to speak to us in such a rational and calm manner,” replied the woman once she had returned to normal. “If you think that the price is too low, then what is your desired amount? Could you let me know?”

“My strength levels are enough to impact the top three competitors. Don’t you think this price is a little low?” Garen asked instead.

“What you say is true, and your current levels prove that you undoubtedly possess extremely good character. You say that you can attack the top three, Bally, Merseus, and Caus, but the three of them are not average people that can be shaken easily,” said the woman lightly.

“I can prove it to you in the next competition,” answered Garen in a straightforward manner.

“Oh? How are you going to prove that?” the voice on the other line changed suddenly. It was now a crisp female voice that sounded somewhat cold but also strong at the same time. It was obvious that the speaker on the other side had switched temporarily.

“How about the three Level 2 combat techniques?” replied Garen in a brisk and casual tone.

“…!!!” there was no sound on the other side suddenly as they were clearly subdued.

Indeed, even Bally and Merseus were only confirmed to have Level 2 strength through the results of the comprehensive assessment. Out of all the topics of the actual combat assessment topics, there were only ten that could truly provide a comprehensive assessment of an individual’s strength levels. Among these topics, Garen was able to achieve the Level 2 standard for three of them at once. Coupled with the Laser Cannon integrated techniques that he had displayed earlier, he was able to grasp four Level 2 techniques in total. This meant that he was almost halfway there. Everything was just as Garen had said. He had the strength to surpass the top three and was highly hopeful that he could overtake Caus’ position at least.

“Are you certain that you’re not mistaken?” after keeping quiet for a while, the other person finally spoke again.

“Of course,” answered Garen calmly. He was undeniably and incomparably powerful in terms of combat. Although his Willpower was slightly weaker which forced him to use his basic combat techniques to display his strength, his Master-level combat experience could not be compared to the current strengths of the weaker fellows. If it was not for the Moonfang’s time limit, he could definitely snatch the third place position and get rid of Caus. However, the same could not be said for the first and second places as the Level 2 combat techniques of this world seemed to be linked to Willpower. This produced strange qualitative changes that Garen had never seen before. He could not be sure of the integrated powers that the other two would use.

After all, his extremely weak Willpower was also a terrible shortcoming. If he was hindered for a certain duration or if changes that exceeded his expectations appeared suddenly, it would be impossible to easily ensure his victory.

“…We will need to consider and discuss this. Please wait a moment.”

The female voice on the other line became more polite suddenly. It was obvious that Garen’s strength had exceeded their expectations greatly. Furthermore, it was just as Garen had stated. Their attempt to exchange something for the victory of a professional would be easily detected by the academy. Moreover, a normal member of the crowd would be able to see through a trick like that as well, and they would end up shooting themselves in the foot if they were not careful.

Garen was not anxious at all. Instead, he merely pulled out his tablet computer quietly and begin to click his fingers against it gently. He had learned programming skills in the Vampire world on his own and was able to adapt to the computing input programs here quickly once he had arrived in this advanced and computerized world. The computers here were unlike the backward machines that he had used before. Meanwhile, the likes of quantum computers existed here. The concept of quantum computers stated that most computers that utilized binary systems used 0 and 1 as their basic units. When computing, countless 0’s and 1’s would circulate through the computer as its data.

Meanwhile, quantum computers could be visualized as numerous computers that were operating inside binary system computers. When they encountered certain combinations of nested problems that were difficult to untangle, these computers would be able to solve them at the quickest speed.

Quantum computers were computing models that used sets as units while the older computers used elements as units. Therefore, their computing abilities had been improved greatly. They could gather various methods to solve problems. This was also the main reason for the great developments throughout the Mech Battleships.Professional divisions of various types of quantum computers were able to utilize certain complicated, optimized organizational structures of Mechs several times as sets to perform unit calculation analysis. The Mechs that were assembled through this process could perform beyond people’s expectations and achieve extremely good progress.

There were similarities between quantum computers and traditional computers because of their origins. Therefore, Garen was able to adapt to the programming models here quickly once he had come into contact with the computers in this world.

The tablet computer that he was using now was a typical miniature quantum computer. Although it was not highly advanced and could not operate larger units, it could still react quickly towards web environments regardless of their complexity and analyze them.

Seconds and minutes ticked by. Garen tapped against the virtual keyboard that was projected by the tablet computer continuously while the rotating image of a soundwave on the screen gradually became clearer. He had already achieved the first step of determining the current position of the other person’s phone call.

“Your requests are very reasonable if you can truly display this strength tomorrow,” the person on the other line finally spoke again.

Within this short duration of fewer than ten minutes, Garen had managed to discover a series of information regarding Blue Narcissus in the academy.

The Blue Narcissus organization was an internal organization of a larger scale within Blackboard Academy. As one of the three main student organizations in Blackboard, Blue Narcissus was comprised of influential officials that represented the strength of their disciples. Although their individual members did not necessarily possess great strength, their network of background relations was still the strongest out of the three main organizations. In simpler terms, they were a group that specialized in recruiting strong forces that comprised of the supposed princes and princesses in the academy.

Unlike Black Rose that revered actual combat and strength, or the moderate Thousand Year Tree, the main idea of Blue Narcissus revolved around the notion that relations, background, and individual power were all a form of strength. However, they were more welcoming towards influential disciples as many generations of their leaders were all first-rate powerful proteges.

“Among the three main organizations, many people actually have misunderstandings towards Blue Narcissus,” explained the woman on the other line quietly. “We are not inclined towards influential individuals. On the contrary, we merely recruit geniuses who can break free of the whirlpool of power around them on their own. This matter is strictly in accordance with the academy’s purpose.”

“I understand. What do you plan to do then? Regarding my problem I mean.”

“Your conditions are something that we agree with fully,” the woman answered certainly. “I am representing Blue Narcissus to agree with your requests as elites should only be given elite treatment.”

She pondered for a moment. It was possible that she was exchanging opinions with the others.

“Regarding our cooperation with you, we now have a new method to do that. However, we don’t know if you will be willing to accept it.”

Garen pressed the enter key on the keyboard of the computer single-handedly before looking at the bunch of blue narcissus flowers once again.

“What methods? Tell me.”

“Regarding the new methods, if you really possess the power to impact the top three, you only need to join Blue Narcissus so that we can support your claim to overtake the top three to snatch a spot for an elite personal fight. As long as you can become an elite member, I will be able to give you the best treatment for your family and your personal development. I’ve heard that… Your previous surgery fees were paid for in advance by your instructor. I’m sure that you want to repay Instructor Hamm for the expenses as soon as possible, right?” it seemed as though the woman on the other line was very knowledgeable about Nonosiva’s information.

“What kind of treatment?” Garen had always been concerned about the practical benefits only. The changes in the other person’s attitude were things that he’d anticipated as well. It was one of the main situational variables and did not greatly faze him at all.

“Your parents’ occupations will not change but their gloomy salaries will be increased to five hundred thousand Units a year. In the academy, you will receive a certain amount of background strength and support that is given to all Blue Narcissus members. Of course, your opponent in Grade C, Arello, is included as well, and you will not have to worry about him using his family circumstances and background to suppress you. Meanwhile, I believe that you will be able to deal with the direct confrontations as you managed to teach Caus and his friends a painful lesson previously, right?” it seemed as though the woman was clearly more relaxed now.

“Is the background strength guaranteed?” the information that Garen had investigated stated that this was the main method that Blue Narcissus used to entice students with good potential. Students with good potential that came from financially unstable families were easily oppressed by others who were influential disciples. Under these circumstances, those of them who had yet to mature were unusually weak and would squander away their talents if they were not careful. Therefore, Blue Narcissus’ actions provided a beneficial platform for them to exhibit their strong backgrounds fully while mediating and assuring the development of these students with good potentials. Finally, once these potential students had matured and become the new generation of influential individuals, most of them would not forget the ones that provided help during a key point of their lives.

Blackboard Academy had been established for hundreds of years and these three main student organizations had stood firm through time. They naturally had their own commendable points and could not simply be known as arrogant organizations.

However, the ones that could truly receive the exceptional treatment from Blue Narcissus were naturally only the authentic first-rate geniuses that had good futures ahead of them. They were lucky if they could even find five of these individuals within a grade. Instead, they only recruited more influential disciples in each year, naturally paling themselves in comparison to the other organizations.

Garen pondered carefully for a moment. The main shortcoming that was faced by his current self, or rather Nonosiva, was that his family background and circumstances would cause him to be easily oppressed by powerful and influential disciples. This would also hinder his personal development. The support that Blue Narcissus was willing to provide was something that he truly needed.

“Increasing the strength of Blue Narcissus’ elite scholars is a point that we pay close attention to. An individual who can enter the elites despite being a new student will always receive additional resources and favor as such a new student usually possesses great potential,” explained the woman sincerely. “Have are your considerations going? Joining Blue Narcissus will be your best decision.”

Garen became quiet for a while. “From what I know, aren’t there two other main organizations? Black Rose and Thousand Year Tree…”

“Unfortunately, your opponent Caus is a member of Thousand Year Tree while his older brother, the assessed student named Cor, is an elite Grade B member of Black Rose. They have a network of special relations within the Mech actual combat department and since you did not display any shocking aptitude or talents, it was only natural that they did not invite you,” the woman did not hold back and chose to speak the truth directly instead.

“…Okay. I agree to join Blue Narcissus,” replied Garen right away after considering for a while. In his opinion, joining an organization was merely a temporary decision to borrow power. As long as this organization gave him a favorable impression, he did not mind repaying them once he had matured. Moreover, the key factor was the other party’s sincerity. The things that they had mentioned were the same as what he had discovered through his hacking skills. Therefore, this meant the other side truly wanted to recruit and invest in him.

“The aim of Blue Narcissus is to turn each of our members into our pride and joy while becoming the dignity of our members as well,” replied the woman earnestly. “You will not regret joining us.”

Garen smiled before hanging up the phone.

Chapter 799: Urgent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Within the arena that was projected by a gigantic Battleship

Bouts of cheers and screams rang out and echoed throughout the competition arena continuously as the crowd yelled excitedly. Large blimps floated across the sky above the arena while rows of new data constantly appeared on the display screen on the side of the blimp.

‘Grade A, first place Nicotine Kate, second place Carlos, third place Minda.’

‘Grade B, first place Kanda, second place Ruth Tribune, third place Marie.’

‘Grade C, first place Merseus, second place Bally, third place Caus.’

The data on the blimp’s display screen clearly showed the results of the three strongest individuals in the arena according to their grade. These rankings were not based on just their current individual results. If they had similar achievements, the results would also depend on their rankings in their respective grades to determine their positions.

More than a hundred classes were assigned to their respective boxes in the arena. The boxes resembled little honeycomb boxes and were filled with contestants and instructors from various classes who were constantly discussing the finals that were about to start today.

Unlike the roaring crowds at the side of the arena, most of the elite contestants inside these boxes had calm looks on their faces. Their expressions were composed as if they were not affected by the enthusiastic atmosphere at all.

Contestants who displayed abnormal behaviors after being affected by these matters would have been eliminated by this stage already. Only those whose abilities and qualities improved throughout all aspects had remained.

Inside a black box on the left side of the arena.

Garen, Fervale, and Sara were listening to Instructor Hamm’s warnings quietly.

“Today’s arena is unlike yesterday’s. When you proceed, you must remember to stay calm and collected while displaying all of your strength. Don’t leave any regrets even if you lose.”

“Understood,” it seemed as though Fervale had readjusted himself and regained his previous composure. His gaze occasionally drifted in a different direction towards another box.

Sara spoke beside Garen’s ear softly.

“Fervale met the competitor from his family’s opposing clan yesterday. It seemed as though his opponent had said something to provoke him.”

Garen glanced over in the direction of Fervale’s gaze and coincidentally noticed a girl with light green hair who was grimacing at Fervale and running her finger across her throat. The girl with short hair looked extremely fierce and had a robust figure. There was a scar at the corner of her brow and her pure white school uniform gave off a clean and nimble disposition.

He noticed that Fervale had begun to tighten his fist slightly.

“Really…” Garen heard Sara sigh and shake her head beside him as if she was already aware of certain ulterior motives.

However, he was too lazy to ask because it was almost his turn to step forward.

‘Nonosiva of Class C5 vs Enzo of C14.’

While the mechanical announcer’s voice rang out, Garen entered the Mech in the passageway quickly.

*************************

A bakery in the southern part of the city

“It’s Lon’s big brother! Come and look quickly!”

the shop assistant Shirley was yelling loudly.

Suddenly, everyone else inside the shop glanced over, including a couple of customers who were busy choosing cakes.

“Stop yelling,” Lon rushed over with an embarrassed look on his face and pulled Shirley away while his cheeks continued to blush.

On the television screen, two Mech Pilots were displayed on separate screens while they were getting into their respective machines. In front of half of a white Mech that was shown, a black-haired young man who had just sat inside his Mech had attracted the attention of everyone inside the shop immediately. When Shirley pointed at him, everyone discovered that he was Lon’s older brother Nonosiva.

The black-haired young man on the screen had a calm expression on his face. Both of his eyes were deep blue valleys that gave off cool dispositions. His blue and white Blackboard Academy uniform hugged his well-built figure tightly.

When he sat upright inside the Mech, a black helmet above him lowered itself automatically and covered the youth’s average-looking face. Next, numerous electronic display screens around him began to light up progressively in succession before the blue and white fluorescent lights illuminated the interior of the Mech.

‘Currently broadcasting live is the first match of the Winners Bracket of Grade C. Enzo from class C14 is here to challenge Nonosiva of class C5. Both of these participants are new elite students who have only entered Blackboard Academy for a year. Within the short span of a year, both of them achieved considerable progress. Compared to Nonosiva’s impressive record of consecutive victories, student Enzo encountered the current first ranked competitor Merseus halfway and unfortunately lost…’

The scene on the television screen moved to the two seated announcers suddenly. A beautiful female announcer and a white-haired old man sat side by side while facing the audience. They were currently introducing the achievements and identities of the two individuals on screen who were about to face off.

“So cool!”

A young male shop assistant who stood beside Lon could not help but exclaim softly.

These were the sentiments that most of the other people inside the shop shared as well. On the left, Enzo was a young woman with long white hair. A composed expression was plastered on her beautiful face. Meanwhile, Nonosiva on the right gave off a cold and emotionless air.

“Are these Mech Pilots?” beside the shop owner with long pink hair, a black-haired boy stared at the two people on screen with a look of faint admiration in his glimmering eyes. “How cool!” he murmured.

“You must study hard so that you’ll have a chance to be like them in the future!” the shop owner laughed happily and slapped her palm against the boy’s head.

“Ouch! Sis, why did you hit me again?!”

“I’m just encouraging you!” “What kind of encouragement is this?!”

Lon stood on the side silently and watched in awe at the black-haired boy who was now covering his head and running around. Although he was currently balancing his life between working and studying with much difficulty, it was inevitable that this situation would affect his studies. Therefore, his results had started to deteriorate gradually.

“Perhaps I could properly learn some pastry making skills in the future to become a normal but dependable person…” he raised his head and looked at his older brother on screen who was currently waiting to begin his battle while a strange glimmer flashed in his eyes.

“Lon!” someone clapped his shoulder gently at once.

Lon returned to his senses immediately before noticing that the black-haired boy was already standing in front of him now.

“Don’t worry, you’ll have a chance next time as well!” the boy smiled at him shyly.

“You are not your older brother; you are you. It doesn’t matter if you don’t want a cold older brother like him because we’ll be your siblings in the future!” beside him, Shirley bounced over with the shop assistant Daisy.

In the shop, Lon was sincere, honest and hardworking. He displayed natural talents when learning pastry making techniques and was also a kind person who constantly helped others whenever he could and would never refuse them. This had won him the friendship of his co-workers.

When he saw the crowd that gathered around him, Lon’s heart was unusually touched.

“I…”

“The competition has begun!” suddenly, noises that indicated that the match had started echoing from the television.

*******************

The moment the words begin to drift off, two white laser beams shot out suddenly from the white Mech that Garen was controlling. The strong force from the laser cannons resembled two sharp swords that were piercing towards the chest of the black Mech. However, they were speedily evaded by their agile opponent.

At this moment, Garen had apparently discarded the Laser Cannons that he held in his hands earlier. Instead, he placed his hand behind his back and removed a hidden Gaussian Electromagnetic Gun. When his opponent was dodging the laser cannons, he was able to level the barrel of the Electromagnetic Gun properly.

The thick black barrel was aimed precisely at the black Mech.

Bang!

The black bomb passed through a distance of more than ten meters instantly and hit the transparent screen behind the black Mech directly before rebounding and hitting the jet engine behind it.

Boom!!

The black Mech lost all movement and stumbled a few steps forward before collapsing on the ground.

It was hit with another bomb before the top of the Mech exploded, causing the fight to end.

“This is… Rebound Interference!!”

Outside the arena, Instructor Hamm stood up in disbelief while a look of incredible surprise appeared on his face, “Another Level 2 technique!!”

Loud cheers exploded throughout the crowd outside the arena. Rebound Interference, a Level 2 technique was a Level 2 technique used by Mech Pilots. It was one of the three fighting techniques that did not require Willpower. It used various judgments and calculations from the outside world and used long-range weapons to form rebounds or refraction effects from shooting.

By using Rebound Interference and his integrated Laser Cannons from earlier, Nonosiva had already displayed two powerful techniques that did not need to be combined with Willpower.

Garen kept his Gaussian Guns and turned to walk out of the passageway without even glancing back at the black Mech on the ground.

On the other side, Fervale was using a different black Mech to fight frantically. The intensity of this fight was far fiercer than the one over here. Meanwhile, Sara had yet to step into the field but had already entered the waiting passage.

The three lowest ranked competitors of the Winners Bracket from each class had already been matched with their opponents.

Happy and prideful expressions appeared on both Aier and Mina’s faces when they watched the competition that had ended within moments. The ability to exhibit displays of strength and achievements like these so easily despite reaching such advanced stages undoubtedly showed Garen’s incomparably powerful innate strength.

Meanwhile, on the seats behind them, a few composed-looking students nodded faintly when they witnessed Garen’s performance while hints of astonishment flashed in their eyes.

***********************

The bakery

“He actually used the Rebound Interference technique! I really cannot believe that this technique would be displayed by a first-year student who just entered the school!” the announcer exclaimed quietly and covered her little mouth while looking at the fight on the display screen.

“Although we’ve previously already seen the first-rate techniques such as short-range bursts and victories that were won by spears of electric currents, I’m still amazed to see skills of such difficulty being displayed by youths despite their young ages,” the old man that was speaking shook his head in admiration. “When we compare our elderly selves to these young people, it seems as if we have simply wasted our years. They are truly the geniuses of Blackboard Academy.”

“That’s right. Young geniuses will always emerge during Blackboard Academy’s Elite Qualifier Matches every year. Moreover, they will always exhibit amazing performances,” nodded the other announcer.

“Indeed, since he is already able to use Level 2 techniques with ease, as long as he continues to train in actual combat, this young man will be able to reach the standard of a captain who can lead the Mech Pilots to fight on the battlefield. Furthermore, he’s not even eighteen years old yet,” praised the old man.

“He is truly amazing… The students of Blackboard Academy are really first-class geniuses…” the black-haired youth began to exclaim unconsciously again. When he noticed Lon staring blankly in a daze from the corner of his eye, the youth involuntarily stroked the little item that he had picked up not long ago.

“But I won’t fall behind either. With this, I will be able to become an excellent Mech Pilot as well!”

“Don’t touch my pure body as you please!” a voice that was both feminine and masculine entered his mind suddenly.

“Oh… I’m sorry. That was unintentional,” the black-haired youth immediately apologized in his head.

“Don’t worry, the future you long for will not be bleak. Although you are merely a piece of garbage without the slightest hint of aptitude, there are still certain types of garbage that can be useful,” the voice spoke in a lofty tone without concealing its disdain at all.

“Is my aptitude really that terrible…? Don’t tell me I’m actually less than average?” said the youth helplessly.

Chapter 800: Urgent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Compared to that normal fellow beside you, the difference between both of your aptitudes is equivalent to the difference between a firefly and the moon. I’d be praising you excessively if I said that you were average,” answered the voice scornfully. “If you had not recognized my noble self by a lucky coincidence, I’d assume that you would be forced to spend your entire life gathering scrap metals.”

The expression on the youth’s face collapsed in defeat immediately as the other person’s words had instantly made him feel uncertain and hopeless about his future.

“Don’t worry, as long as your humble self listens to your Master’s instructions and does as your great Master commands, you will definitely surpass your wildest dreams in the future. That’s right, what is your name?”

“Clint… Clint Beza…” answered the youth feebly.

“Alright, Clint whatever, I need you to do something now.”

“Do what?”

“Stick me on the body of the youth beside you temporarily. I need to probe him for a while. If this is successful, this guy can probably become one of your underlings,” said the voice in a straightforward manner. “At the present stage, your ignorant and useless self has made it impossible for me to use too much strength. Therefore, finding some trustworthy people to control as your subordinates is the first task that you must prepare.”

“Baylon is my friend, not my subordinate,” young Clint corrected the voice weakly. His life had begun to change slowly ever since he’d picked up the thing after he came over to his older sister’s place to experience the working life. He said meaningless things to restore his past glory and accepted the approval of others reluctantly. In the end, his life was immediately turned upside down.

“Garbage is basically garbage. You don’t even have the guts to assume the responsibility for someone else’s fate?”

Clint glanced at Lon beside him and saw the exact same desire and admiration in his eyes towards the Mechs.

“Moreover, even if I dared to undertake the responsibility, you would still require resources to modify yourself, right? Wouldn’t you need time as well?”

“Alright, the decision is yours. Stick me on the surface of that guy’s skin once you’ve finished thinking.” the voice fell to a lower tone immediately.

Although he did not know why the once tyrannical other party had suddenly become so good-natured, Clint could still sigh in momentary relief.

He shifted his gaze towards the television screen again where a Mech fight scene between students of higher grades was being shown on the screen currently.

“Master Red Moon…”

“What’s the matter? Speak now if you have something to say. I’m very busy!” said the voice impatiently.

“I… Could I achieve Lon’s older brother’s… Could I achieve the level of Lon’s older brother?” Clint lowered his head in uncertainty.

“His level? Your goals are too low, don’t you think?” the voice that was referred to as ‘Red Moon’ said scornfully. “Moreover, you really think that the guy called Nonosiva is amazing?”

“Umm… Isn’t he amazing? He could use Level 2 techniques despite his young age…”

“Hehe… Is it really like that?” Red Moon sneered. “Patterning actions like that meant that his Willpower… Enough, you wouldn’t understand even if I told you. You will know next time!”

“Oh…”

***************

The third match

Garen sat inside the Mech and inhaled deeply. Using his Willpower for long periods of time formed a faint ache around his temples. This was caused by his extreme lack of Willpower. Despite possessing the Moonfang’s additional abilities, extended durations of fighting would still increase the burden on his Willpower.

However, this was also a part of the competition. Fighting for extended periods of time would test the endurance of his Willpower.

On the opposite arena, a Black Mech stood facing him on the black alloy ground like a giant approaching enemy. It held a silver towering shield that covered half of its body in one hand. This whole towering shield resembled a mirror that could speedily reflect light beam type weapons or attacks. Moreover, it was made of a durable alloy that possessed even better defensive effects against Gaussian type live ammunition weapons.

“The competition has reached a standstill. London, the Elite from the Losers Bracket is currently up against the instant killer Nonosiva who has a record of consecutive victories. How will the results turn out?” the commentator’s voice could be heard faintly from the outside.

Garen’s face was expressionless. He had already come so far and would truly become the ultimate victor in the Winners Bracket after winning a few more rounds.

His opponent on the other side, London, had defeated Sara. Their leader was currently in the finals with Fervale, but no one knew how the results would turn out.

If Fervale was defeated… The position of Class C would not go any further. They would not be allowed to participate in the internal matches within the Winners Bracket and their previously significant ninth place position would be displaced, causing them to fall to eleventh place instantly.

“But…” Garen stared at the Black Mech opposite him while his head continued to hurt slightly. That guy basically resembled a tortoiseshell. Regardless whether he hit him with a shot from his Concentrated Laser Cannon or used his Rebound Interference technique, his attacks would constantly be resisted and unloaded by his opponent’s Impregnable Wall technique. Moreover, his opponent was an extremely patient person as it was obvious that they were delaying their defense and counter attacking tactics.

Bang!!

A loud explosion could be heard from the Gaussian Cannon suddenly before a black cannonball hit the upper right corner of the Black Mech’s towering shield instantly. It attempted to hit the shield until it was sent flying sideways.

However, it seemed as if the Black Mech had anticipated this much earlier. It turned its body to the side while the shield suddenly moved slightly simultaneously as well.

Clang!

The black Mech stumbled a few steps backward. It was facing Garen sideways now while directly using the center of its shield to counter the cannon balls by deflecting and sending them flying at once.

“Blocked again! Student London’s Level 2 technique Impregnable Wall has been using the core position of its shield to ward off its enemies attacks. Nonosiva’s Gaussian Cannons were sent flying directly as well,” the commentator who was only prepared for the final match spoke hurriedly.

“This is a tortoiseshell!” Garen glanced at the time quickly: 8 minutes.

“I need to finish this immediately!”

Bang!

The black Gaussian Cannon exploded again before the cannon shot out again after a cooling down period of ten seconds.

Before waiting for the next cooling down period, Garen did not look at the outcome but chose to switch to his Laser Cannon before shooting again.

White laser beams hit against one side of London’s shield for a period of time while the entire arena was only filled with the attack shots from Garen’s side. Meanwhile, London could merely defend himself.

As the competition continued to progress, Garen encountered stronger opponents as well. Meanwhile, the consumption of his Willpower became greater. Initially, his Willpower was only at the middle section of the foundation level as he could not even reach one proper level. However, after continuously fighting numerous matches, his Willpower restoration could not fully keep up with his depletion anymore.

Clang!

Black Light flashed from the Gaussian Cannon, finally hitting London’s shield sideways slightly. When it exposed the body of the Mech behind it, only then did the audience realize that all of the continuous Gaussian Cannons from earlier had hit against the same spot without much deviation.

“That’s it…” Garen adjusted his Laser Cannon slightly while white light gathered at the barrel.

It was over…

Tch!

Suddenly, the white Moonfang light in the control console flashed before dimming suddenly.

“This again!!” Garen immediately sensed that something was amiss. He lost control of the Mech’s body instantly while the Mech became abnormally delayed and seemingly unable to react again! “Not this time again!!” a gloomy expression flashed across his face.

Seconds and minutes ticked by while the white light of the Laser Cannon disappeared as everything returned to a calm state again. Garen’s White Mech stood in its spot quietly while facing the Black Mech on the other side. The arena turned completely silent for a while.

The Black Mech glanced at the shield in its hand and became silent for a moment.

Almost ten seconds later.

“I surrender.”

The voice of the Black Mech Pilot London echoed over.

The Black Mech discarded its towering shield and only then did the crowd realize that its shield was currently full of holes. It was almost pierced through. It was obvious that if this went on for a little while longer, this towering shield would become completely useless. Therefore, admitting defeat right now allowed him to lose without being embarrassed completely.

‘Winner, Nonosiva of Class C5!’

The cold mechanical voice was replaced with the announcer’s enthusiastic voice.

Most of the students cheered happily, especially the students of Class C5 who were extremely excited.

On the other side, Fervale cut off the right arm of his opponent’s Mech in one swift movement. Sparks were flying all over his Mech and it was obvious that he was reaching his limit soon. Moreover, both of the Mechs were undeniably worn-out. It seemed as if he had only won this victory through endurance and perseverance.

‘Winner, Fervale of Class C5!’

Similar noises rang out while Fervale sat inside his Mech and closed his eyes slightly while his exhausted face turned pale.

There was a screen on the side of the blimp that floated across the sky. The ranking of class C5 remained steadily at the ninth place as they had finally defeated the three challenging classes from the Losers Bracket.

Garen raised his head and glanced at the rankings while pressure began to form in his mind. If his opponent had continued to attack without giving up during the risky situation earlier, he might have become the loser instead.

His extremely weak Willpower made it more difficult for him when he encountered subsequent opponents. Without an abundance of Willpower to sustain himself, he could only depend on the Moonfang’s control and coordination. He could truly be dragged to death if he encountered long-lasting tortoiseshell-like opponents again.

“Willpower… I need to solve this problem quickly.” when he recalled the continuous times he had screwed up during important moments, Garen knew that the source of his problems was still his weak Willpower.

The unstable circumstances that appeared because of the Moonfang made it difficult for him to grasp the situation when he encountered defensive opponents. If he did not solve this problem, the following internal matches in the Winners Bracket would be very troublesome.

Once he had gotten out of the Mech, he congratulated and celebrated with the others. Next, he underwent restoring massage treatments and replenished his nutrition fluids. When the arena closed in the evening, Garen declined the offer to celebrate the results of keeping their ninth place position again. Instead, he left the arena alone and walked towards his dorm.

The finals would be held on the third day. There would be an internal match in the Winners Bracket where the top three competitors would be selected as the Elite participants who entered the school this year. Most of the competitors in the Winners Bracket had grasped one Level 2 technique and none of them would be easily defeated.

Garen was currently somewhat clearer about his level now. In situations where Willpower was strictly limited, he could only use his combat experience for fighting techniques that did not require Willpower. However, this was merely one factor as his limited Willpower made it impossible for him to fight for extended periods of time. Furthermore, the inability to use fighting techniques that were combined with Willpower made it difficult for him to counter his opponent’s Willpower techniques.

In the following final match, he would also need to watch out for accidental situations where the Moonfang would screw up suddenly.

“This is so troublesome…” Garen walked on the road back while constantly focusing on the changing time on his Attribute Pane that represented the time taken for his heart to be modified. The schedule that was counting down kept shrinking continuously.

“I can only find a way to solve this by using Secret Techniques. I can probably use White Peacock Stones to speed up the modification of the Peacock Technique.”

Garen returned to his dorm and clicked his terminal communication’s address book immediately once he had closed the door. He looked for the contact number of the bearded merchant and called him at once.

After a continuous beeping waiting tone, the other side was connected quickly.

“Why are you calling so early? The goods aren’t here yet,” said the bearded merchant suspiciously.

“When will the second batch of goods arrive?” Garen asked directly without making any small talk.

“If all goes well, it will be here by noon tomorrow. After all, they’re being delivered from other areas and the quantities this time are slightly larger as well.”

Chapter 801: Pressure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The price is still the same as the last time. The difference in the wholesale price that you gain from distributing it will be your commission. Urge them to hurry up and send the things to me as soon as possible.”

Garen furrowed his eyebrows when he spoke.

“Are you that anxious? Alright, I’ll take a look at the process in between to see where it is now. I’ll try to speed them up,” Beardy sounded somewhat helpless. “As for the commission and whatnot,” he wavered for a while before becoming slightly more sincere in the end. “I don’t want the commission or anything like that. I’ve already earned a lot just by doing this.”

Cooperation was something that required a long duration of perseverance and it was clear that Beardy understood this. If he wanted this business deal to be repeated in the future, he could not give the other party a reason to change business partners. Moreover, he would need to show him that he was a superior associate as much as possible.

“That’s right, what is your name?” asked Garen suddenly.

“Kendall…” the bearded man sounded somewhat impatient as he had clearly introduced himself previously.

“Alright, Kendall. If you can deliver the items to the academy by tonight, I will increase the payment by an additional five Units for each item,” said Garen while attempting to lure him in with the promise of an immediate gain.

After coming to this world and encountering mysterious Willpower systems, he could vaguely feel, and had a premonition that this Willpower was actually a powerful force that was not inferior to his Secret Technique systems. Through his martial arts consciousness, he could vaguely see the future of Willpower training methods through this.

The ability to dominate civilizations in the universe that used planetary territories as units while occupying peak forces meant that it was highly likely that these systems were hiding certain powerful aspects that were unknown to most people.

“Tonight?” the person on the other terminal became silent for a while as if he was considering something.

Garen was not anxious and chose to wait quietly instead. He required a large batch of goods this time. He had spent one thousand Units for two hundred pieces previously, which meant that he had almost spent five Units for each piece. Although it was not a huge leap when the price increased to five Units per piece, it was important to note that he was buying more than two thousand pieces this time. Therefore, he would be performing a transaction of over ten thousand Units at once. Transactions like these were not considered as minor business deals in physical stores, much less for little vendors like him who only had enough capital to run pushcart businesses.

“All of the White Stones will arrive at your doorstep before three o’clock in the morning tomorrow!” finally, Kendall’s confident voice echoed from the other line. His tone was firm and it seemed as though he had made up his mind.

“Alright, I’ll be waiting for your news!” when Garen heard the other man’s words earlier, he could tell that Kendall truly planned to display his resolution during this business deal. The expenses and energy that was needed midway throughout the process to shorten the route by half of its required duration was not something that a regular small vendor could provide. It was clear that Kendall was planning to put in all of his effort to invest in this business. The important part was to flaunt his sincerity and cooperation abilities.

After he had disconnected from the terminal, Garen inhaled deeply.

“I need to make up for the shortcomings in my Willpower immediately. This world feels more complicated the deeper I dive in…”

He sat in front of the desk and turned his tablet computer on before beginning to do research on information regarding high-level fighting techniques.

Unfortunately, there were no web pages with related information as most of them were banned and taken down. Although they were a few websites with information regarding Mech battles, these things looked extremely inauthentic and did not possess great referencing values.

After spending a period of time in this world, Garen had unconsciously assimilated into this place gradually. The information regarding the greatest strength in this world was naturally the subject that he wished to understand the most.

He clicked through web pages continuously while looking for the related information on his computer. He relied on his hacking techniques, and although he was not very familiar with these converted techniques yet, it was still easy for him to find information.

After passing through conventional channels, Garen was able to find certain advanced information about certain Mech Pilot assessments quickly.

A white square frame was displayed on the light blue background of the screen. Inside the box, the assessment subjects that advanced Mech Pilots were supposed to go through were listed in neat rows.

‘Compulsory to achieve Level 4 in Willpower tests’

‘Possesses a suitable Mech that belongs solely to themselves’

‘More than one qualifying record’

‘Has been issued a certificate of qualification by authorized governmental branches’

“There is still no concrete information regarding strength comparisons,” Garen pushed his tablet away. “It’s clear that an administrator who is even more skilled than me is currently controlling the information here. My hacking techniques are only impressive compared to those of the average person. There is still a great difference between me and the real first-class hackers.” he was already aware of this matter.

“I was already used to powers that were equivalent to Fifth Star levels in the previous world. Right now, I really cannot adapt to such a weak body…” Garen furrowed his eyebrows and clicked on the battle network messaging client AL. This was a communications software that was similar to QQ which could only be used to connect battle networks.

He had a lot of good friends on the AL website. They were large clusters and groups of them, but he had not contacted many of them after adding them as contacts. Perhaps some of them had even deleted Nono’s number from their list of ‘good friends’ long ago.

Garen clicked on the friend list pane that marked his unknown contacts. There were two colorful avatar images that were blinking there. He glanced at these avatars but did not click the images to connect with them in the end. After all, these were Nono’s friends, not his.

There did not seem to be any messages in the bottom right corner of his AL page. Instead, there were only two advertisements from the AL officials.

This was the first time that Garen had used Nono’s number to look at his interpersonal circles.

There were only a few high school students in his circle of good friends and two groups of friends from elementary school. Next, there were his good friends Aier and Mina and his family members. Other than that, he did not seem to have any other relationship networks.

“This is so simple,” he randomly glanced through the messages from his circle of schoolmates and noticed that none of them were substantial. One circle was basically dead while the other one was much livelier. However, none of them mentioned Nonosiva, making it seem as if he was not part of the group at all. Even though he was currently an exceptional student of Blackboard Academy and now possessed an enviable identity, it seemed as though no one was aware of this, as the conversations inside the circle showed that none of these people knew of the situation at all.

After getting to know Nonosiva’s interpersonal circle, Garen understood the facts better now. He closed the AL tab and glanced at the Terminal before noticing that there were a bunch of unread messages on his Watch Terminal that came from an unknown number.

‘We’ve already seen your performance today. Someone will meet you at your place tonight to proceed with the registration. Looking forward to your cooperation. — Blue Narcissus (This message will delete itself automatically after it has been read)’

‘Notification regarding the arrangement of the individual matches. The matches will be organized in this manner: First round of the finals vs the eighth group of the Winners Bracket. Second round of the finals vs the sixth group of the Winners Bracket. Groups will be automatically allocated once the winners are determined.’ This notification was released by the academy.

Garen responded to Blue Narcissus before turning the lights off quietly. He sat cross-legged on his bed while practicing his training methods. No one would disturb him at this hour as Aier and the others knew that he would be taking part in the finals tomorrow. Therefore, it was important for him to rest now.

Time ticked by slowly.

The sound of slow footsteps could be heard outside the window faintly, coupled with the occasional noise of passing cars.

Garen immersed himself into his training methods. Although he could not sense any progress, practicing this was still better than sitting around lazily. The aptitude of this physical body was too mediocre, and sitting around in an elite school like Blackboard Academy while remaining indifferent would cause him to become inferior. If he was unable to fix this, Nonosiva would become useless during his senior year of high school even with the Moonfang. Next, he would be exposed for cheating and finally expelled from the Academy. After facing a blow like this, it would become extremely difficult for him to become a Mech Pilot for the rest of his life. However, for the students in the Academy, becoming a Mech Pilot was something that was bound to happen in time. This was the stark difference between them.

Knock knock.

A soft noise could be heard from the door to the room suddenly. It was not the sound of the doorbell, but a soft knocking noise instead.

Garen opened his eyes and got up before walking to the door. He looked outside through the peephole and saw a young woman in a cream-colored school uniform. The woman wore glasses and had long brown hair that was slung over her left shoulder and reached the front of her chest. She gave off a gentle air.

Garen opened the door with a ‘click’ before sizing up the other person faintly.

“You are?”

“I’m here to help you with the registration process,” the woman smiled casually.

“Please come in.”

Garen nodded and turned his body sideways so that she could enter.

“My name is Kris, and you are Nonosiva Lin, right?”

The young woman walked into the room and took in her surroundings before asking casually.

“What do we need to do?” Garen turned his head and immediately heard a crisp clicking noise. He happened to see Kris take a small camera-like object out before snapping his picture.

“We are registering your photograph. Please press your finger here for a while to register your fingerprint,” Kris took a tablet computer out and turned the screen towards Garen.

Garen stretched his hand out and pressed on the screen before a brief beeping noise could be heard from the computer suddenly.

“Okay, that’s all. We will specially create a membership badge for you soon. You just need to focus on the competition now,” Kris smiled.

“It’s so simple?” Garen was slightly surprised.

“It has always been this simple. There will be a three-dimensional image modeling scan after this. It will be done once you’ve entered. All of your personal information will be recorded in your archives since you’re a Grade C member of Blue Narcissus now,” Kris nodded.

“The next part will be key.”

“What?”

Garen gestured for her to sit before both of them sat on the two chairs beside the table together.

Kris lifted her legs slightly before moving backward and leaning against the back of the chair.

“Student Nono, regarding your opponent in the finals tomorrow, we have already listed certain information about their previous match records. You can find out some things about their strength levels so that you will be prepared. Besides that, as a member of Blue Narcissus, if you become an elite member, you will receive a membership card for Lyles General Hall. You will be able to enjoy many free services there such as gym facilities, entertainment, and lodging. The membership card that is worth a hundred thousand Universal Units yearly will also allow you to enjoy free consumer benefits throughout the whole Blackboard Region. It is equivalent to a converted bank card.”

“Such good treatment?” Garen was somewhat tongue-tied. They were willing to invest a hundred thousand Units on him without determining that he was actually sincere in joining Blue Narcissus. This was truly a bold move on their part.

“Of course, Lyles will also provide many other convenient communication services and hiring services for you. If you want to purchase certain contrabands, this can be done as well,” Kris smiled. “There are many restricted items outside but Lyles can supply these things, including land. As long as you are capable, you will definitely be able to accept employment opportunities from other people through this platform to earn a sizeable profit or side income.”

“This is very convenient…” Garen nodded slightly. Regarding the supposed contrabands, they were definitely referring to a few specific items such as drugs, military supplies, and… territories. Other than the Blackboard Region, there were many other territories that were owned by noble lordships. The nobles and lords once possessed legal territories, but after the chaotic period, in order to exchange their land to develop more technological resources, it was excusable for most of them to sell a portion of their territories. The law had prohibited the buying and selling of territorial lands. However, everyone was already aware of the real situation. No one cared about these matters, and no one was powerful enough to control it anyway.

Chapter 802: Pressure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Territory… Really…?” Garen’s emotions were slightly moved. If he was able to obtain a territory of his own and become a noble lord, the land would merely be secondary as the truly important benefits and rights that he would gain from this was that many illegal matters would become legal through the right of a noble lord. This was the most important thing to him.

“You’re probably aware that although many territories are actually extremely small areas, all of them are still very valuable. Therefore, there are still many people who scramble after these territories madly despite being unable to find a way to purchase them. Meanwhile, Blue Narcissus provides a means for our own internal members to obtain this land as a benefit. Neither Black Rose nor Thousand Year Tree provides this benefit. This is something that only Blue Narcissus has specially obtained,” Kris could see Garen’s fervent interest towards these territories.

“Looks like I’ve made a wise decision,” Garen smiled.

“Of course,” Kris took out a pendrive that looked like a gold pendant the size of a fingernail. It looked like a shell-shaped piece of jewelry. “All of this is information. I’ll be leaving first. May you be victorious in your match tomorrow!” she stood up.

“Thank you very much,” Garen stood up as well and nodded.

Kris shook Garen’s hand lightly before turning around and exiting the door.

Once she heard the clicking noise of the door shutting behind her, she nodded towards a young man who was waiting in the corridor. Both of them walked together and left the new students’ dorm.

“How did it go?” the male student was also dressed in a cream-colored school uniform. This was the uniform of Grade B. Meanwhile, the students of Grade C wore pure white uniforms.

“It was very strange. This Nonosiva was completely unlike the rumors. He gave off an air of experience,” a faintly surprised expression had appeared on Kris’ face. “I felt as if I was dealing with an old man. He spoke steadily and remained indifferent the entire time. He did not seem like a young person at all.”

“Isn’t that a good thing? If he possesses good potential, just form a close relationship with him. There are many students in the Academy who can pretend like this. You don’t need to be shocked,” said the male student while smiling.

“I don’t think he’s pretending…” Kris furrowed her eyebrows slightly. “He just gives off an extremely strange air. Realistically speaking, he should feel some pressure at least since the final match is about to begin. However, I noticed that his mental state could not be better.”

“Alright, stop overthinking. These things aren’t related to us. It will be even better if this Nono has good potential.”

“You’re right,” Kris nodded and changed the subject. “What should we have for supper tonight?”

“Let’s go take a look. We ate things with a lot of calories during lunch so I don’t really feel like eating now.”

Both of them walked down the road that was lined with street lights under the night sky. They resembled the other student couples that snuggled closely next to each other. Frankly, they did not look any different from the rest at all.

****************

Whoosh!

Garen pulled the curtains together and sat in front of the computer. All of the hard drive’s contents had been downloaded offline into the tablet computer.

There were four files in total and he opened one to investigate it carefully.

The state of the finals was immediately displayed in front of him. Compared to the academy’s simple announcement about the match, the information here was clearly more abundant.

Moreover, the thing that caught Garen’s attention was not the class rankings but the individual rankings instead.

Once they had reached this stage, class C5 had already secured their position in the top ten. However, overtaking the next few positions would be a problem. The subsequent fighting matches would all be Total Defeat Matches.

‘Total Defeat Matches refer to matches where victories will only be determined once all of the competitors on the other side have been defeated.’

‘Three-on-three matches will be held. The previous rule of three wins out of two matches has been abolished. The new standard states that all of the members of the opposing team must be defeated before a winner is determined.’

‘This decision has taken the final match into consideration, as well as the strength of the entire group and the Elite competitors. The Total Defeat model is used to create a strength assessment that is ultimately fair.’

‘The final match will split the first three competitors into three melee groups. This will ensure that the three strongest competitors from the individual battles will form three groups of powerful individuals. Therefore, each person will be given one chance to challenge…’

Garen glanced through the information continuously while time ticked by.

Unconsciously, the night sky became darker. Numerous videos of his opponents for the next day were attached to this information. They were arranged in detail and Garen was fully absorbed when he watched them.

The more he watched, the more apprehensive he became.

The weakest opponent that he would face tomorrow was already at the same level as London, whom he had encountered today. None of them had any weaknesses and were all characters with sharp minds. Although it seemed as though they lacked fighting experience, each of them was still able to use specialized techniques that were combined with their Willpower. Their unusually powerful levels had exceeded Garen’s expectations and imagination.

One of his opponent’s information stated that he had previously used a Willpower move known as the Electric Wave Hammer.

The Electric Wave Hammer was an external Willpower weapon that was produced by integrating one’s Willpower and Mech to release a warhammer-like force field that could not be seen or touched. However, it could pass through Mech armor to injure the opposing pilot’s somatic functions directly. Opponents who possessed Willpower levels that were similar to his own were the only ones who could detect and see the Electric Wave Hammer prior to its attack. Therefore, they would be able to dodge or defend themselves from it. Meanwhile, they could only defend themselves if they possessed specialized measures.

After going through it carefully, Garen understood this technique was not considered as the strongest among the Level 2 or higher techniques. There were other powerful techniques that could only be used if one’s Willpower was strong enough. For instance, the Willpower Slicing Blade, another opponent’s finishing blow that possessed great destructive power. When facing opponents whose Willpower was much weaker than his own, he could simply destroy them within a second. One direct strike against the body of his opposing Mech Pilot would form a sharp attack that resembled knife wounds.

“How troublesome,” Garen’s eyebrows were furrowed. After coming to this world, he had always retained a strong ego. Although this place was a tremendously technologically advanced world, he still felt as if it was far from the Ancient Endorian Secret Technique civilizations in terms of developing his potential. However, he had now realized that the paths that were opened up by Willpower were not inferior to those of Ancient Endor in terms of strength…

“These are two civilizations that are going in different directions. It looks like I’ll have to be careful in the future,” after looking at the specific effects of these highly destructive moves, Garen stopped belittling them completely before acknowledging the Willpower strength systems properly.

“How would I compete with these techniques that were solely based on Willpower?” although it had been explained in the information, Willpower techniques that could pass through Mechs and injure the Mech Pilots directly were extremely rare. Moreover, they would consume a lot of the attacker’s Willpower as well. Therefore, they could only be used in close proximity. Most of them were techniques that were integrated with one’s Mech to produce more powerful forces. Meanwhile, just because other techniques were rarer did not mean that were non-existent.

Garen purposely selected the information regarding Willpower techniques before searching online again.

‘Willpower fights are slightly similar to mental strength fights. They are not always valuable as they require a large contribution for low returns. Moreover, they can only be used for one-on-one combat. There are many limitations and conditions as well. In long distances in outer space, these abilities are not very useful as the Mech Pilot’s Willpower will not be able to surpass the level of high energy particle winds and the great distance between themselves and their enemies to be able to hit them precisely. Therefore, this technique is mainly used for ground-level combat.’

Garen became more apprehensive as he continued reading. If he encountered techniques that were purely based on Willpower in situations where it was impossible for him to detect them as they could neither be seen nor felt, there would be no way for him to counter his opponent’s direct attack. He had simulated this in his mind numerous times but he could not even win five times in the end. This was also done in the situation where the Moonfang could be used unlimited times.

His mood was becoming slightly more serious.

“Seems like I can only aim for the top three spots at most…”

From this information, he had also discovered that Mech Pilots whose Willpower had reached Level 3 could use these techniques in their normal lives. In other words, they could still use these dangerous techniques despite separating themselves from their Mechs. This was also one of the main reasons why Level 2 Mech Pilots were well-respected by others.

****************

Blackboard Academy’s simulated battleground

Caus and the other red-haired male student sat across each other at the rest area. They watched the roaring Mechs clashing outside the glass window continuously while drinking purified fruit essence.

The ruby-like essence was sucked upwards through the straw inside the glass cup and gave off a glass-like luster when light shone on it.

“All of the information you wanted is here. Moreover, that guy has joined Blue Narcissus as well,” the red-haired male student passed a piece of paper with information over.

Caus took it and put his cup down before beginning to flip through and read it slowly.

“I did not intend to use tricks initially as secret maneuvers are meaningless. Isn’t it better to publicly beat him up until he becomes a begging dog that kneels before me in front of everyone in the arena?” he smiled.

“You’re certainly in high spirits,” said the red-haired male student while yawning. “I also have the assessment that I got from the leaves over there.”

“What are the comments?”

“Just the usual General Excellence level grades.”

“Oh? He defeated a good number of Excellent level opponents consecutively, so why was he awarded such a low grade? General Excellence only means that he is an outstanding student within his own class in the entire academy,” Caus was now interested.

“This fellow Nonosiva has a fatal weakness,” the red-haired male student straightened one of his index fingers. “It’s his Willpower! It’s too weak.”

Caus seemed lost in thought suddenly.

“Did you notice? When Nonosiva fights, he never uses fighting techniques that need to be combined with Willpower. Moreover, he’s well-known for using two out of the three main techniques that don’t require Willpower. What does this mean?” said the red-haired male student confidently.

“This means that his Willpower is extremely weak. It’s so weak that he’s unwilling to even consume a tiny bit of it. Otherwise, it will probably affect his endurance during the battle matches,” Caus nodded faintly while a glimmer of understanding flashed across his eyes. “In other words, I’m planning to attack his weak point.”

“Two tactics,” said the red-haired male student while raising two fingers. “If he’s able to charge at you from the front, you have two choices. The first one is to use your Willpower Techniques to get rid of him. The second one is to drag him out slowly to his death. Compared to that Impregnable Wall London, your defense techniques have almost reached Level 3. Furthermore, you are almost on par with Merseus in this aspect. You can actually play with him until he dies.”

A smile appeared on Caus’ face suddenly.

The red-haired male student glanced at him wordlessly.

“To be honest, I really don’t understand you. You could get rid of that guy in one go with your Stunt Phantom Beam Blade. You could even disable him easily by cutting off a limb if you didn’t want to kill him. Does it make sense to use such a powerful weapon against a normal student?”

“He almost murdered my older brother. What do you think?” Caus glared at him coldly.

“Don’t glare at me. I was just saying,” the red-haired male student shrugged and yawned. His gaze suddenly shifted towards a little red gadget on Caus’ shirt collar. “F*ck! You’re actually planning to bring this gadget into the arena even though you’re only going up against a normal student who hasn’t even reached Level 2?!”

He was momentarily stunned. He had always known that Caus was despicable but never expected that he could be much worse than he had imagined.

“Safety first,” Caus smiled and flipped the little gadget inside his collar to shield it.

“Really… Caus, this is the first time that I’ve thought you were exceptionally despicable.”

“Thank you for the compliment.”

“Willpower Booster… And a hidden version as well…” The red-haired male student was finally speechless when he saw the other person keeping the red square item. They were allowed to use this item, and even Merseus and Bally would realistically possess one for themselves. However, they would not use it during unimportant periods because of two reasons. Firstly, this item was consumable and very precious. Secondly, extended periods of usage would cause them to become dependent on it.

This gadget was like a stimulant that would be consumed before a long-distance race. It could be hidden so that it would not be easily discovered. Moreover, it would also produce certain amplifying effects towards their Willpower. However, the effects would be weaker when it was used on higher level Willpower.

Despite possessing Level 2 Willpower now, Caus was still unable to let go of such a minor booster.

Chapter 803: Advancement 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As night approached.

Garen sat on his bed as he inhaled and exhaled quietly.

The light wasn’t switched on in the room. Everything was pitched black, and through the tree leaves and branches outside, one could faintly see the lights from the streets blinking from afar.

The Watch Terminal on Garen’s wrist suddenly lit up.

Beep beep…

He immediately opened his eyes, raised up the watch and the contact number was shown. It was Kendall.

“He finally calls,” he gave a sigh of relief as he answered the call.

Kendall’s head appeared on the terminal.

“The stock has arrived. Do you want me to send it directly to your place?” the beardy uncle’s eyes were red and he looked very tired.

“I’ll meet you outside the entrance of the academy,” Garen nodded. “Thank you for your hard work.”

“It’s fine, just prepare the Universal Points,” the beardy uncle gulped down huge amounts of water. “I’ll be there in about ten minutes or so.”

“I’ll go out now.”

“It’s a truck numbered c563171.”

“Understood.”

Garen hung up the terminal and swiftly donned his coat uniform. He then grabbed his keys and left the dorm.

It was extremely cold and quiet outside and no one could be seen moving about at all. He looked at the time and it was two hours and forty-two minutes past midnight. Almost all of the students had already fallen asleep.

As he walked out of his dorm, the cold wing welcomed him. The street lights formed a line by the side of the road, stretching it into the darkness. Moonlight wasn’t present as it was covered by the clouds.

Garen wasn’t able to differentiate the direction as he walked towards the illuminated streets.

He walked across the field in the academy. The academy’s buildings stood silently as if it was a huge black box placed on the land. Some had some electronic lights blinking on them while some were completely dark.

As he arrived at the emergency area, Garen took out a coin and placed it into a coin box for a white academy car.

The white academy car suddenly lit up and the driver’s dashboard turned green as it rang.

‘Welcome to using the Blackboard Academy’s car, please enter your destination,’ a female robotic voice rang loud and clear in the quiet night.

“Number 1 Gate Entrance,” Garen sat in the passenger seat.

‘Please fasten your seatbelt and press # to confirm once more.’

Garen started laughing as he heard her because he recalled the days back on Earth where the phone would say the same thing as well.

He sat down before the car activated and started moving along the road inside the quiet academy.

Along the road, he occasionally stumbled upon some students who came back late at this hour. Some of them were so tipsy that they slept in the academy’s car. There even were couples who were groping one another in the car without any shame or fear of people seeing them.

However, there were very little people present.

After ten minutes or so, the pitched black number 1 gate came into sight.

There were levitating vehicles from the outsiders parked at the entrance. The Academy’s car beeped twice as it reached the entrance.

‘We have arrived at the destination. Please leave the car.’

Garen jumped down from the car and walked out of the gate as he squirmed through the gaps between the levitating cars. Further out there was a lively night market with many blinking lights. The whole area was filled with yellow and red lights, music and the sizzling sounds of a midnight barbeque.

There were a lot of people on the streets who were enjoying their supper. Some of them were drinking while talking about random stuff while there were some who were about to leave the area. There were also people who had just arrived. A portion of these people were students from the academy as they were in the Blackboard’s uniform.

Garen looked around and saw a middle-aged man in a thick coat exhaling white vapor at the side of the street.

Behind this man was an old black car. He stood beside the car as he kept rubbing both of his hands. His nose was red and he kept taking out tissue paper to blow his nose.

He towards him and gently tapped the man’s shoulder from behind.

“Ahhh…!!” The middle-aged man was startled as he turned around quickly. He gave a sigh of relief when he saw that it was Garen.

“Don’t you know you can scare out my soul like that!” Kendall looked very fragile as if he had lost a lot of weight. “I’m sorry I couldn’t attend your competition as the location was quite far away this time. However, the quality of the items are good so I went a little further than usual.”

“Thanks for your hard work,” Garen felt bad as he realized that Kendall was doing his best for him. He also could see that he was very sincere towards him this time around. “Let’s go find a place and drink.”

“Everything’s on you!” Kendall immediately said so.

“Fine. I’ll treat you,” Garen didn’t care in the least as he gestured his hand.

He locked the car and then they proceeded towards a drinking place that was still open and requested for a single room.

The white drinking place’s environment was pretty good and the noise isolation of the single room was pretty good as well. As the majority of the Blackboard Academy’s students were rich and didn’t care how much they spent as long as they enjoyed themselves, the shops just outside the academy were very expensive but the quality and services were top notch.

Piping hot milk and coffee were soon served to them along with a few almond cakes. The yellow and soft cakes looked very delicious and there were even fresh red cherries placed at the center of the cakes as well.

“Please enjoy yourself,” the young female worker bowed smoothly before leaving the room.

“Alright let’s hear it. How many have you gotten this time?” Garen sipped on the coffee. This world had a drink that was similar to coffee. Although it had a lot of other drinks available, he preferred the drinks he was used to as this brought forth a slight nostalgia.

Kendall slurped down the whole cup of coffee and stuffed the cakes into his mouth as swallowed them whole before taking a breather.

“The total amount is two thousand five hundred and sixty-two pieces. The quality will not disappoint you! I’ve taken all of these from a few merchants who sell these white stones. I even bought their items for the whole season!”

He then took out a white stone from his shirt and passed it to him.

“Take a look at it. This is a sample that I’ve taken out from the stash.”

The moment Garen got hold of it, he instantly felt that the White Peacock Stone essence within the stone was much purer than the previously obtained one. This meant that there were less impurities and the high energy fuel and white peacock stones were more concentrated.

He raised the stone up and placed it by the light as he carefully examined it.

“Nice. Where are the others?”

“It’s in the car outside. There’re at least two thousand of these and it’s huge!” Kendall took up a wet napkin to wipe the dirt off his face.

“I need to check the rest.”

“Of course.”

Garen wasn’t in a hurry so he waited for Kendall to rest for a while more and had something to eat while checking his the current amount of his Universal Units. He had been earning his Universal Units through the battlenet and had earned about fourteen thousands six hundred Universal Units from the countless of games that he had played.

There were a total of 2562 pieces of the stones. If each stone costs 5 units, then he would need a total of 12810 units.

This was a huge sum of money. Kendall, who had forked out his money beforehand to buy this huge amount of white stones, had taken a huge risk. Ten thousand universal units were considered a few months’ salaries for a small timer like him. If Garen were to reject all of these stones, he would have been at a loss. You could say that Kendall had wholly invested in Garen with the utmost sincerity.

After Kendall had finished eating the food and rested for a full ten minutes, Garen then stood up and walked towards his car to check the material.

All two thousand of the stones were of good quality unlike last time, where there were a few fake ones. This made Garen very satisfied with him. With his Peacock Technique, he could instantly know the quality of the stone by just pressing on it. With his hands, he had examined the stones in no time.

Two of them then walked back into the single room and sat down.

Without any hesitation, Garen immediately sent 13000 points to Kendall, leaving himself only 1600 points.

“You can keep the change. Take it as the reward for your risk.”

Kendall didn’t reject it and accepted it with all his heart. He knew that Garen was the standard person who didn’t care about money from his previous encounter. This time around he decided to show his sincerity so that he could earn his rightful amount.

“I still have another thing I need to raise to you,” he continued after receiving the Universal Units.

“What is it?” Garen took up a dessert and ate it slowly.

“All of the merchants were shocked that when I wanted such a huge amount of Rainbow Stones. You have to understand that those who really wanted the high energy fuel from these ingredients would never use the Rainbow Stones as it contains too many impurities. Furthermore, it’s simply not profitable if they were to increase their price. Hence the sales of these stones were mediocre at best. However, with the number of stones I’ve purchased from them, the owner caught wind of it and wanted to meet the true purchaser of the Rainbow Stones in person,” Kendall explained honestly. “I’m not certain if you still want these stones in the future but if you do… it’s better to establish a long-term partnership.”

Garen crossed his fingers. The reason he purchased these Rainbow Stones was to train his technique. Although the Hellfrost Peacock Technique would not require these stones in the future, it could still enhance the training process and it was very important to him as it could bring him back to his strength within the shortest time frame.

Currently, he wasn’t lacking in Secret Techniques nor Secret Methods. The only thing he was lacking was energy accumulation, and the Rainbow Stones were able to fill this hole.

“That man is trying to bypass you to make a trade directly with me. Are you not concerned that I will bypass you?” Garen felt rather puzzled and fired back a question.

Kendall smiled.

“The only good point about me is that I know my worth. I’m not needed in this business and if you were to bypass me and deal with him directly, I’m fine with that since I’m not in the loss at all.”

He was very sincere and truthful towards Garen.

Garen smiled back.

“How about this. I may still need your help in the future. Our chances of working together are still plenty so you don’t have to worry at all. I’ll take these items for the time being so you can wait for my news.”

“No problem!” Kendall nodded as he sent the source owner’s number to Garen. He then sat comfortably on the chair. “You can go back first as I still need to rest a bit more. You don’t get to have a rich person treating you to this place often and I wouldn’t even dare to enter this expensive place! It’s simply not worth it to leave within such a short amount of time.”

Garen shook his head and stood up, speechless. “Alright, then you should take a good rest. I will call you once the finals are over.”

“I’ll wait for your news,” Kendall waved his hand.

Garen paid for the bill and walked out of the shop. He then walked towards the car and took out a big sack of stones. The sack was very dense but due to his physical changes, it wasn’t too heavy for him.

With the package in hand, he swiftly returned to the academy, sat in an academy’s car, threw in a coin and went back to his dorm.

There were no hiccups between the journey and by the time he had reached his dorm, it was already four o’clock. As the final would start at nine in the morning, he still had another five hours before the competition started. Although Garen only slept for a few hours, he felt very refreshed.

Chapter 804: Advancement 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After returning to his dorm, Garen pulled his curtains shut, locked the door and immediately took out the bottle that had been used to store the high energy fuel powder. This time, he had prepared a huge number of bottles to store them.

It was the same procedure as before.

He spread out a huge cloth and poured the stones onto it before he took off his shirt and sat on his knees in front of the stones.

This time, the amount and quality of the stones far exceed the previous ones.

After finishing his preparation, he closed his eyes as he slowly adjusted the Living Secret Technique’s Seed inside of him, which was the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s core. In an instant, his body was covered in a mysterious blue layer, as a sense of coolness spread out his body. The temperature of the room started to drop slowly.

He reached out his hands and gently placed them in front of the stones.

Crack. Two of the stones that were lightly touched by him rolled down and turned into two piles of white dust before it reached the cloth.

Then, the pile of stones started to break down, disintegrate and turned into white dust that slipped through the gaps between the stones

The sound of the falling sand kept rustling inside the room.

Garen started to observe the overall changes in his body.

He felt that his body was like a deflated balloon that was being inflated without rest. Under his supervision, the series of blue frost lines quickly flowed into his palm. It was different from the last time where he did not require to use the frost blue lines in his body. The White Peacock Stone’s essence would naturally be absorbed into his palms and it seemed to be much safer as well.

As huge amounts of frost stream entered into his body, they were absorbed by the blue lines in his body and kept flowing through the five elements of his body.

These icy blue lines had automatically formed a complex web inside his body. It didn’t follow the path of the meridians, arteries nor the nervous system. In fact, it had formed its own route independent of the other two major systems. It seemed to have created a new biological system of its own with the seed of the living secret technique as its core.

As Garen observed the automatic circulatory system of the seed of the living secret technique, he finally understood the principles behind it.

As time passed, he noticed that the Hellfrost Peacock Technique in his attribute pane started to change.

‘Secret technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique, Living Secret technique of unknown origin. Second grade Heart Reformation. The heart shall be reformed with the Hellfrost Peacock as the standard in order to improve the overall physical attributes of the body. Time required: Two months and six days.’

‘Third grade’s progress at 25%’

This was the previous data that Garen had seen. However, as the huge amount of frost streams entered his body, the third grade’s progress bar started to turn muddy.

As the cold stream was absorbed into and started moving around his body, Garen could feel that the stream had entered into his heart, giving him a new strength. Countless frost lines gathered by his heart and with every frost line inserted into his heart, he gained a new momentum.

Bam!

A clear and crisp sound could be heard from the heart.

However, it was this sound that indicated that the third grade’s progress of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had increased.

‘Third-grade progress is at 26%.’

“It increased!” Garen was slightly excited.

Immediately, the progression bar started to increase at an increasing pace.

27%… 28%… 29%… 31%…

The value kept increasing at a steady pace. As the huge amount of frost lines entered the heart, Garen could clearly feel that his heart was becoming stronger and stronger, to the point his chest was about to burst.

He stared at the progression bar as it reached 40%, 60%, 80% and finally 90%!

Suddenly Garen felt as if his heart had been torn apart as a muffled splash was heard.

He opened his eyes and looked down at his chest. It was glowing blue, so brightly so that the light penetrated through his ribs and muscles. It shone so brightly that it gave off a weird vibe in the dark room.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s Heart Transformation enhancement has ended, third grade’s progression has reached 100%.’

The instant he saw this sentence, Garen felt an excruciating pain emitting from his chest. The pain was so excruciating that it was similar to someone twisting his heart or even scratching on it. The pain was transmitted to his brain, surpassing every pain that he’d ever felt in his entire existence.

However, since Garen was once the strongest being of the worlds he’d once lived in, he naturally wasn’t afraid of such pain.

As the second grade’s heart transformation was completed and reached the end of third grade, the pain was most likely due to the extremely shortened duration of the time-consuming process of reforming his body.

He endured the pain as he sat quietly in front of the stone while the stones slowly turned into a pile of white dust.

After some time, he regained consciousness. He was sweating profusely and felt extremely tired but his body was better than before.

“It finally ended…”

Garen loosened up the moment he saw his attribute pane.

“Finally there’s a qualitative change.”

At a glance, his body seemed to have changed completely and it was the first time that it had a qualitative change.

‘Nonosiva. Lin — Strength 1.7, Agility 1.5, Vitality 18, Intelligence 1.5. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 40’

‘Potential Quality — Void Hunter’

‘Soul Seed — Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water technique, Holy Phoenix Demonic Book.’

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock technique: Living Secret Technique of unknown origin. With the Hellfrost Peacock’s bloodline as the standard to reform the heart to achieve an enhanced body. Time required: Completed.’

The third grade had completely reformed his stomach to match the peacock’s swallowing ability. In combination with the stomach’s ability to take up almost any sort of item and the heart’s reformation, he had gained the ability to eat everything.

‘Obtained a natural ability — Devour (Hellfrost Peacock Technique has opened up the basic powerful ability of the Queen of Peacock)’

‘Fourth grade progression at 11%.’

‘(A total of five grades of foundations and three grades of derivative level) With every progression of a grade, the body will cleanse the blood to gradually acclimate towards the Hellfrost Peacock’s constitution. It will eventually reach its highest form, and its limit is at Army Level.’

‘Imprint of Steel: to enhance one’s body to increase his strength and vitality.’

“There’s an average increment in all attributes. Although it isn’t much, Strength has increased considerably, Agility has increased by 0.3, Vitality by 1 point and Intelligence being the least, which is only about 0.1. However, the main dish of today’s result is the natural ability…” Garen’s vision was on the new icon at the back of the Secret Technique. It was an icon that represented his latest natural ability, Devour.

As his vision landed on it, information was immediately sent to his consciousness.

‘Queen of Peacock’s Devour — A unique devour ability from the Hellfrost Peacock. One can devour most materials to improve one’s physical characteristics. The impurities that were devoured can be stored, condensed and formed into a Distorted Seed that can infect other beings.’

“Distorted Seed? Infection?”

Not only did his physical characteristics improve upon achieving grade three, he also had obtained an additional Devour ability. It was obvious that this natural ability must have a unique effect.

He shifted his gaze to the Distorted seed.

‘Distorted Seed: the Hellfrost Peacock is naturally able to release a very strong radiation from its body, which is able to distort the status of any living being near it, infecting them into a strange battle machine that has no consciousness. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique mimics this ability by emitting this radiation to distort the material into a Distorted Seed that can infiltrate into the enemy’s heart without detection. It would then turn them into a powerful killing monster. The radiation would increase their attribute by roughly 1.5 times.’

Garen couldn’t help but frown as he read the message.

“This ability will be very useful during a war but in this world where wars are between planets… I wouldn’t be able to get close to the enemy with this ability.”

He continued reading to find out more about the effects of the Distorted Seed.

‘…In order for the Hellfrost Peacock to cleanse itself and its surroundings, it releases the radiation to pollute the surrounding environment. The Distorted Seed’s presence will kill anything other than the Hellfrost Peacock. The slain beings will then explode, releasing a stench into the air and surroundings, giving off a strong radiation to the surroundings.’

“It’s indeed useless…” Garen’s frown deepened. “Let’s look at the enhancement effect of Devour.”

He reorganized the Living Secret technique’s seed to extract the information of the Devour ability that had been previously locked. Suddenly Devour’s information changed once more.

‘Queen of Peacock’s Devor– There is nothing the Hellfrost Peacock is unable to digest. It is able to devour metal, alloy, woods, living beings, stones, and liquid. If your vitality is strong enough, you can even devour lava. All the energy obtained through digestion can be used to create the Distorted Seed and enhance one’s body. The enhancement maximum effect is to increase the original attribute by five points. Once one had reached the advanced stage, one can even release the frost to freeze the enemy, giving birth to a new derivative ability called Freezing.’

Most of the information was useless to him.

“With me being in the interplanetary era, the Distorted Seed is rather ineffective. On the other hand, the ability to freeze my opponent by devouring items to reach the advanced stage is definitely useful.”

Garen looked at the effect of Freezing and found out that it had a long range of at least a hundred meters. He could also apply it to weapons to shoot it out. When he applied it to the guns, he could deal damage and freeze his opponent at the same time.

With so much information at hand, Although the Secret Technique was still in its foundation phase, the potential that it revealed was considered good. It’s just that it didn’t suit the world he was currently in.

However, he had an endless supply of impure White Peacock Stones. With the next level up, he was confident that a stronger ability would appear, which made him very excited about what’s to come.

“Next up is the most important part,” Garen stood up and put on his shirt. His body was cold and was giving off a faint aroma. “Once I’ve reached the third grade, how much has it affect my Willpower? This is the main point…”

Chapter 805: Opponent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He closed his eyes once again and calmed himself down. Garen’s vision fell onto the part where it stated his Willpower.

‘Willpower — Middle Basic Level,

(Training method: Blackboard Manipulation. Blackboard Academy’s training method is free of charge. However, continuous training would result in weaker effects. The speed of progress would be one level for every twelve years)’

“Is that still on the Middle Level?” Garen frowned slightly. But just at that moment, a faint cold current slowly trickled down into his upper abdomen, the first position of his practiced Willpower.

The moment the cold current entered his upper abdomen, his Willpower’s Skill Pane finally changed a little.

Suddenly, it was as if the words of the Middle Basic Level jumped about. It went blur for a while, and then it became clearer once again. However, the words had now turned into Upper Level.

‘Willpower — Upper Basic Level, (to strengthen the increase of a certain level of Living Secret Technique)’

“It has an effect!” Garen relaxed. According to his deduction and analysis, the first position of the training method is the upper abdomen which is also the stomach. Hence, the Living Secret Technique should be able to strengthen the quality of his whole body. Naturally, his stomach would definitely strengthen too, and it would be affecting the training method of Willpower. After all, Willpower came from the awareness field that gathered all the cells. If all the cells had strengthened, then the increase of Willpower was without a doubt.

“If in that case, in the meantime, while I’m practicing the Living Secret Technique, my Willpower will definitely increase,” He sighed with relief. He was afraid that the Living Secret Technique would not affect Willpower at all.

He then checked the slight magnitude increase of Willpower.

At first, he was close to achieving the Upper Level. Now that he had been promoted to the Upper Level, he was almost at the top of this level.

In fact, the different levels were just a way of dividing each range of category. Even the middle had it’s gap. The increase of Living Secret technique this time had also directly increased his level of Willpower. Even though Upper Basic Level would not achieve the same standard as Level 1 and it could not freely control a mech, compared to before, this was a huge improvement.

“At least there is hope.” Garen started putting the impurities of the White Peacock Stone powder into the bottle. This power was still mixed with some other mineral impurities, but it was much easier to collect when compared to before. With slight processing, then he would be able to extract the expensive high-energy fuel powder. When the time comes, he could then solve his money issues very quickly.

Garen saw the terminal on his watch. On the top, there were only about few thousand Universal Units left; with so little money, he had almost spent it all without noticing. Even worse, he had spent two hundred over Units for buying someone dinner. Now, he only had 1402 left.

“I have to think of ways to earn money. If I can make another batch of White Peacock Stone next time, then I should be able to breakthrough Level 1. But I would not be able to make it now. I just had a breakthrough and I still need time to stabilize. I also don’t have money to buy enough White Rainbow Stone,” Garen did a mental calculation.

He then looked at the bottles of powder that were ready.

“These powder will be able to earn me some money, but I need to have a reasonable cover up. Otherwise, how can I, a mere scholar separate such high-energy fuel powder? Once people start realizing this cheap technique I use, it would be a crime!”

The only place that can separate such high-energy fuel powder is…

“The laboratory, a biochemical plant, research base, and more. Only these places with high precision technology can achieve this separation of fuel.”

Garen pondered.

“How can I put on this layer of leather?”

On one hand, he did not have a clue as to how he could do it. If he built his own laboratory but he did not have connections with strong capital resources, then he did not even need to think about it. However, a laboratory was the third cheapest option out of all.

For a moment, he tossed that idea out of his head. Garen looked at the time, where the sky was slightly brighter. Even though he did not sleep for the most of the night, but he was still very awake. It seemed like the advanced Peacock Technique had also strengthened his vitality.

He simply woke up and straight away took a shower. After that, he sat cross-legged on the bed and started practicing the training method.

In such a meditational-like state, time passed by very quickly. In the blink of an eye, the alarm he had set on his Watch Terminal started ringing.

When Garen opened his eyes, he could already vaguely hear scholars’ talking and footsteps as they passed by. He could also make out the sparsely beeping horns of the suspended vehicles that constantly came in from the outside.

He let out a long sigh. Garen could feel the Willpower in his body that still had not reacted. From that feeling, he knew that this time’s training method had not much of an effect and it was far less refreshing than absorbing the White Peacock Stone.

“It seems like money is the most important thing at this point.”

Very quickly, Instructor Hamm had called.

“How are you? How was your rest?” Instructor Hamm’s chubby face appeared on his Watch Terminal. His face also carried a hint of drunken flush; his hair was in a mess. It looked like he did not sleep after the celebration last night.

“I’m good,” Garen nodded his head. “Instructor, you guys did not celebrate the whole night, did you?”

“Ha… Let’s not mention that. Do your best today. To be honest, I don’t think I can be as satisfied as I am calling you now. After this, no matter if you win or lose, we have already won! Don’t put too much pressure on yourself,” Hamm cheerfully waved his hand.

“I understand. All I have to do is put in all my effort — I will do my best,” Garen understandingly nodded his head.

“As long as you understand, it’s good enough. You should quickly come out for breakfast. I’ll hang up first.”

“Okay.”

After he hung up, Garen looked at his SMS messages. There were his parents’ messages — encouraging him to do his best in the competition, be aware of his safety, don’t be too hard on himself. Then, it was his siblings’ congratulatory messages, as well as some of Aier and Mina’s congratulations and questions.

Once he was done with all his replies, Garen blow-dried his hair, and immediately put on his Moonfang before he left.

Outside, the entire school was broadcasting the review of the final’s results. Garen avoided those that were not relevant, and only picked out the important ones.

“In the semi-finals of this Qualifier Match, Merseus used the Level 3 technique of a triple beam gun to suppress Nobis’s red shield. Finally, she broke the limit with an easy victory using the back raid ion jammer. That was the third time Merseus had demonstrated the Level 3 technique. Does this indicate that she is about the enter Level 3’s general standard? Even if we use our Blackboard’s criterion, Level 3’s standard is considered an Instructor’s level of standard. Since she was young, Merseus was already a talent. When she was ten or more, she could activate her Willpower and practiced the toughest development of the Hourglass training method. Even at nineteen-years-old, she could break through to the standard of Level 3. This speed of progress…”

After that, it was a series of words that praised Merseus. Merseus, this young female scholar who was in the same class, and had such unbeatable strength and figure such that she had already been imprinted into the minds of all the scholars who were in the same class.

While Garen was walking, he was eating a nutritious meal that he bought at the road-side shop — a bread, milk box, and a nutritious ball. These were artificially produced by synthesizing grain supplies. Although it looked like bread and milk, in reality, it is not. Instead, it is a replicated product. The real and natural food products were really expensive. For an average family, they would only be able to afford it during special occasions.

Since the exploitation of various high-energy fuels, the rapid development of scientific and technological civilization, and the reckless destruction of the war, it has caused the planet’s ecological environment to worsen. The disadvantage it brought was that food could only be synthesized, just like drugs. Otherwise, there would not be enough food to go around. The pressure of the population was so huge that even things such as hybrid grains were useless.

Along the path to the Academy, he got onto the Academy’s car and went straight to the Arena.

The Arena was almost full, half filled with a crowd. Most of them were scholars’ parents, who rushed here from the outside just to watch the battle. Nonosiva’s parents were working in the outer states; his younger brother was working, or maybe he did not come because he was afraid, and his sister had disappeared all day. He did not know what was going on too.

“Hey, I’m here.”

When he walked into the Arena, Kendall’s voice came from the upper right side. Following the sound, Garen looked up and could not believe that this bastard really did come into the Academy to watch the battle.

He waved at him and immediately walked towards the area where the contestants would enter into the field.

The Arena was getting livelier. There weren’t a lot of remaining contestants. When Caus, Bally, Merseus, and more entered the field, they attracted a lot of attention.

After going through the same prompts as before, the competition officially began.

Garen sat quietly in his contestant area, eating the breakfast in his hands. As the synthesized food went into his stomach, he used the ability from the Peacock Technique to swallow.

When he swallowed, he could feel the food in his stomach digesting at a stunning speed. He stuffed a bread, that was the size of his fist, into his mouth. Within half a minute, it was completely digested as if he had not eaten at all.

When he finished eating, he then drank four bottles of nutrient solution under both Fervale’s and Sara’s shocked gaze. The solution flushed into his stomach like it was a bottomless pit; no one could even see the bloating of his stomach.

Garen himself felt a little weird too. But he could feel the insides of his body, the lower part of his stomach, vaguely storing a cold liquid thing. As his food intake increased, the thing became bigger and bigger.

“In the meantime, while the swallowing ability increases the magnitude of the body’s quality, it can also condense the produced impurities to form a power that can freeze the opponent. Unless this is that thing?”

Garen guessed.

However, there wasn’t much time left. Very quickly, it would be his turn to compete.

‘Class of C5’s Nonosiva versus C2’s Long Yuka.”

The broadcasted voice immediately rang out.

Garen stood up from his seat.

“All the best!” Instructor Hamm pumped his first in the air and smiled, “Be careful of your safety and that’s all. It doesn’t matter if you lose.”

“Don’t worry,” Garen replied with a ‘no problem’ gesture. He smiled for a bit and quickly walked towards the opened passageway into the Arena.

At this stage, most of the opponents were absolutely the top elite talents. No one was here because of luck.

As he sat in the Mech, Garen eyes squinted and stared at the black Mech on the opposite side.

“Long Yuka? Weird name.”

‘The competition has now entered the battle of the top ten. Now, Team Grade C will compete. Long Yuka, ranked in eighth class will compete against Nonosiva, who is ranked in ninth class. Both of them are powerful in their own ways — Long Yuka’s previous battle results barely lost to both Bally and Usala in two separate battles, even though he won all his other battles. Whereas Nonosiva is much more powerful. He never lost a single battle, and entered the finals with his absolute victory…”

The broadcast was not a mechanical sound anymore. Instead, it was a professional narrator spluttering as he explained the situation of the competition.

In the Arena, two Mechs confronted each other with a distance of over a hundred meters. Similarly, both of them had chosen the long-range shooting method. More so, it was a similar long-range defense play with long range weapons as well as defensive shields.

The huge black and white shield tower covered the almost half of the back of the two Mech’s body.

Although this shield looked mighty, if they did not know how two use it, it would only take two hits for it to be broken.

Chapter 806: Opponent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen activated his shield.

“Let the competition begin!”

Just as the word ‘begin’ fell out, he raised two of his Gaussian gun.

As the muffled gun sound rang out, the Gaussian cannon shot out two black-lines of afterimages. Suddenly, it hit the front of the black Mech’s shield tower. Then after it slid off the shield tower, it was deflected towards the two sides and it immediately bounced off. It was as if it has some invisible power that attracted both the cannons.

‘Let’s not play along with these useless testings. Let’s see it for real,” the opponent’s voice came from within the black Mech across from him. With this backhand, he took out a black and round ball-like thing that was the size of the Mech’s fist.

“Watch out for my tracking grenade!”

Before the voice rang, he quickly moved towards the left to avoid the next cannon. Then, he violently dived towards the front.

Among the whistling, the black-round ball was flying directly towards the top of Garen’s head. After that, it exploded with a bang, and it was turned into black and small round pearls which sprinkled right down to his face.

“Heavy magnetic interference grenade!”

Garen’s heart jumped. Even this weapon could be used by the opponent — this was the mass killing weapon that could only be used three times in Level 2 of Willpower. The strong interference strength would create a huge distorted signal the moment it touches the Mech. In turn, it would then affect the Mech’s internal signal transmission, causing the Mech’s movements to slow down. There was also the possibility that it might even paralyze the Mech.

“You have to dodge it!”

During times like this, he must move. In this range of scattershot, even if he used his shield to block it, the falling bullets would automatically connect to the magnetic field. Then, it would affect the Mech’s energy consumption, which would increase the burden as well.

The Moonfang that was originally used to control the Mech was already tough and unstable. If he added this thing to the Mech, the rate of losing would be much bigger!

For the first time, Garen felt that this competition was out of his control.

“Luckily my Willpower was upgraded yesterday. Hence, the burden on the Moonfang has lessened a lot more. So, it should be able to support a slightly more intense movement,” this idea flashed across his mind.

He took a glance at the countless iron bullets that were falling down and he suddenly slammed into the ground. He quickly rolled out towards the right side to create some distance. Then, with a muffled thump, he fired a Gaussian Gun from his body when he was rolling. The bullet brushed past the black Mech’s shoulder while he wasn’t paying attention, nearly hitting the head’s control center. It scared the opponent so much that it gave him a cold sweat.

“Amazing! However, only such an opponent is worthy for me to kill!” It seemed like Long Yuka was getting even more excited. Once again, he took out a heavy magnetic interference grenade and he tossed it again.

Puff!

A huge amount of grenade overwhelmingly shrouded Garen again.

For a Mech, up to ten meters of coverage area could be avoided with just one movement. But Garen’s Willpower was short. So this time, he could only roll away to avoid the coverage network. As he raised up his hand, it was another two shots again.

The Gaussian Cannon was just the correct size for Mechs. Lifting it up with one hand was also very easy, but the cannon still fell onto the opponent’s shield and it was bounced off again.

“The turtle shell again!” Even though Garen had expected this earlier when he was looking through the details of his opponent, it still felt frustrating when he had encountered it for real.

Among the two Mechs in the competition, one Mech hid and the other one threw grenades; occasional Gaussian gunshot sounds were heard. The competition was at a deadlock for a moment.

The white Mech that Garen controlled rolled on the ground to dodge the opponent’s grenade again and again, but it seemed like the power of the heavy magnetic interference grenade had affected the Willpower. It was certainly the power of the technique that the opponent had combined with the Willpower that seemed a little strange.

He could vaguely feel that his Willpower was becoming slower. He couldn’t help but feel slightly fearful.

Once again, another roll. Garen had unconsciously gotten closer to the black Mech. Their distance was not more than twenty meters apart.

The Moonfang did not leak this time as if it was because of the strengthening of Willpower. Garen felt slightly calmer. But he realized that only two minutes had passed after he quickly took a look at the time.

Seeing as the black Mech did not notice the closing distance between them, Garen quickly dodged to the left to avoid the bullets that were falling onto the floor.

A sneer came from inside the black Mech as he raised his hand again. This bastard was prepared to throw another grenade! Furthermore, he was throwing it directly in front of him!

Just as he lifted his hand, the grenade was still in his hand.

Garen hastily fixed his gaze.

“Now!”

He suddenly dashed forward and the Mech almost threw himself over; the blue thruster on his back burst violently with the strongest blue flame.

Bang!

The two Mechs fiercely slammed into each other and then they slid away from each other with about a ten-meter distance on the ground.

“You bastard!” The black Mech, Long Yuka made an angry sound and violently twisted the grenade in his hand.

Bang!

The grenade instantly burst opened large bullets, drawing both Mechs inwards. As if the large black bullets had a life of their own, it was sucked onto the surface of the two Mechs.

A shocked sound suddenly came from the audience. It was obvious that no one had expected this to happen.

Garen’s expression turned cold as his right elbow straightened for a moment. At the same time, while one of his knees was stuck in between the opponent’s legs, he used his other hand to pull the trigger of Gaussian gun.

Elbow, and cannon — they both shot up and out at the same time.

Hong!

The white Mech’s close-body combat was a rookie move, Garen had consecutively hit all spots with almost no pause. However, the shields of the two Mechs had flew off from the impact of the hit just now and there was nothing stopping him anymore.

As the explosion rumbled, the black Mech’s cockpit immediately burst into flames. Then, a black rescue capsule popped out and was pulled upwards by the gravitational field.

‘The competition ends there with Nonosiva as the winner!”

The electronic sounds in the Arena rang out.

Garen’s white Mech was also covered with cracks that were caused by the explosion. However, it was naturally much better if he compared it to his opponent whom which he gave a surprise attack to.

‘This is a shocking victory! Scholar Long Yuka practices the Giant Current Training Method that was passed down from his family. The total amount of Willpower he had was nearly twice as much as that of an average person’s training method in his generation. This is why he is able to use heavy magnetic interference grenade as a conventional weapon. But who would expect him to die in the hands of a long-range opponent using close body combat? Undoubtedly, it was his carelessness but it was also due to the opponent’s variety of powerful and comprehensive tactics,’ the narrator started explaining again.

Standing up quietly, Garen lifted his head up and looked at Long Yuka’s unsatisfied face that was in the rescue capsule. This yellow-haired young man did not seem to believe that he had lost the competition.

He took a look at his Moonfang and sure enough, the series of violent movements just now had made this thing sparkle again. He estimated that it would not last much longer before it retires.

Only then did Garen slowly drove the Mech towards the outside. He did not dare to make the movements too big, nor too fast, but only at a slow pace.

Though others felt as if he was exceptionally calm.

‘It seems that even though contestant Nonosiva is in the finals, he is still very calm. After his victory, he is going back to the Mech Warehouse in his uniquely slow pace. He has proved himself to be one of the only four contestants to date that has a record of an absolute victory,’ the narrator’s sound constantly echoed in the air.

Garen could not be bothered to think about it. After changing his Mech, he still had to compete in the Wheel Battle. Hence, he could only rest for a bit. Fervale should also be starting his finals by now. If they did not win, other opponents in other classes would deal with him as they continued.

Back in the Mech Warehouse, he immediately leaned onto the wall to catch some rest after he came out from the Mech. He watched as the damaged white Mech got carried away and a new white Mech walked in again from the inner Warehouse. Rays of repair lights hit the surface of the Mech’s body. There was no one around, he was the only one there. Everything else was the automated facilities. But he could clearly feel that the surrounding monitoring equipment was placed in every corner, constantly monitoring everything that goes on in here.

“Only the first opponent and it was already such a troublesome one…”

After letting out a harsh sigh, Garen closed his eyes to repose his energy.

If it would be unpredictable, then he would need to face two strong opponents later on.

******************

Both of Fervale’s eyes were already squinting from the sweat that was dripping downwards. He did not dare to wipe it off, he could only try his very best to keep it open. He fixed his eyes on the white Mech who was wrestling him.

The two Mechs on the Arena tightly smashed into each other, with their elbows tangled up. They constantly fought like a bull that exerts its force from its horns.

When the Mech’s capabilities are the same, the only thing that would determine a win or a lose was the Mech Pilot. The strong or weak strength Mech Pilot’s Willpower, or whether the posture taken was favorable, would be the key to winning.

Fervale did not know how he had ended up in this wrestling position, but he knew that this was the position that would benefit him the most.

“Don’t waste your energy,” a light tone came from the Mech opposite of him. It was a girl. “Since we were young, when have you won? I did not switch schools his time to waste my time on you.”

“I will win!” Fervale did not speak much. All he did was mobilized his Willpower and continued to inject it into his Mech’s input port.

“It’s useless.”

As the white Mech’s knees hit forwards, directly breaking into Fervale’s chest, a series of sparks ignited.

The two of them were now separated by a little distance. It was at this moment, the white Mech suddenly dashed forwards. Her elbows and knees quickly burst outwards, like a thunderstorm heading towards Fervale.

Bang bang bang bang bang!

Fervale reluctantly shielded himself one time after another, but his whole Mech body was constantly pushed backward.

“Damn it! Why, why, why! Why can’t I win this time!” Hia face was becoming more and more ferocious. As if he did not care about his life anymore, his Willpower wildly entered input port with all that he had.

But to no avail, the Mech lost its balance and violently flew backward. Immediately after, the white Mech’s arrows chased after him and it was directly aimed at his elbow.

Thump!

Fervale felt a huge force pulling him out.

“I lost…”

He knew it was the rescue capsule.

“Such weakling…” He lowered his head. Through the glass, he could see his opponent, the green-haired girl’s arrogant expression.

‘Class of C2’s Celine won!’ The electronic voice rang out.

Fervale closed his eyes. He had once again lost to her. As they were growing up, he had never won once. Even if it was only once!

Celine was the family’s genius. No matter if it was the family’s inner competition, or for the future inheritance for her father’s hard-earned business, if no one could beat her in the end, then the inheritance would only go to Celine, according to family tradition.

Whereas his inheritance rights would be taken away by Celine because of his incompetence. The family would only allow the strongest person to be the successor; there would not be any exceptions.

Celine is unbeatable…

That girl not only has Level 2 of comprehensive strength, she even has the full details that would enable her to challenge Merseus and Bally!

Chapter 807: Celine 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“He lost? It seems like this fellow will not be able to face me now,” Caus simply said as he looked down at the Arena.

A few boys crowded around him and laughed at what he said.

“Should we give that guy a little more seasoning since he dared to beat my younger brother up the last time?” Someone said.

Caus looked down at Nonosiva’s tired face. Suddenly, he did not know what struck him but he felt a slight boredom. How would he, someone who was destined to be one of the top three competitors, waste his energy on such a nobody?

“That’s funny. My opponents should be Merseus and Bally. Even with that role, he still did not get into the finals. If he can win this round, then we’ll talk about it again.”

He looked at the black-haired guy who was walking towards him from the other side.

“Did you get the information I wanted?”

“I got it, but it’s not very detailed. No one really knows all of Bally’s true cards and I have also put in all my effort only to find out one trick of his,” the black-haired man shook his head slightly.

“One trick is good enough,” a hint of surprise flashed across Caus’s eyes.

“Let me deduce it this time for you.”

“Thank you.”

“No need. Just don’t forget us once you’ve entered the elite,” the black-haired man smiled gently.

“Of course not!” Caus solemnly nodded his head. He simply took a glance at Nono who was below and faintly inclined his head to say a few words to the people beside him.

“Go and give Celine a tip on that bastard’s weak spots. I don’t have time to waste on this bastard.”

“Understood,” a young one by his side nodded his head.

*****************

Blackboard Academy, in the Upper-Level Control Hall of a huge Battleship.

The black arched hall was densely inlaid with silver gemstones. Four tall black seats were suspended in the air by strong magnetic force and it each occupied 4 different positions, forming a square. Virtual three-dimensional figures vaguely flickered on top of the seats; there were three older people and one middle-aged woman.

The middle-aged woman’s face did not show the slightest trace of aging, but everyone who knew her knew that she was the oldest among all the other Deans in the Academy. Cruz von Shaw was now two hundred and fifty-nine years old. Since she took on this position as the Dean, she had now been in charge for a solid seventy-nine years.

This elder who had survived for two centuries did not show signs of aging because of her strong Willpower. She had thus been the most powerful Strategic Level Mech Pilot when it came to repressing the Blackboard Region. She had also been awarded the Three Star Honor by the Mother Planet Federation. She had destroyed tons of local Mechs on the battlefield and her impressive reputation spreads throughout the battlefield.

At the moment, Cruz’s both eyes revealed a rare tension as she silently stared at the rotating silver spherical model that was in the middle of the hall.

“What do the three of think about this?” She suddenly said, after observing the sphere.

The other three elders were the Academy’s older professors who were highly respected. They were all strong Mech Pilots, but their ranks were a notch lower when compared to the Dean.

Similarly, the three of them looked carefully at the rotating silver sphere that was in the middle. Their faces revealed a dignified expression, especially when the white light flashed continuously on the surface of the sphere.

“I do not know the source of the rumor, nor where it came from,” a bald-headed old man with a head full of wrinkles said in a deep voice. “But it does not matter if this rumor is true or false, it is not a good thing for Blackboard Region.”

“Why isn’t it a good thing? The bigger the risk, the more benefits we’ll get. If we could get one component of the Forbidden Mech, then it would elevate the quality of our entire Academy!” Another old woman argued.

“Then we would need to have the ability to be able to bear the risk!” The old man frowned as he looked the other person in the eyes.

“Have you become a coward?” The old woman sneered.

“It seems to me that you’ve gone crazy from your pharmaceutical research.”

The both of them were at each other’s necks with their disagreement and they were not willing to compromise.

“Quit arguing. Didn’t Karfi bring back a surviving child from that attack?” Lastly, a white-haired, but radiant-faced professor spoke up; both his eyes had a faint sense of sharpness. Obviously, he was another careerist who did not like being left out — his name was Sims. To date, he was named one of the two strongest Mech Pilots in the Academy’s history. He was the next best, after the Dean who had not shown her skills for many years. At the same time, he held the position of the Academy’s Vice Dean. He was wise and a firm advocate of the theory of force.

“What about the child that Karfi brought back?” It seemed like Dean Cruz had thought of that too. Karfi was one of the Academy’s strongest Black Star out of three, and he was the old woman professor, Baba’s inheriting disciple. Within the Academy, there were only three Level 4 elite students.

“The Black Star has left for the Polar Region. In such a short time frame, we could only estimate to allow these three boys to represent us. It is also a form of training,” Professor Sims simply said.

“What do you mean?” Dean Cruz looked at her old friend whom she had known for many years.

“It can be said that this kid, Black Star Diofie is the strongest talent that our own Academy has brought up. He is destined to surpass all of us,” Sims smiled. “But even tigers who live alone in the mountains will not be able to beat a pride of lions. Even the most powerful people need their own forces — they need to have their own people to help. That’s why we had to allow Medero and the three of them to truly become Diofie’s right-hand assistants.”

Cruz frowned slightly.

“Will there be any danger?”

“If the nested eagles never fly out from their mother’s nest, they will never really spread their wings,” Sims maintained the same smile.

“I agree with this point,” The old-woman professor, Baba nodded her head.

The last person just kept his mouth shut, neither agreed or disagreed.

“Behind this time’s Forbidden Mech issue, there must be a relatively larger organization to promote this, just as it was twenty years ago. But if it’s only within our Region, I will still have the confidence that would ensure the three kids’ personal safety.” After Sim said those words, he did not speak again.

Dean Cruz let out a long sigh.

“Alright then. I’ll pass on this Forbidden Mech issue to the trio of the Black Light to go ahead with the investigation.”

“That’s good too. This case is now settled,” Baba nodded her head. “Then what about the little Kid who was saved?”

“He and the Forbidden Mech must be related. His family was destroyed and it seems like his enemy is looking for something too. If it’s possible, ask him clearly on the valuable items his family possess for their opponent to be making such a big thing out of it — whether it includes having a component of the Forbidden Mech,” Cruz instructed.

“Alright, I will ask Karfi clearly,” Baba nodded her head once again to show her understanding of this matter.

“Then let’s end it here today. Dismiss,’ Cruz slapped the button on the chair and suddenly, the three of their virtual image disappeared in a blink of an eye.

******************

‘The second round — Nonosiva versus Celine!’

The mechanical sound rang out. Garen took control of the white Mech and slowly walked out to the aisle, without using the Ejection System immediately.

It gave him a shock when he noticed that his opponent was using two red boxing gloves. The black Mech forgo-ed the weapons in its hands and instead, it was clenched into a fist, wearing a red pair of spiked gloves. By the looks of it, it seemed a little ferocious but it also seemed a little flimsy.

Because other than that, there were no other protective measures.

The opponent stood firmly. It seemed like it wasn’t moving, giving people a hint of energy that it was as stable as the mountain.

Garen’s Willpower had strengthened and upgraded to another level. He could vaguely feel a certain magnitude of his Willpower’s force on his outer body. At this moment, he could too clearly feel the uniquely strong force that was emitting from his opponent’s body. It made him shudder with fear.

“The opponent this time will be very troublesome…” Garen recalled all of Celine’s information. On the top of the message, it showed that his opponent had only just achieved a Level 2 of Willpower. But looking at her now, it seemed like his opponent had hidden the truth from his informant too. This bastard’s standard was above Level 2…

Celine frowned as she stared at her opponent’s white Mech. At first, she had wanted to choose white, but she did not expect her opponent to choose the same color. This made her a little unhappy.

“Ms. Celine, can you hear me?”

Suddenly, a clear voice echoed inside the Mech.

“Madon? What happened?” Celine sat quietly in her seat and asked calmly.

“I just received news. Your current opponent’s enemy has sent you his weak points — his absolute weak points. This opponent of yours, Nonosiva’s Willpower is…”

“Weak points?” Celine bluntly cut off his sentence, “Does it seem like I would need you to tell me his weak points? Or are you saying that I won’t be able to beat him?”

“That wasn’t what I meant–”

“I don’t want to listen to your nonsense, stupid,” Celine stripped him off his ego. “In front of a stronger competitor, the weak point of the weaker competitor is their whole body! If you can’t even understand that, then you’re really stupid!”

Her communications immediately quiet down and only rapid breathing sounds were heard. Madon was also very enraged. However, although it was obvious, he could only keep it to himself.

‘Let the competition begin!’ the starting voice suddenly rang out.

Celine coldly shut off all her channel communications and directly focused her attention onto the opponent’s body.

Thump!

Both of her Mech’s legs violently jumped off the ground. The jet flames on her back spouted disorderly in mid-air. The Mech flew in a strange arc-shaped curve and dived towards her opponent.

Small Arc Leap! It was one of the lowest depletion steps of Level 2. For normal students, it was one of the most difficult steps of Level 2. Whereas for her, it was easy natural as breathing

With three ‘pengs’, the black Mech was like a flying bat. However, she was flapping her wings much faster than a bat, throwing herself towards the white Mech from mid-air.

The sharp spikes on her fist fiercely scratched two red scars on Garen’s head. However, what was even more surprising was that as she did her trick, a gush of inexplicable tremor suddenly spread throughout.

Boom!

Two Mechs had hit each other abruptly. In turn, Garen’s white Mech was smashed and it staggered backward. His right shoulder revealed a scar. The Gaussian Gun too flew out of his hand; as it rotated in the air, it hit the protective barrier and fell downwards.

“What is this thing?!” Garen sat in the Mech feeling dizzy. Just now, as his opponent leaped in the air, he had wanted to aim and shoot many times, but his opponent had strangely dodged it. It was impossible for him to aim. More so, the most important thing was that his opponent seemed like she could naturally emit a certain sense of heavy interference power from a single movement. This interference had seriously affected his ability to react. If it wasn’t for the strengthening of his Peacock Technique, his vitality was different than before. Under this interference force, he foresaw that he would not be able to hold on to his life until the end.

“Shockwave Killing Fist! It seems like Celine had been practicing the powerful Shockwave Killing Fist, which is almost a Level 3 skill! No wonder she’s named the top talent in the family! Celine really deserves it!” The broadcaster’s voice rang in the arena, through the speakers.

Chapter 808: Celine 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen felt a shiver in his heart.

The Shockwave Killing Fist, he had only heard of the name of this combat skill before. With every strike and blow, it could create a strong concussing effect on the opponent’s willpower, and even those with willpower on par with her’s would be affected by these blows, causing their reflexes to be slowed. Unless you had undergone training to strengthen and enhance the stability of your willpower, against this kind of opponent, even if you had a stronger willpower, you may still lose the battle in a David and Goliath fashion.

“Hahaha! How interesting! To think you managed to survive the first hit!” Celine’s voice rang from the black mech opposite him. She lunged towards him once again. With her level 2 Dodging Techniques along with the effects of the concussive blow, Garen did not have even the slightest chance of getting his aim right.

On the other hand, close combat required that he get closer to the opponent, making him susceptible to even stronger concussions.

“What a terrifying bastard!” for the first time in his life, he felt a complete lack of confidence. He had always had the upper hand against his enemies, but this was the first time his abilities and strength were weaker than his opponents.

He saw his opponent dashing towards him.

“What can I do!?” Numerous possibilities of countermeasures flashed through Garen’s mind, but even for a Master-level veteran with tons of combat experience, he was rendered helpless against this type technique that combines willpower. All the information he had gathered about Celine could be thrown out the window, as this bastard’s hidden strength was too terrifying, its level was even comparable to Merseus’ strength.

If only Garen wasn’t piloting this mech, but rather fighting with his physical body, Garen would have countless methods to temporarily stimulate his potential as a countermeasure. However, when it came to piloting a mech, his options were very limited.

“I can’t possibly be defeated here by a brat that’s so much younger than me…” as Garen scanned over the Moonfang, he started to feel a sense of adrenaline he hadn’t felt in decades. Only when backed into a corner could a situation be considered a difficult challenge! He hadn’t felt this way in a very long time.

Maneuvering the mech to crouch down, he avoided the two flying fists piercing at his head. Then, with a fierce kick, he propelled himself upwards!

Whoosh! The flames from his thrusters were at maximum intensity!

In an instant, the white mech did an action completely out of anyone’s imaginations.

From a crouching position, the mech’s legs kicked upwards. The sharp bit of the leg’s armor pierced into the cockpit where Celine was in.

“How could this be!!?” Celine started to panic. “His willpower was definitely far weaker than mine! How could he possibly manage to counter-attack with such a swift movement without being affected by my strikes!?” She could not wrap her head around how this could’ve happened. Judging from their difference in willpower, her opponent should have at least a few seconds of input delay when it comes to maneuvering the mech. With that amount of delay, even she would be rendered helpless. However, this opponent she was facing right now managed to not just dodge her attack, but even successfully hit a counterattack of his own!?

“This has got to be a joke…”

From the stands, the two spectators from Blue Narcissus stood up in awe. It wasn’t just them, almost the entire stadium stood up, giving him a standing ovation.

“Did this fellow not get affected?”

“Impossible! Based on his performance just now, he was definitely affected!”

The two stood there in shock over the scene that just presented itself in front of their eyes.

At the judge’s seat floating at the top.

“This is…” Red-Eyed Medero was completely shell-shocked, her vision scanning through the tournament brackets, locating the finals for Grade C. “Even under the suppression of his willpower, this guy managed to do all that…? This fellow…”

“What’s wrong?” A guy by her side asked with a weird look. He seemed to have missed the key part of the battle.

“Nothing much, it’s still too early for me to say anything.” Medero started to question what she just saw.

******

Clank!!

The black mech’s arms collided with the legs, causing a loud crash.

Both parties were knocked back by the tremendous force of the impact, flying backward as they lost their balance.

After a couple of flips, Garen rapidly got back on his feet, whilst Celine, in the black mech, used a burst of her thrusters in an attempt to regain her balance.

Staring down her opponent, beads of sweat started dripping down Celine’s forehead.

“You… didn’t get suppressed?!”

“Who knows?” Garen’s calm voice rang from inside the white mech.

He was undoubtedly being suppressed, but at that instant, he predicted his opponent’s likely course of action from a combat standpoint, then input the actions beforehand. In other words, even before Celine did anything, he had already predicted her moves.

This was the fearsomeness of a Master-Level martial artist, he could completely see through his opponent’s actions. Every one of his opponent’s actions was within his calculations.

Even exceeding the Master-Level, Garen was at the level of King of the Century. At this level, they could completely see through all the tricks each other had up their sleeves, rendering all their special moves and secret techniques useless. The deciding factor in such a bout would be a clash of overbearing absolute force. At the level of King of the Century, they could achieve a level where they only needed to rely on open tactics, forcing their opponents to have no choice but to take the initiative and use their full potential in a burst to counter incoming attacks at any moment.

Hence, even though his abilities were restricted when piloting his mech, Garen was not a small fry that could easily be defeated.

“Come on!”

Celine refused to believe that he could completely counter her every move.

The black mech lunged forward once more, the two mechs exchanged blows. Almost as if two humans fighting, with a flurry of strikes and blocks from both sides.

As the fight went on, Celine started to feel worried. It felt almost as if the opposing white mech was covered with eyes on all corners, all of her hidden tricks were completely seen through. What’s even weirder, she had multiple opportunities to deal the killing blow, but somehow in a swift move, the opponent managed to turn the situation around, forcing the battle back into a competition of pure strength.

She felt that her no matter what she did, she was completely seen through by her opponent, almost as if he was peering into the deepest parts of her mind, seeing all her secrets. This induced fear caused her reflexes to slow down, and her strikes were also getting meeker.

“This bastard…” Celine was drenched in sweat. “I’m sure he was being suppressed by my willpower, how is this even possible! How could he still move like that!!?” she was certain that her opponent’s willpower was still being suppressed by hers.

All of a sudden, she hesitated with her actions for just a brief moment. Not being able to react in time, Celine felt a blow on the mech’s legs.

The warning alarm for damaged circuit boards started to ring.

The damaged modules on the leg started to flash red.

At this moment, Celine saw a gigantic fist flying towards her.

Due to her moment of carelessness, she was immediately forced into a corner.

Her feelings of disbelief started bursting out from her heart.

“I am Celine!! I will not be defeated!!” looking at the fist that was getting closer, she had a frenzied look in her eye.

“Go to hell!!”

A piercing sense of willpower suddenly burst out.

Shapeless Needle!

As Garen’s fist pounded onto his opponent’s cockpit, at the exact moment, he felt a sudden strong piercing willpower forcefully passing through the mech, stabbing him in his chest.

Willpower Attack!

He suddenly felt that this was his opponent’s Hail Mary attack.

Unable to dodge or block, Garen could only follow his backup plan, concentrating all of his willpower together, preparing to take the opponent’s attack head-on.

This type of attack that used pure willpower at the cellular level, if he didn’t manage to block it, would directly destroy his willpower at the cellular level. This would cause all affected body parts to lose their functionality, losing their livelihood, almost as if it was an attack on his body matter itself.

Bang!

It almost seemed as if an explosion had erupted in his mind as an immense pain started spreading throughout his body, originating from his chest.

Even Garen, who was unprepared for this attack, let out a long sigh, his face was extremely pale. At that moment, his willpower that had just evolved was almost dispersed, almost turning him back into an average human.

At the same time, at the center of his chest right above his stomach, a black dot started to form on the skin underneath his clothes. The dot started spreading out, almost like a drop of black ink in a body of water, expanding to the size of a fist. All the spots where the skin turned black felt almost like a wilted plant, as it had lost all its shine and elasticity.

The two mechs staggered back a few steps, then stood motionless.

With the last blow onto the cockpit, Celine was bleeding profusely from her eyes and ears and passed out on the pilot’s seat. Her appearance was completely ravaged.

On the other hand, Garen was hit by that piercing willpower and his body was permanently damaged. He was also heavily concussed and unable to come back into consciousness for the time being. He took had suffered serious injuries.

The two were both unable to continue their battle and could only remain idle.

‘Results of the battle: the two parties are unable to continue the battle. It is a draw.’ the result was quickly delivered by the judge’s panel. It seemed like the judges did not want to have any permanent damage done to these two unimaginably powerful geniuses just because of a competition like this. Hence, they reached a decisive conclusion as the result of this battle.

“It’s a Draw!”

Instructor Hamm and the others finally breathed a sigh of relief. Neither him, Fervale, nor Sara could’ve predicted that just within one year, Nonosiva could improve so much, reaching such an amazing level. To put it in a more concrete manner, even though his willpower did not strengthen too much, his combat prowess seemed to have had a huge leap after his injury from last time.

“Celine… Draw…” Fervale stared at the screen displaying the results with a complicated expression. He couldn’t believe that the undefeatable Celine was almost defeated by Nonosiva, who he had always seen as inferior to him. To put it bluntly, for someone who was utterly defeated by Celine earlier on, it was a complete mockery of himself.

“Don’t think too much of it. After all, Nono is also one of the members of our class,” Instructor Hamm patted his back to comfort him.

“I understand.” Fervale nodded while taking a deep breath.

******

On the Arena

Numerous ambulances and technical crew rushed to the scene. They were each checking on the condition of the mech and the pilots.

Garen was carried out of the mech. Looking at the black patch of dead skin on Garen’s chest sent a shiver down the paramedics’ spines. This kind of wound caused by the sheer force of willpower was the hardest to deal with. To their surprise, Garen was still conscious; although his forehead was drenched in sweat, he was definitely still conscious. He tilted his head over to look at his opponent Celine who was being dragged out of the mech right opposite of him.

Celine’s body was completely covered with blood as she was being dragged out, and her body was as stiff as a plank. The paramedics immediately attached an oxygen mask to her and rushed her stretcher to the ambulance.

Swiftly, the two were carried onto the same ambulance and transported out of the arena, leaving a trail of ambulance sirens. The technical crew also started towing the two mechs off the arena.

This was the worst injury Garen had sustained in this body to date. The damaged parts of his chest were not the problem, but the traces of Celine’s willpower around those parts were troublesome. These traces was what was left from Celine shattering her own concentrated willpower, the remaining power. All of these traces were a portion of the power from the strike earlier, preventing his body’s recovery system from repairing his injuries.

There was a pair of doctors and nurses next to each stretcher attending to them to monitor their condition.

“You’re too good!” Celine said through the oxygen mask.

Chapter 809: Rising Wind 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Are you praising yourself? It was you who beat me up into such a state,” Garen said calmly. He intentionally squirmed a bit to mimic being in pain, pretending~ to make an agonized expression. Truthfully, this kind of pain was almost commonplace to him. If not to appear more normal, he could even sit up and move about. Furthermore, he could even treat his own wounds, but that would not fit his appearance as a kid who hadn’t even hit his twenties.

“To tell you the truth, I was aiming to get into the Top 3 to become an Elite Student,” Celine thought back to the feeling she felt earlier, almost as if her entirety was being seen through. It left a bitter taste in her heart.

“What a coincidence, I was thinking the same thing,” Garen ‘forcefully’ let out a chuckle.

“Oh?” Celine turned her head towards him. “And here I thought there were a lot more experts like you over here at Blackboard.”

Garen remained silent. He continued lying there letting the nurse wipe off his sweat.

“If there really were so many experts, then my dreams of getting into the Top 3 would be impossible,” Celine continued.

“What was the name of that pure willpower attack that you used at the end?” Garen already knew that the tournament was already over for him, but he managed to show his true potential. Gaining the attention and respect from Blue Narcissus shouldn’t be an issue now, so he might as well focus on the stuff he was interested in in the meantime.

“It’s Shapeless Needle, a skill that I can only use once,” as Celine was speaking to an opponent of her level, she has completely lost the prideful air she had earlier and looked a lot calmer. “Pure willpower-based techniques are extremely difficult, even I only managed to learn two types – Willpower Concussion and Shapeless Needle. In addition, most of them require a lot of self-exertion.”

She paused, “You, on the other hand, even though you were being suppressed by me, how did you manage to initiate that strong counterattack?”

Garen laughed, although Celine could be foulmouthed at times, she wasn’t necessarily a bad person; she simply just has a desire to attain more strength.

“That was purely just my offensive instincts, I could predict your actions,” he didn’t hide anything from her, as even if he revealed this to her, there was no way she could easily learn this. This was something that can only be obtained from large amounts of experience in combat and a high level of physical prowess. Otherwise, with the countless amounts of martial artists present in the Secret Technique World, there wouldn’t only be a couple of King of the Century level experts.

Unsurprisingly, Celine also understood that point.

“What are you talking about, this level of proficiency can only be achieved by the likes of the Inheriting Pilots. How old do you think you are?”

“Well, your offensive tactics weren’t that advanced either,” Garen responded.

“Err…” Celine was left speechless. It was true that if the opponent were much better when it comes to such tactics and strategies, this would not be impossible.

However, Garen managed to read in between the lines of what she was saying.

“Do you mean that there really have been people who managed to achieve that high level of proficiency?”

That had to be a joke, out of billions of people, barely a handful could be considered at the King of Century level. How could there easily be such a person here?

“Of course, Inheriting Pilots are all experts in battle strategy, this degree of offensive instinct would only be the foundations of their skills,” Celine naturally replied.

Garen pondered a bit more, this was indeed nothing too surprising.

The King of the Centuries of the Secret Technique World were hailed as kings, but in that world, the number of people who practiced secret techniques was only a few million. Out of that number, there was a one in a million chance that they would become a King of the Century. On the other hand, in this world, taking the entire planet as a unit of measurement, this planet contains easily billions in population. Learning to pilot mechs was also one of the most mainstream paths and out of the billions of people, at least tens of millions would pursue a career in mech piloting. There were countless students from institutions and academies all aiming to become a mech pilot, aspiring to be the one-man-army of the heroic legends.

With this ratio, having more King of the Century level people would not be strange at all.

Celine did not notice Garen’s pondering look as she continued to talk to herself.

“Even within our Blackboard Academy, there are these types of experts. Dean Cruz and Vice Dean Sims are both top-level experts. Combining their expertise with their willpower, their strength is almost comparable to the fearsomeness of the one-man-army from the legends.” Celine’s eyes were full of admiration.

“Alright, let’s change the topic. Since we got a tie in our match, I wonder what arrangements they would have for us,” Garen asked.

“There are no arrangements. We won’t be able to continue on in the tournament. Damn! If I didn’t have to face you, I could’ve easily beaten Caus. I might’ve even stood a chance in a heads-up battle against Bally,” Celine had a dissatisfied look on her face.

“Save your strength for healing your injuries. If you’re dissatisfied, just go back to challenge them in the future,” Garen lazily said.

Celine suddenly felt like a deflated balloon, glaring daggers at Garen. She helplessly just turned her head and went to rest.

******

Caus was seated in the contestant area, discussing the previous bout with instructors.

“Those two fellows…” beads of sweat started to form on his forehead.

“If you were the one facing off against them, do you have the confidence to win?” the instructor asked in a low voice.

Caus wanted to answer but he still had his own dignity, and the answer wouldn’t change anything anyway. Disregarding everything else, merely with the Willpower Concussion technique, he would’ve been utterly defeated, or even just one-shotted.

“Let’s just focus on your preparations for the next match,” the instructor sighed. “Don’t think too much of it. Since they have already left the battlefield, let’s just consider that your fortune. There are only 3 top spots after all.”

Caus let out a long breath.

“Understood.”

However, one thing continued to linger in his mind, since when had Nonosiva possessed such a strong potential and strength? If he continued on with their grudges, was it really worth it? It was something he had to take into consideration. Luckily he wasn’t the one who directly confronted him back then, he was only supporting his juniors in their actions. He could push all the blame onto them and start over with a clean slate.

When faced with an opponent that you cannot easily escape, especially if the opponent was one that constantly grew stronger, under these conditions and the constraints of a legal system, no matter what grudges one had before, the first thing anyone would think of wouldn’t be how to defeat the opponent, but rather how to solve this issue.

Only a dumbass would continue on under these conditions.

Caus had already planned out his strategy to win over Nonosiva. The guy was from a poor background, giving him some small benefits should be enough, this shouldn’t be too big of an issue.

******

Garen was forced to withdraw from the tournament as a result of his draw with Celine. Although they didn’t manage to advance to the final stage, they managed to show off their true potential and extraordinary abilities. The top brass should give some sort of acknowledgment.

After settling the placings for the tournaments, Instructor Hamm, Fervale and company rushed off to the hospital after the ambulances. Mia and Aier also followed them.

From the spectator stands, the two Blue Narcissus spectators were exchanging their opinions.

“Let’s just report it as it is, we’ll just leave it to the people in charge of Grade C to decide.”

“I think they should pass, they have the makings of an Elite Student.”

“However, the fact is that they still didn’t pass, I think…” the two didn’t continue on, they genuinely felt sorry for Garen’s misfortune. “They definitely had the potential to be Elite Students, what a waste.”

“Yeah.”

The tournament did not come to a halt just because of Garen and Celine’s withdrawal. The tournament continued on as scheduled after a wave of discussions at the judges’ seat. Regrettably, they still remained inconclusive and they decided to focus on the upcoming matches in the meantime.

However, the recordings of Garen and Celine’s battle were leaked out, and their reputations as prodigies started to spread. Whether Garen or Celine, the battle had proven their abilities as pilots. Although both of them were heavily injured in the match and were forced to withdraw from the tournament, their final battle had left a lasting impression on everyone who saw it.

As Merseus, Bally, and Caus made their way into the Elite Council, Nonosiva and Celine also became the strongest First Seats in every Grade C student’s heart.

Especially mid-level students like Fervale, they were mostly students who had Upper Level 1 willpower, they were far weaker as compared to Celine who almost reached Level 3 willpower. They were also the ones who fully understood the difference in their strengths. Regarding Nono who managed to hold his own against Celine, linking it with his past winning streak, they naturally also regarded him as a perceived Level 3 when he combines his general abilities.

Who would’ve thought that an expert like Nonosiva was still at a Level 1 willpower? If Celine had started off the battle with her pure willpower attacks, it was unlikely that Garen would have been able to attain this result.

At the same time, all throughout the Blackboard Region, all eyes were on the Qualifier Match of the Academy. The matches sent shockwaves through the outer areas of the Southwest region of Blackboard.

******

Southwest of the Blackboard Region

The sky was a stretch of clear blue, without a cloud in sight.

Hiss!!

Suddenly, a twisted black ball appeared in the sky out of nowhere. The ball was engulfed in glowing black electric discharge, making a crackling sound. The ball started off at the size of a soccer ball, but it rapidly expanded.

Bang!

With a loud noise, the ball burst open, revealing a damaged black and red mech. The mech was in humanoid form, and half of its head had been sliced off by a sharp object. Its right arm and leg were covered with some sort of cast in an attempt to keep it in one piece. It was holding a long black curved knife, but the knife was full of chips and had various dents and blunt edges on it as if it had been used to block strikes.

Just as the black and red mech appeared, it started nosediving straight towards the ground. Although it was trying to stay afloat using its thrusters, it could barely slow down the fall.

“I’m… not done…!!” from inside the mech, a voice shouted in agony.

Crash!!

The mech collided with a hard rocky cliff and exploded into countless bits and pieces. The yellow and red flames formed intersecting light rings, slicing through everything it came in contact with. Only after spreading a few hundred meters did it slowly fade away.

All the areas that were sliced through by the two light rings were perfectly cut through.

The edge of the rocky cliff also started to crumble, as if the light ring had sliced off a huge portion of the cliff.

Chapter 810: Rising Wind 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was at this moment that a black ball of sparks appeared in the middle of the sky once again. The ball exploded, this time revealing a white and red humanoid mech.

The mech was more than 10 meters tall with a lean and elegant shape. However, its arms inspired a sense of curiosity from everyone who looked at it. One of them was holding onto a snowy white alloy sword that looked like a straight letter opener while the other didn’t have a hand structure; instead, the arm was in the shape of a cannon barrel. There were some symbols and patterns carved in dark red at the area around the cannon lip and muzzle, giving it an antique vibe.

However, the thing that stood out the most about the mech was the soft green fluorescence shining from all the gaps on its chest and shoulder plates, almost as if a neon green liquid was flowing through all of these crevices. These growing green crevices seemed to naturally form a single character: Light.

“How dare he attempt such a stunt even after being so heavily damaged? Serves him right!” a cold and hoarse voice sounded from inside the mech.

All of a sudden, numerous white humanoid mechs appeared behind this mech. All of them had the white-red color scheme, but none were as intricately designed as the mech leading them. They all had a simple green diamond-shaped gem embedded in their chests.

“Go down there and retrieve the parts,” The leader said emotionlessly.

“Understood.”

Out of the 5 mechs that just appeared, 3 of them nosedived downwards while the remaining 2 started circling the area as if they were patrolling.

“Based on your potential, to be able to force me, the Great Light Mech, to personally take action, you should be proud,” the leader mech sneered as he looked down at the remains of the exploded mech.

Almost immediately, the results of the search were reported back, neatly organized on the mech’s quantum computer. Pieces of black machine parts start popping up on the computer screen.

“The next target is…?”

Inside the Great Light Mech, a young man in a white mask quickly opened the email that he had just received.

Swiftly scanning through the contents of the message, the man’s sharp eyes squinted slightly, showing a hint of surprise.

“There’s also a fragment in the Blackboard Region? Well since I’m already here, I might as well go get it.”

******

Blackboard City South District

Inside a bakery with the sign “One for All Bakery” at the corner of the street.

The interior of the building was dimly lit with a warm yellow light, creating a warm and cozy atmosphere even during the day.

Clint Beza was seated on a chair in a lazy, half-asleep state, looking almost like a droopy slime. Saliva was slowly flowing out from the corner of his lip, dripping down his chin. The saliva was dangling from the side his face, creating some sort of thin saliva thread.

Whew…

With a slight breeze, the dangling saliva thread swung towards Clint’s shirt collar, creating a damp dark stain.

Slurp…

Clint sucked up his saliva, then continued to sleep with his head tilted to the side

“Oh my god!!! Ohmygodohmygodohmygod! Goddammit! We’re screwed! This time we’re screwed!” out of nowhere, a loud shriek rang out in his ear. The loud sound made Clint feel a sense of numbness throughout his body and it immediately woke him from his slumber.

Clint looked dazed. After taking a moment to regain his composure, he cupped his ears and started roaring loudly.

“What are you doing! My ears! Ears…!”

“You’re screwed!” Red Moon answered concisely.

“Why?” Clint asked. “Why am I screwed?”

“You’re dead!”

“Why?” Clint asked on with a confused look.

“You are an idiot! Dead! This time we’re dead!” Red Moon continued to shout.

“Oh my god…” Clint held his head as he cried out in agony.

After 10 minutes of forcefully resisting the intensely loud shouts, Clint went to attend a few customers before finally getting an opportunity to use the washroom.

“Lord Red Moon, what the heck are you going on about this time! I can’t take it anymore, I really can’t take it anymore! If you continue on my sanity levels will definitely go down, really!”

Pulling down his pants, he sat his ass down on the toilet and let out a long sigh.

“I have unfortunate news to tell you,” Red Moon angrily answered, “We’ve been found out!”

“Found out? What do you mean?” Clint was once again confused.

“An expert is now on the hunt for my parts, and they’re already here in the Blackboard Region,” Red Moon said in a serious tone, “I’m not joking around this time. If we get found, we’ll be dead meat. I’ll get reformatted, and you will definitely be silenced!”

Clint felt a cold sweat drip down his forehead.

“S-Silence… You don’t mean… They’re going to kill me???”

How could this kind of television drama progression happen to himself in real life?

“You better believe it,” Red Moon replied coldly. “I’m telling the truth. My original body was once known as the Forbidden Mech by your people, one of the strongest tiered mechs in space. Even if it’s just one of my parts, it would be considered a valuable treasure worth a small fortune to the average person. For an expert to come and collect my parts is no surprise. The only thing out of my expectations was that they somehow managed to find out about my existence. Is it really a coincidence?”

“Forbidden Mech…” Clint swallowed hard, feeling as if he was getting dragged deeper and deeper into this hole he dug. “Lord Red Moon… You’re just joking with me right…?”

“Do you think I’m in the mood to play around with you?” Red Moon directly interrupted his thoughts. “We need to find a way to escape our pursuers!”

“Oh my god… Ohmigod… Oh, God!” This time Clint started gasping.

“The most important thing right now is to avoid being found by our pursuers. I can feel that my part is nearby this area, though I don’t know whether they can pinpoint our exact location right now. However, just in case, I’ll switch into a power-saver mode to reduce the signal reception,” Red Moon rapidly reported the situation. “After this I might not be able to sense their location, but the same can also be said for them. You shouldn’t have to worry too much for now. This is Blackboard City, the center of the entire Blackboard Region. It is surrounded by Blackboard Academy’s most elite mech division, so they wouldn’t dare to try any funny business over here.”

“So does this mean that I’m safe?” Clint’s face was as white as a sheet, he was so terrified.

“You’re safe for now. All we can do now is to bet everything on this. If they can find us even after I cut off all connections, then it’ll all be down to our luck,” Red Moon explained.

“What if I just throw you away right now?” Clint suddenly thought of an idea.

“Too late!” Red Moon laughed coldly. “Your body already has my mark, and anyone who comes in contact with me will be tainted by a sort of aura. This type of radiation-based aura will be easily recognized by them. With such an obvious trace, they will definitely kill you off.”

“No!!” Clint shouted with his head in his arms. Luckily everyone else had all left for lunch, he was the only one left in the shop.

“Lord, please have mercy on me. I’m only a normal 16-year-old teen, I’m not some prodigy harem protagonist from those works of fiction!!”

“Just accept your fate, effortlessly leaving this up to luck is actually a great option for you. You’re nothing more than a useless waste of space anyways,” Red Moon scoffed. “Sooner or later, everyone connected to you will also be dragged into this ordeal. Your sister, your parents, your only friend Darby, Baylon, all of them will also be killed. Their only mistake was being related to a piece of shit like you.”

“You must be just scaring me,” Clint suddenly calmed down. “That’s definitely it, Lord Red Moon, you have always liked to scare me. Making this time’s attempt so realistic must be all part of your plan, it’s my loss. Well, I’ll be on my way, I need to get back to watching the shop.”

“Scaring you? Are you in denial?” Red Moon was speechless.

“Sis and the others are going to be back soon, I should hurry back, or else I’ll be scolded again,” Clint felt almost zen-like. He stood up and flushed the toilet.

“So not being able to handle reality forced him into a shell of his own delusions huh…” Red Moon had nothing left to say. Looking at the image from the parts, their opponents weren’t shady characters. They will definitely attempt something big. Well when it really becomes a problem, that’ll give this guy the wake-up call he needs.

******

“This is my second time being hospitalized just within this short semester,” Garen said as he laid back in the upper-class intensive care unit as he carefreely conversed with Celine.

These two were admitted this time due to mutually inflicted injuries. Taking into account their stellar performance, the council acknowledged their abilities and potential, so these sorts of medical arrangements were mere trivialities.

The doctors and nurses had just come in a while ago to re-apply their medication. They had then left to allow the two to get some rest.

One of Celine’s legs were wrapped with a white cloth and elevated by a stand. She was completely bandaged up like a dumpling, only revealing her eyes, nostrils, and mouth.

“It’s only your second time?” it was by Celine’s request that she was transferred to this shared ward. She was quite interested in this fellow Nono. Even if he was a prodigy student, he was still just from an average household. How did he manage to get so strong in combat capabilities that he could manage to fight on equal footing against herself, who was using willpower techniques? This was undoubtedly a miracle.

“I would get hospitalized once a week, at the very least,” she casually said.

“Every week? Why?” Garen was feeling bored anyways, so he might as well have a chat with this person.

“Assaults, challenges, and all sorts of troublesome stuff would all lead to injuries. Every so often, I just found myself in a situation where I need to be hospitalized,” Celine said thoughtlessly. She looked over at Garen. Other than a bandage across the chest with some applied medication, he looked no different from other average patients. Looking at his rosy face, an average person wouldn’t even believe that he had sustained an injury.

“You have quite a sturdy body don’t you, must be all the combat training paying off.”

“I’m still doing decently,” Garen crossed his legs, shifting into a more comfortable position. “By the way, you specifically requested to be transferred to my ward, anything I can help you with?”

No matter how much Celine lacks in femininity, she was ultimately still a girl, an 18-year old young teenage girl. Transferring into his ward like this, rumors about the two would surely spread.

“I feel that even my private coaches are no match for you when it comes to combat abilities. I want to learn the art of combat from you,” Celine said in a straightforward fashion.

“You have no qualms about being injured so badly by me?” Garen was surprised by her request, as he didn’t expect this girl to have such a personality.

“I do mind… but that’s why I want to learn the basics of combat from you!” Celine answered sincerely.

“I will charge you,” Garen frowned.

“Just state your price,” Celine answered ostentatiously. “How do ten thousand Units per day sound?”

“My training is very harsh,” Garen actually started to consider it, as he’d been lacking in funds recently.

“Harsh training is not a problem. As long as my limbs are still attached, I can take it,” Celine answered without hesitation.

Garen was speechless, just what kind of training had she previously undergone? This level of commitment was mind-boggling… It felt like a matter of life and death.

“Oh right, what’s going on between you and that guy Fervale?” Garen asked directly. He felt that Celine was quite pure-hearted to be honest, she purely wanted to get stronger. Her battle philosophy was completely different from Fervale.

“That guy is completely useless. He’s too weak. Even after wasting so many resources, he only grew by that insignificant amount. I was born stronger than him, that’s why the household chose me as the heir. After losing that position to me, he probably felt jealous. That’s most likely why he always had a grudge against me,” Celine casually explained. “I originally thought that this grudge would serve as motivation for him to get better, but he’s always caught up with impure thoughts. He has lost his focus on improving himself to pursue that business force or whatever. What an idiot.”

Thinking back about that guy Fervale, Garen could definitely feel that he was too narrow-minded. His heart was filled with impure intentions, unlike Celine who was completely pure. Not being able to focus on one thing at a time, how could he ever surpass a training junkie like Celine? Him being left in the dust was no surprise at all.

Chapter 811: Rising Wind 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“These injuries will probably take about half a month to heal. Just lying here all day is quite boring, do you have any ideas?” Celine asked while humming cheerfully.

“Ideas?” Garen was about to speak, but the ward door suddenly burst open. In came Instructor Hamm and a yellow-haired man with a neatly shaved buzz cut.

“If you’re bored, why not go on the Battlenet?” The yellow-haired man said.

“Coach, you came?” Celine looked at the yellow-haired man. It wasn’t a look of pure and utter respect, it was more like a look one would give a friend.

“I went to your ward earlier but you weren’t there. After asking the nurses, they told me that you transferred to another ward. It was at that moment I knew that you were definitely after contestant Nonosiva over here,” The yellow-haired man shrugged nonchalantly.

On the other hand, Instructor Hamm had a worried look as he stood at Garen’s bedside. Following closely behind him was Mina and Aier, and also a few others from Garen’s class. They were all here to visit Garen.

“Instructor,” Garen turned over while trying to stand up, but he was stopped by Instructor Hamm. Hence, he had no choice but to lie back down on his bed.

“Rest well, don’t think too much about formalities right now,” Instructor Hamm patted him on his shoulder. “You already did amazingly well and now it’s time for you to take a break.”

“If it wasn’t for meeting you, I would’ve breezed straight through to the top 3,” Celine chimed in from his side.

Garen ignored her words and asked the instructor about the situation regarding the tournament. As expected, after they had taken their leave, the tournament progressed to its final stage and the final 3 were decided. Unsurprisingly, Merseus got first place, almost one-shotting Bally, who was in second place, with his Level 3 Double Magnetic Field Line Cut. As for the third place Caus, this kid knew his own limits and didn’t even attempt to challenge Merseus for his first place. Thus, the rankings for this tournament were decided.

The spectator team at the judge’s seat came to the decision of accepting the three as Elite Students on the fly, allowing them to enter the council and choose their own specialization for their training.

“They’re currently holding the closing ceremony for the finals, but a lot of people have already left earlier. So, we decided to come over to visit you guys,” Mina said with a smile on her face. “Nono, this time you’ve really came into the limelight. To be able to suddenly get such a huge leap in rankings, our class getting 9th rank was all thanks to you.”

“Well, I can rest easy now knowing that you guys are doing fine,” Instructor Hamm laughed. “Mina is right, the academy will reward prize money for getting 9th rank. However, since the judge’s panel unanimously agreed that your strength and potential was on par with 4th place. Thus, although you won’t get the treatment of the 4th ranked student, the amount of prize money awarded to you is equivalent to that of a 4th ranked student. So that’s some good news for you.”

“How much is there?” Garen was suddenly energized at the mention of prize money. He was truly in need of money right now, mainly because the impure White Peacock Stones required to learn the Peacock Technique were burning a hole through his wallet. As he progressed deeper and deeper into this ‘hobby’ of his, the accumulated requirements got increasingly higher. If he already needed so much money at this point in time, surely he would need even more in the future. If he didn’t start saving up now, he’d definitely go bankrupt.

Instructor Hamm and company paid no mind to it, after all, Nono was from a poor household, so him being excited about prize money was, of course, completely natural.

“Eighty thousand!” Instructor Hamm answered with a cheeky grin, showing off his pearly whites.

Eighty thousand, for a normal household, would be approximately a year worth of household income or even more. Now, just by getting the 4th place in a tournament, he’d managed to get his hands on this gigantic sum in the form of prize money.

Garen felt as if he was relieved of a great burden, as the prize money solved his current worries for now. The third batch of white Rainbow Stones was in sight.

‘However, directly purchasing these Rainbow Stones isn’t worth it. All the high-energy fuel powder I obtained can be covertly resold off, I just need to find an anonymous trading service. This eighty thousand can be used to purchase a small laboratory. Using that as a cover, I can bleach the fuel powder and sell it off.’

Garen started thinking of different alternatives. On the surface, he was still casually chatting with Instructor Hamm, Mina, and Aier, and also thanking his classmates for their thoughts and prayers. However, the only thing Garen had on his mind at the time was the question of how he could bleach the fuel powder he had on hand.

Based on his prior research, in the current market, the high-energy fuel powder he had was currently, even in its most impure form, worth about 120 thousand universal Units per thousand grams. Of course, that was only the retail price, and if he sold it in large quantities, the price would no doubt be slightly cheaper. However, even if he only charged 100 thousand Units per thousand grams, he would still make a killing.

Garen thoroughly calculated the amount of powder he’d obtained from absorbing the White Peacock Stones from the start. The first batch was some stone powder that cost him 1000 Units, and the amount of powder that remained was approximately 2 kilograms. That amount managed to completely fill a bottle. This powder was also very dense, and it also had a bit weight to it. The second batch was the powder that remained from his previous absorption, it was easily 20 kilograms in weight and had cost more than 10 thousand Units.

In other words, if the degree of purity could hit the standard, his investment of 1000 Units would easily net 200 thousand Units in returns. This was an insane 1:200 rate of returns!

“The current problem now is the question of how to solve the anonymity issue. With this huge amount of profits, there would be plenty of people investigating me and my methods in a fit of jealousy. What kind of cover can I use to prevent that?” Garen was still a bit unfamiliar with these sorts of schemes.

After staying with Garen for a little longer, Instructor Hamm and company finally left to give Garen and Celine some time to rest.

“Hey, Celine,” Garen called out to the green haired girl.

“What’s up?” this girl suddenly opened her eyes, as if she was a cobra that had just awakened. For a young girl to be able to give off such a vibe, it was obviously the results of the intense training of her willpower attributes.

“Normally speaking, if you were to obtain a batch of chemical raw materials from an unknown source, how would you go about exchanging it for money?” Garen asked directly, not even trying to hide anything. This kind of training techniques wasn’t something that others could learn anyway since the Life Secret Technique was something that only a person with a soul seed could learn. In this world, except for him, it was impossible for anyone else to have the second seed for the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. Even if thieves stole the powder from him, he could easily just create even more from his training.

“Chemical raw material from an unknown source?” Celine was amused by the question. She had no idea how this topic suddenly came up. Now that she thought about it, Nonosiva must’ve gotten his hands on some sort of stuff and is trying to earn some money from it.

As she was quite fond of Garen and wanted him to teach her in the future, she felt that there was no harm in giving him some aid.

“You can just hand it to me, if the amount isn’t too much, I can directly exchange it for Universal Units. This way, you don’t have to worry about anything in the future,” she said in a carefree tone.

“How are your guys going to go about doing it?” Garen questioned on.

“I have friends from various professions that deal with different types of illegal items and undocumented assets and valuables. They will have their means to settle this. Why do you ask? Do you have some goods you need to settle?” Celine looked over at Garen with suspicion. Based off of his looks, he seemed to be from a simple and innocent background with a completely clean record. Why would he come in contact with these kinds of stuff?

“What if I can provide a long-term source for these types of undocumented valuables?” Garen continued on.

“If that’s the case…” Celine started to frown. “I’m not very interested in these kinds of stuff, but if you’re really keen on doing this I can introduce you to some of my connections. He should be more familiar with these sorts of topics, this issue should be trivial to him.”

She looked Garen in the eye and said, “However, you have to guarantee that the source of the goods won’t cause trouble.”

“That’s not a problem,” Garen nodded.

“Then I don’t think there’ll be any issues. I’ll give you his number so you can contact him directly. I’ll give him a heads up in advance,” Celine nodded.

Garen continued on with his queries about this issue. When he hit on the issue of the laboratory, Celine was suddenly shocked.

“This project of yours, at a larger scale, would cost tens of millions or even up to a billion. Even at a smaller scale, it would at the very least take tens of thousands of Units just for attaining the laboratory itself. It’s common sense that no matter how amazing the facilities and equipment are, if you do not have a decent human researcher, it wouldn’t yield any good results. On the other hand, if you have a good researcher, but you only have mediocre equipment, you’ll still manage to yield decent results.”

She suddenly realized something as she looked over at Garen once more.

“You cheeky bastard… Did you come up with some sort of new technique or skill?”

All these teenagers who were talented enough to hold the title of genius or prodigy weren’t people to be taken lightly. Especially for people like Celine who was from a huge influential household, they grew up surrounded by all sorts of big-shots. Naturally, their mental responsiveness was very high, and they were usually able to piece together everything accurately with just a couple of clues.

Garen also felt that there was no point in hiding anything.

“Yes, I developed a new technique. The goods produced from it are worth quite a bit, but it should just be mere pocket change for you.”

“What stage is it at?” Celine got more curious.

“Do you want to become a shareholder?” Garen chuckled. “If you help me settle the underground issues, I’ll give you 10% of the shares. Think of it as my gift to you, you don’t need to do anything except for helping out once in a while during key stages of the project.”

Celine was seriously considering his offer.

“Alright, this is such a blatant bribery-based relationship though!”

Garen was very calm about this. He knew that if he took all the profits for himself there would be a lot of trouble. With such a large cash flow, it would be near impossible to hide from the rich and the powerful. For an average person like him to have such a high yield technique, he would definitely be viewed as a sinner. Rather than having to deal with the pressure from other forces in the future, it would be easier for him to just start strengthening relationships right now to protect him.

In this case, for someone like Celine who is from a rich and powerful household, she was definitely a prime candidate to form a strong connection with. There was no such thing as too much money after all. Even if Celine wasn’t too mindful her wealth, there was still no reason to refuse.

“How much would the approximate income for this project be?” Celine lowered her head, seemingly deep in thought. She then raised her head and continued, “To be honest, I truly just want to become your friend, I’m afraid that you’ll still have reservations about teaching me.”

“The monthly income should be at least 100 thousand Units,” Garen didn’t dare to promise too much, so he gave a conservative estimation.

“100 thousand Units per month… That’s still somewhat acceptable, count me in.” Celine nodded after a brief moment of hesitation. For her, this amount nothing much at all. In her current position, even if she took only her own assets in her household into account, the number of funds she could liquidate within a year would easily be over a few million. If Garen’s monthly income was around 100 thousand, giving her 10% of it would be approximately 10-20 thousand per month, it was just pocket change to her.

“I meant that your income would be 100 thousand Units per month,” Garen noticed that she seemed to misunderstand his statement.

“!?”

Celine was completely shocked, she could only stare at Garen in disbelief.

Chapter 812: Rising Wind 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“There’s no mistake. For 10% of the shares, if everything goes smoothly that month, your income for the month would be easily 100 thousand Units,” Garen said casually. Observing Celine’s look of disbelief, he helplessly let out a sigh.

“Go on, keep on blowing your trumpet,” Celine scowled as she grabbed a date and tossed it into her mouth.

“Why would I want to lie to you about this?” Garen said seriously, “This technique is something only I can achieve, there’s no one else who is able to do it, so I don’t mind telling you about it.” In reality, no matter how he calculated, this was already an extremely conservative estimate. However, as per Garen’s hypothesis, at this level of cash flow, to someone as rich and powerful as Celine, although it wasn’t too much, it was enough to lure her in without attracting too much attention from the higher-ups. With someone like Celine as his shield, it was the option that presented the least risk and the safest option available to him.

“You better not be scamming me,” seeing Garen’s seriousness through his statements, Celine’s facial expression started to soften. She started to suppress the concerns in her heart and said with a very serious tone, “If your project will really rake in such a huge amount of profits, I can help you get in contact with a couple of my connections.”

“Of course, I wouldn’t joke about something as big as this,” knowing that he’d managed to lure her in, Garen nodded seriously.

After thinking for a while, Celine continued to inquire more about the details of the project.

Garen responded to all her queries assuredly. He was once a top class specialist back in the various regions of the Totem World, and his knowledge had reached the absurd level of even being able to conduct a heart transplant and alter the genes and souls of others. Dealing with Celine was nothing more than just throwing out a couple of new theories to impress her.

It was just a matter of changing the names of the existing theories from the Totem World and attaching a prefix and suffix to the theory itself. This made the theory seem even greater and mind-boggling. With this simple method, he’d completely stunned Celine.

After the explanation of 3 core theories, Celine started to understand the message behind Garen’s technique a bit more. With this, she confirmed that he wasn’t just tooting his own horn. With her newfound trust towards Garen, she started to connect him with her own circle of friends.

Nonosiva was a genius from a normal household and a future mech pilot, and even just being a genius within Blackboard Academy would’ve given him a promising future. For him to make his way up the ranks of the military wouldn’t be a surprising thing. Now, if he could garner enough funds, resources, and support, his future opportunities would be limitless.

After all, a few of the young generals in the past in the military had similar humble beginnings. It was completely possible for Nono to become a general in the future.

Unconsciously, Celine’s impression of Garen started to change. For a genius like him with enough potential, along with an offer with enough profit, these two conditions allow this person to be able to negotiate with her on equal standing. At the very least, she no longer underestimated this person’s capabilities.

After a hanging up from a call, Celine slouched back with a look of exhaustion.

“Luckily you already proved your worth to the higher-ups in the academy. Otherwise, your background would’ve been too lacking in credibility. There would be no way for you to be able to retain this amount of profits.”

“Have you set the time for the meeting?” Garen overheard a portion of her conversation earlier.

“Yeah, after we get discharged, we’ll have a look at your goods. They want to inspect the quality of the goods before agreeing to anything. If the fuel powder quality is decent enough, there won’t be any issues,” Celine nodded. “I’ve contacted a few people, there were two that were quite keen on this deal. They will come view the goods together at a later date. One of those guys come from an even more influential background than me, so you should take care not to offend him. Otherwise, there’ll be a lot of trouble coming our way.” she cautioned him.

“I understand,” Garen nodded his head with a smile. He knew there was hope in achieving his goals. With his current identity as Nonosiva, he was nothing more than an average person in the eyes of the others.

******

Blackboard Region Border

Noon, Sunny

The green hills looked as though they were covered by a gigantic green rug which stretched all the way to the horizon.

Shoo shoo shoo!

A fleet of black humanoid mechs with circular discs imprinted on their chest plates was engaging in a battle over the hills against numerous red and white mechs.

“Who the hell are you guys!? Don’t you guys know that we’re the stationed troops over here at the Blackboard Region Borders!?” one of the black mechs loudly roared. The response to his question came in the form of a white steel trident being stabbed through the cockpit at its chest.

“No…!” Bang! The black mech exploded in a ball of flames. The white and red mech that stood right in front of him pulled his trident back, seemingly letting out a few chuckles.

“Open fire!”

The remaining black mechs readied their double-handed cannons and started firing in the direction of the white and red mechs. Light orange cannon shots started raining down through the sky, but somehow none of the shots managed to land anywhere close to the white and red mechs.

“Too slow! Too slow! Hahaha!” one of the white and red mechs burst out in laughter, easily dodging the cannon shots coming its way. With a swift flick of its trident, it managed to slash through another black mech’s chest.

Bang!

Another one burst into a ball of flames.

Meanwhile, the remaining black mechs had their backs against a wall. Comparing the pilots’ skills or the mechs, the black mechs were vastly inferior to the white and red mechs on both aspects. At this point, their frontlines have almost been completely annihilated.

It was at this moment that a huge black mech started rising up from below.

“How dare you invade my Blackboard Region!” this black mech clad in a Viking helm roared out loudly. With a sword in one hand and a shield in the other, the mech charged straight towards the white and red mechs above.

On his way up, he passed by an out of position white and red mech. With a flash of silver light, a clean cut appeared across the cockpit of the white and red mech. After a couple of sparks, the entire mech exploded as it crashed down to the ground.

“Invaders! Go to hell!” the mech in the Viking helm let out another hoarse roar. Raising up his shield, he aimed the pointed edge on the center of his shield at the leading white and red mech and charged straight towards it.

“Finally, someone who’s somewhat decent appeared,” the white and red mech let out a chuckle. With a flip, it started lunging downwards while throwing his trident towards its opponent. At the same time, the mech’s mouth started to turn slightly red as it opened its mouth.

Whooo!!

A bright red laser was fired from its mouth, directed towards the Viking helm mech.

“What? A laser from the mouth!?” the Viking helm mech was surprised.”But this kind of particle doesn’t stand a chance against my shield! Moron!”

What he failed to notice was that the particle beam wasn’t aimed at him to begin with. It was aimed at the handle of the trident that he’d thrown earlier with utmost precision, creating a huge explosion.

Bam!

In a puff of smoke, the trident was propelled by the explosion, causing it to accelerate to tremendous speeds and even break the sound barrier. In an instant, it hit the side of the black mech’s shield.

Clank!

The Viking helm mech’s shield was flung away and a large chunk of his right upper shoulder was ripped away by the trident, revealing the malfunctioning circuit boards.

At the last moment, he’d managed to steer the mech away using high leveled piloting skill, narrowly escaping death. However, this near-death experience definitely left him drenched in cold sweat.

Hearing the sound of the trident crashing to the ground, the Viking helm mech no longer underestimated his opponent. He raised his two-handed sword up as he glared at his opponent with absolute concentration.

“Oh? You managed to dodge that. You’re not half bad,” the leader of the white and red mechs had a glowing green gem embedded in its chest plate, looking slightly different from the other red and white mechs. Although the voice from inside the mech had been heavily altered electronically, from that monotonous line, he could sense the mocking tone the opponent had.

“Who the hell are you people!?” the Viking helm mech shouted loudly, “I am Commander Bender of the 7th Squad of the Blackboard Region Borders Stationed Military! Name yourself! Invaders!”

“Your level should almost be at around Level 4, not bad,” the white and red mech laughed coldly, “but that’s as far as you’ll go.”

“We’ve wasted enough time, Milu,” out of nowhere, another black electric ball appeared next to the white and red mech. From inside the ball, out came another white and red mech with a similar green gem on its chest plate, with the same electronically altered voice. “The leaders are gonna be here soon, let’s stop wasting time.”

“Understood! Understood! I rarely get to come out on these expeditions, so I had a little too much fun.”

The Viking helm mech started to feel like he was in danger.

“Another one!?” He frantically pressed the emergency report button in the mech cockpit.

Woo… Woo… Woo…

For the first time in years, a piercing alarm sounded from below.

“Let’s finish this quickly!” the second green gem mech said coldly.

“Stop nagging!”

The two mechs suddenly lunged down at high speed, far exceeding their movement speed from earlieras well as the reaction speed of a Level 4 mech pilot’s willpower. The movement left a streak of green across the sky.

The two green trails intersected right at the location of the Viking helm mech which was attempting to escape. After the exchange, the two mechs appeared once again.

Bang!!

The Viking helm mech immediately burst open and was engulfed in flames as it crashed towards the ground.

At the same time, the other black mechs were also being picked off one by one, exploding into balls of fire.

A few of the white and red mechs moved to the ground to collect the remains of their fallen allies. After collecting everything, they charged towards the Blackboard Region. After a short while, the sky was once again filled with countless silhouettes of mechs. All of them were the white and red mechs, with one of leaving a trail of green light as it moved. They formed a huge “Light” character in the sky, standing out a lot.

“Pick up your paces. Once we’ve approached the target, everyone will scatter and move individually. We will regroup once again at the target location, understand?” the green light mech gave out his orders as they sped through the sky.

“Understood,” four voices echoed one another.

The synchronized answer displayed the amount of discipline this group had.

This team consisted of 4 green gem mechs, all with a glowing green diamond gem embedded in their white and red mechs. If the Viking helm mech who had just been defeated saw this time, he would’ve been shell-shocked.

The green gem on the mechs symbolized that they were mech pilots who are almost at Level 5. Now, there were four of these people just within this team. However, what was more terrifying was that the one leading this group was someone who’s even stronger. It was someone that exceeded even Level 5.

Suddenly, the green light mech turned his attention to his right.

“That was unexpectedly fast,” inside the mech, a red-headed male in a white mask said with his head held low. His mech followed suit and went into a fighting stance.

“It’s the Blackboard Academy Elites, Sir Guccidor!” the entire team came to an immediate halt as one of the green gem mechs reported.

“They must be the Elite Students stationed at the nearby Academy Branch. Don’t get too cocky, these types of enemies are at least Level 3 and above.” The leader Guccidor cautioned calmly. “The opponent has a Level 5 Instructor level experts in their ranks. If we do not manage to end this confrontation within 2 minutes, all members scatter and retreat.”

“Yes!”

Guccidor was calmly observing the fire red humanoid mech flying over in the distance. On the back of the mech, two wings were spread wide. Its diamond-shaped eyes were glowing in an icy cold green.

“Level 5 expert… Fiery Kaizen! How interesting…” he let out a small grin.

Clank!

A straight alloy knife sprung out from his mech’s arm.

Chapter 813: Woven Web 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Time flew by, and Garen and Celine had already stayed in the hospital for over half a month. After a few visits from friends and family, the two were safely discharged, as the injuries on their body were almost fully healed even after there was a small hiccup in the middle of recovery. Garen’s physique received praises from his attending doctors and nurses, as it was a physique attained by strong athletes, yet it was seen on a normal student.

With an average of 1.5 points increment from normal people’s physical attributes, he displayed nearly twice the overall qualities of a normal human body.

Upon his return to the academy, the final match had already ended. The award money was directly transferred to Garen’s account.

Life returned to the daily routine of classes and training in the battlenet. However, the two geniuses that had emerged from the finals, Celine and Nonosiva, had slightly prolonged the excitement. These two bastards that suddenly came out of nowhere nearly had the chance to claim the thrones of the top three and drag Caus down by a notch.

Of course, Garen didn’t have the time to care for such trivial matters. He was busy attending to the clients Celine had contacted, after all, Blue Narcissus had gained some publicity after this.

Within his dorm, Garen greeted them with his hand extended to welcome them in.

“There’s not much for me to serve you, but do sit anywhere as you please.”

The two people who just came in observed every corner of his dorm room. These two people were clients introduced by Celine to examine the goods, in respect to Celine, as well as potentially reap greater benefits. The two of them had personally come instead of sending their henchmen to examine the goods.

Among the two, one of them was a gentle-looking man wearing a white shirt and glasses, the other was a red-dressed girl with slightly puffy shoulder-length hair.

“Student Nono, let’s not delay any longer, just show us the goods.” the man was named Wade, and he didn’t mention his surname. Regardless, he was still rich and influential. He adjusted his glasses before returning his gaze to Garen.

“I’ve already prepared the goods, however, it would be impossible to display it out in the open. I shall show it to you immediately,” Garen nodded. He then retrieved a bottle of highly potent fuel powder from the cupboard in his room.

Within the transparent glass bottle he just brought out were powdery, pale yellow shards. Some were still clumped into tiny pebbles.

Garen passed the bottle to the man and then retrieved another one for the girl to examine.

“For the two of you to have personally come all this way, it is obvious that you’re familiar with this thing. Tell me, what you think of its purity?” Garen smiled as he said.

The two lowered their heads, opened the bottle and poured out a little of its contents. They examined it closely.

The girl dabbed her finger into it and gave it a taste.

“Quite good, there are higher amounts of impurities as well,” the girl replied softly. Her name was Vivienne Sina, and apart from her family’s background, she was familiar with chemical productions. Her family business thrived on it.

“A thousand kilograms of these could net a purity around 600 kilograms. The ratio itself is quite good already.”

“I just need to know, how much is your purchase price altogether?” Garen waved his hand, his back leaned against the cupboard and asked with a smile.

“Purchase price… let’s not talk about that for now, we’re much more interested in the methods of extraction for this,” the girl smiled while twirling a few strands of her silky hair around the tip of her finger. “If you can provide information of the extraction methods, I’ll be willing to offer this price.”

She extended two fingers on one hand and formed a fist with the other.

“Two million.” [1]

For a normal academy student, even if he was a bit of a genius, a genius who had not matured bore no significance. To offer two million Units was her giving face to Celine.

“How is it? The price is quite high already,” the girl tossed the bottle back and forth and smiled as she replied.

“High?” Garen anticipated such problems would surface early on, hence he wasn’t provoked, “That bottle in your hand alone is worth more than ten million, yet you’re telling me that you’re purchasing the extraction techniques for two million? If I were to truly intend to hand over the knowledge of the techniques, why wouldn’t I donate it to the academy higher-ups? I’ll be able to attain the higher-ups’ attention as well, maybe even receive closer attention in nurturing me when I become an elite.”

The girl’s smile slowly faded away.

“Two million is already not a small amount… There are some things that can’t even be bought once gone, even with all the money in the world.”

“Oh? Are you threatening me?” Garen remained unfazed. “With just your two master bodyguards standing right outside the door?” he wore a shy smile, like how a normal boy saw his crush.

“Perhaps Celine did not mention to you what would happen to anyone who threatens me within 50 meters?”

“Ho ho ho ho….” the girl nodded and replied, “You truly are formidable in a fight. But no matter how long you can last in one, some things only require one instance to eliminate someone.”

“I will kill you first before that happens,” Garen narrowed his eyes.

“You’re quite mad!”

“You may try.”

The atmosphere suddenly froze, as a red electronic key appeared in the girl’s hand. Her thumb rested on its red button, ready to press it at any moment.

Garen folded his arms across his chest, silently staring down his opponent as a sliver of killing intent oozed into his stance. For such a thing as killing intent, which bore no visible shape, it was more like a physical display of determination. From a person’s actions and gaze, along with various subtle movements, one could determine whether or not that person truly intended to kill. A true killing intent, when released through spoken words and the body’s base capability, could completely and truly manifest as an intent of desiring death upon another. This form of biological electric field could generate subtle effects on another being. This was what most people could interpret as a killing intent.

Perhaps other wouldn’t be able to tell the difference, yet the man with the glasses at the side secretly exuded already. He was able to tell, that Garen really would kill without hesitance if they can’t come to an agreement! This sort of killing intent was the kind that he would commonly see on his master bodyguards.

“Alright, alright, everyone, take a step back, each of you take one step back,” the man hurriedly stepped between the two to mediate.

If a fight really broke out, Blackboard Academy’s law and security system would arrive on foot within the vicinity in thirty seconds. Under the cooperation of a squad of various genius masters, it could be assumed that anyone would be caught to face trial before even escaping through the academy gates.

With the strengths of Blackboard Academy, no one would care whether you were a normal student or an influential disciple. The patrol squads upholding academy laws consisted of elites from the inner academy. In a situation where they monitored everywhere, even if the person had any viable connections, he or she could only bring them up after being detained.

And once detained, the elderly shareholders within the inner academy court couldn’t be persuaded with valuable riches. They would stick by the judgment even if it was execution by firing squads, regardless of identity or background, in the name of equality! The only exception was if the person in question was a genius in the academy, then he or she may be looked upon with a more positive light.

As such, Garen had bet on them being unable to fight on academy grounds. Only then did he dare to threaten his opponent without wavering.

“Actually, as long as we don’t demand the extraction techniques, then there will be many agreements to be made. We all seek to profit together, yes?” he smiled, as he took the initiative to warm the atmosphere.

The girl’s eyes darted around before she smiled as well.

“My sincere apologies, it was merely a joke just now. I wanted to see how big of a determination you have in safeguarding your techniques. You should know that if we were to cooperate, and others came in to scour your techniques, one misstep could waste all our invested time and money. So I decided to test you beforehand.”

She changed the topic.

“But truth to be told, I do have thoughts of purchasing the extraction techniques. Although I was joking just now, if student Nono really does decide to sell it, remember to contact me first, alright~” the girl twirled a few strands of her hairs as her body leaned forward, suddenly closing the gap between her and Garen. Her body was releasing a perfumed scent mixed with her body’s natural scent, which permeated Garen’s nostrils.

“I will definitely remember you. Student Vivienne,” Garen replied without a change in his expression.

The two smiled at one another. The sensation of readying themselves to draw blood from before had vanished completely.

“I’ve brought a contract regarding our cooperation, it entails the terms and conditions for our joint business. Take a look,” Garen took out several white sheets of information he’d prepared beforehand from below his study desk. He separated them into two piles for each of them to see.

The two received and read through them as doubt and suspicion lightly flashed across their faces.

In the contract, it was stated that the two of them shall contribute in two parts, improving purity levels and trade marketing. Each of them shall reap in ten percent of the profits. This treatment… it wasn’t bad, rather, it was too good.

“You certainly drive a crude bargain here…” the man with the glasses, Wade, exclaimed slightly, “if we go according to your calculations, when we reach the expected return for a month, with each of us receiving ten percent of the profits, there will be at least ten million Units to be gained from dividing it all. It would total up to over hundred million units in a year! What we want to do, however, can be handled by anyone else which we could easily find, as the demand for highly potent fuel powders now is high everywhere.”

The red-dressed girl, Vivienne, kept quiet and remained motionless.

“Though it’s easy to talk about it, for us to be responsible for the aspects of sales and trading, we’ll definitely be targets of investigation for the source it all. And when that happens, there will be a lot of problems coming our way. This contract is not enough.”

Garen remained unchanged in his expression.

“So what Miss Vivienne suggesting is?”

“Without our protection, your goods can never be distributed. The risks are too high. I guarantee that there are many who wish to interfere. You alone reaping seventy percent is too much,” Vivienne calmly objected. “I primarily handle sales and trading, so I bear the highest risks. I want an additional thirty percent.”

Additional thirty percent!

The heart of the man with glasses skipped a beat. Although he was familiar with Vivienne’s personality, he always knew that her appetite knew no bounds. She was used to extravagant personal spendings and thus had accumulated a huge debt. But for her to immediately ask for forty percent of the profits upon investing in a trading post? Even this condition was slightly over the top for the most overbearing of influential individuals to demand of.

And with so much likely interferences from others? Business would only net around less than two hundred million in a month. Though it would still be acceptable in the eyes of children, such amounts were paltry in the eyes of masterminds.

“I cannot allow thirty percent. Truth to be told, Miss Vivienne, setting yours and Celine’s cut aside along with following the example figures, twenty percent is accounted for profit turnovers and tax payments. Moreover, the remaining fifty percent does not belong to me entirely,” he replied honestly.

“Oh?” Vivienne was stunned, “Tell us, who else is there? Perhaps this person will be willing to show face to the Sina Family,” she replied without a change in her expression.

“Thirty percent of it will be donated to the Blue Narcissus public funds. It will act as shared funds for everyone belonging to the organization,” Garen shared a much more shocking statement with an unfazed expression.

“The public funds of Blue Narcissus!?” this time, even Vivienne’s heart jumped greatly.

For the first time, she carefully stared and measured this boy from a commoner background with her very eyes. His name was Nonosiva, yes? She recalled this person’s name. Such daring confidence! To easily donate away thirty percent of profits which amounted to more than thirty million units a month, all to contribute towards the Blue Narcissus public funds.

From what she knew.

All donations would be openly displayed on the public screens of Blue Narcissus. This sum would be distributed equally to every single member. Although it bore no huge effects on an individual scale, it would certainly address a few problems.

TL Note:

[1] The raws state 二十万, where 万 is a unit representing ten thousand, hence Vivienne Sina’s gesture was twenty instead of two.

Chapter 814: Woven Web 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Firstly, the family influence of the head of finance in Blue Narcissus, Britney, stemmed from the inner circles of the academy. Her power capabilities stretched out far and wide, yet she could only be described as a scrooge. If any money, once pocketed by her, was requested to be refunded, it would be the end of her! As a member of the Sina Family, although Vivienne herself possessed a wide reach of connections and power in Blackboard City and several nearby cities, when compared to the Britney Family which was truly on a high level, it was on a completely different tier altogether.

The Family companies within Blackboard City were all powerful in their own right. Their influences could be broken down into four levels overall: small-sized, medium-sized, large-sized, which was capable of altering the balance of the city’s economy, as well as the heavy-sized, which completely dominated the seats of leaders! Vivienne’s Sina Family belonged to only the large-sized power group. Britney’s, however, belonged to the heavy-sized group. Those who belonged to the heavy-sized power groups were all closely interconnected with those with power.

Secondly, in order to withdraw money donated to Blue Narcissus, such an action will need to be publicly announced on screen. This was financial transparency. Moreover, every member would naturally receive an email notification regarding it as well. Following human nature, in regards to one’s financial assets, the more the better. Nothing could go wrong with increasing numbers, as it would always be a delight to see.

The moment people heard that their assets were lowered, however, people would start feeling uncomfortable. They would certainly mind, especially when there’s a decrease out of the blue.

More than ten million Units of income, all of it could be divided to each member as a small gift or bonus every month. For Vivienne to barge in and snatch away this part of the profits would mean going against everyone in Blue Narcissus. It would still be acceptable if she was a member of Blue Narcissus. The problem was, she was a member of Thousand Year Tree.

Blue Narcissus housed two thousand influential disciples, including but not limited to princes and princesses. If this group of people was ever displeased… Vivienne gave up the notion of that train of thought.

Truly a man who’s aware of his own strengths and weaknesses in situations! There could only be gains if you were willing to lose, anyone can understand the meaning of it. However, only a rare few could successfully integrate it into their actions.

She carefully stared at Garen, as if she was trying to engrave the person in her memory.

“No offense is intended, but if I were you, I couldn’t possibly do what you suggested,” she’d finally wholly recognized the person before her as an equal to discuss dealings with. She saw from the person before her a towering demeanor and presence similar to that of her father’s.

“For things like money, the bigger the hunger, the more profits one can consume. So long as one refrains from being too greedy, that is,” Garen chuckled.

“Yeah. Not too greedy,” Vivienne had considered herself to be a bold and cunning person already. Never did she imagine that she would encounter someone greater than her at the same age. “Nonosiva, let us proceed according to your contract’s terms then. For the first shipment of White Rainbow Stones, do you need my help in finding a channel?” this time she gave in for real. This fellow before her had gained the attention of the academy’s higher-ups, even more so within the sights of the prince and princesses within Blue Narcissus. All of these were enough weight for her to speak with him on equal footing.

“There will be no need for your help in the matter, I’ve already found some channels. I am just in the middle of selecting the most optimal one,” Garen politely rejected.

“How about this then. Here I have some contacts for enquiring information. If you have need of their services, you can just directly contact them. Give them my name, and they will definitely give you face,” Vivienne nodded. “Regarding the shipment teams, however, I will not be involved in the matter. That would be the strength of the Celine Family.”

“May our partnership lead to great wealth,” upon seeing the atmosphere shift to warmth, the man with the glasses, Wade, finally let out a sigh of relief and extended his hand.

Garen and Vivienne extended theirs as well. The three of them placed their hands on top of one another, signifying their mutual agreement.

After further discussing the details and dates of their partnership, Vivienne and Wade bid farewell and left, bringing with them their bodyguards outside.

After traveling a few hundred meters away, Vivienne hung her head in silence as she tread forward, so low that she didn’t notice her family’s hover car. If not for the bodyguard’s reminder, she would’ve walked straight past it.

“Still thinking about that Nonosiva?” Wade could see through her thoughts.

“Yeah,” Vivienne nodded, “this person is very impressive. He didn’t seem like someone who’s yet to reach his twenties,” she recalled that Nonosiva had been calm and collected from the beginning up to the end, without a stutter nor any sign of shock throughout. That pair of deep blue eyes appeared like pools of calm water, unmoving and untampered. She took in a small breath of cold air as she thought about him.

“That fellow…. It felt as if the entire flow of the discussion went accordingly to his expectations. He displayed his determination and ruthlessness, then revealed his true intentions in the end with the backing of Blue Narcissus acting as his shield. He was both harsh and gentle…. Facing him made me feel like I was facing my grandfather.”

“The old man?” Wade was stunned.

“No, I meant his presence,” Vivienne instinctively shook her head, “his methods and speech skills were not considered amazing. However, he gave off this sensation whereby he’ll act as he soon as he spoke about something with no wavering hesitation. That once he makes a decision, no outside forces will be able to change what he sets on… This person is really impressive! Now that I think about it, I’m slightly afraid of him even.”

Wade was somewhat surprised. This was the second time Vivienne had praised him with the word ‘impressive’. It was obvious that Nonosiva had left a very deep impression on her.

Upon seeing Wade’s somewhat confused look, Vivienne huffed. She knew that he had little to no experience in dealing with these methods of deceit, as his mind was not sensitive enough to these sort of matters. She then explained to him.

“You only look at one point. From the beginning till the end, we could say that none of our objectives were achieved. Not a single bit of progress was made. Everything from this document of information and terms of the contract were all prepared by him beforehand. In other words, our trip here has led us to return with empty hands.”

With that said, Wade was slightly astonished as well.

“So you’re saying, that before we even reached there, he already knew how it would end?”

“Not that he knew how it would end, but rather having it ended according to what he wanted,” Vivienne’s gaze grew distant. “He’s so young, probably eighteen years old this year…”

“Don’t think too much about it, Vivienne,” Wade smiled bitterly.

“I’m not overthinking, it’s just… Forget it, not going to talk about it.” Vivienne knew that she matured faster than most, and boys and girls of the same age had no idea on how to have fun with her. She’d integrated herself into the society of adults way too early, while Wade was different.

****************

Inside the dormitory.

After Vivienne and Wade had left, Garen locked the door. He opened the computer terminal in his watch and looked through the list of contacts.

What he said to Vivienne were not lies. True enough, before his period of stay in the hospital, he’d contacted the people of Blue Narcissus to transfer the information he had along with plans for the donations. A recently joined member of the organization came before Vivienne and Wade did. This Blue Narcissus member came earlier to examine the products and left with a contract detailing the thirty percent profits of the deal.

The head of finance in Blue Narcissus, Britney, was extremely happy. She even took the initiative in calling him when she joined a ball. She encouraged him and gave him the contact of the deputy head of the department. She told him that if he contacted the man, he would always be ready to assist his needs.

Garen had predicted as such and thought as much. The one thing he couldn’t foresee was that… the public screens of Blue Narcissus did not display any new entries of assets.

“No doubt Britney has taken everything for herself….” Garen smiled bitterly.

This was favorable as well, however. Compared to dividing it for every single member whereby nobody would bat an eye, it was better for all of it to be given to Britney. His goals were achieved anyway. Besides, this outcome reeled in a greater impact.

Britney’s family possessed a tremendous influence over Blackboard Academy and the entire Blackboard City. Her family was one of the two most powerful families in the entire Blackboard City. They kept close or indirect connections with two of the three highest ranking professors in the academy.

The aftereffect of his ‘tribute’ being entirely consumed was that Garen had reeled in an even bigger fish than he’d originally intended.

“No matter, the outcome is all the same anyway,” he looked at the list of contacts. He’d already figured as much. If the income was rapidly realized into fruition, then his network of special relations would rapidly expand. Only then could he truly root himself into interwoven connections and link all of it into one tremendous power. Right from the start, the matter of income hadn’t concerned him at all and it was alright as long as he had enough to spend. With tens of millions as profit, it would be sufficient for his businesses to flourish. More importantly, a higher purity level of highly potent fuel powders required him to gather White Peacock Stones. As such, his most crucial goal would be achieved. As long as these influential disciples aspired to reap in fortunes, then he’d have access to an endless supply of free White Peacock Stones. That way it wouldn’t attract unwanted attention due to an overflow of shipments, nor would it be stolen by interfering outsiders due to trading divisions’ application of highly potent fuel powders.

If not for the fear of raising suspicions, Garen would’ve set aside ten percent for performance shares instead of the current forty percent.

Thirty percent had been given to Britney, and another thirty percent divided between Vivienne, Wade, and Celine. The remaining forty percent was for him alone.

As he pondered, Garen rubbed above his lips and felt a slight growth of mustache on him.

“It is still a little too much for me. I can still divide it out, just to avoid drawing attention to myself. But who should I divide it to?”

Britney of Blue Narcissus was already not bad, as she would be able to keep this small business under wraps. Then the next step would be seeking out those influential disciples who were keen on splurging, in debt or aspiring to start up a business of their own. It would be slightly risky to invest in just one city as well. It would be best to build a network in the city which supplied White Rainbow Stones.

As he pondered carefully, Garen didn’t have any potential candidates. He set aside that notion for now.

If this worked out successfully, then his greatest profit would be the endless supply of White Peacock Stones and the grand network of connections.

Two million Units worth of income was just an initial estimation. As the Hellfrost Peacock Technique further developed in growth down the line, the demand for White Peacock Stones would continually increase. Profit would snowball more and more as well. When that happened, this stream of small income for influential disciples would gradually garner more and more attention. As for Nonosiva (Garen), he would become a key figure who was respected by all through this extraction technique.

As for the risks of the technique being stolen, however, until that time came, Garen was confident that he would have completely matured and his potential would have transformed into that of formidable power. He’d then gain the ability to speak terms with influential disciples on even grounds.

The network of special relations as of now would become a shield for his life. Whoever decided to threaten him would be going against everyone within this beneficial network. Anyone would rethink carefully and weigh the consequences before they would act against him. This was his actual goal.

“Next, time to see how things are with Kendall,” Garen dialed the number for the old driver, Kendall. Ever since this fellow had shipped over those White Rainbow Stones, he’d returned home to rest. Now, he presumed that Kendall was waiting anxiously.

Chapter 815: Woven Web 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the Blackboard Academy courtyard.

In a corridor within the battleship navy base with silver walls and ceilings, a young man in black with a red disc insignia on his back walked slowly down the corridor. His tall, slender figure, calm expression, and shiny black hair tied in a ponytail gave off a sophisticated air.

As he turned around a corner, the young man reached a fork in the path. The right corridor led down a pitch black path while the path forward was a long-winded silver corridor, with only a couple of light bulbs blinking on the walls.

Sssst…

Suddenly, a white screen extended out from atop the ceiling at the corridor in front of him. The electronic screen expanded automatically and unfolded from one screen to three which aligned with one another, in a similar fashion to unfolding paper.

All three screens suddenly blinked to life, the middle screen revealing a face of a platinum-haired beauty.

“Blacklight 11, please directly head towards the meeting room. The three professors are in a discussion regarding the newest intel,” the beautiful girl spoke to the young man in a lowered voice.

“I understand,” the young man nodded, “Can you guide me please, I am unfamiliar with the newly configured layout.”

“Not a problem.”

The beautiful girl smiled. She pressed a few buttons on the control panel before her. Suddenly, the silver metal flooring below the young man rose panel by panel automatically. These panels reconstructed themselves into a curved-shaped, mini silver hover car. The young man was then lifted up by it.

“Careful with your words, my grandfather is not in the best of moods,” the platinum-haired beauty gently reminded.

“I know, I know,” the young man with the ponytail smiled and waved his hand. He was carried by the mini hover car and traveled deep within the corridors at high speed.

As he swiftly traveled in the empty and quiet battleship corridor for half an hour, white light beamed out from the front of the hovercar and lit up the dark corridors.

The ponytailed youngster observed the changes in his surroundings.

“Why is there a need for headquarters to be this big? What is this? A labyrinth? It’s about the size of a city!”

Soon, the hovercar reached a crossroad. As he exited from the path he traveled, two hover cars exited from two other paths simultaneously. Both had passengers onboard as well.

A black-haired girl and a brute, both wearing the same black shirt with red disc insignia.

“Borus, it’s been a while,” the young man greeted the brute.

“Ah, Matthew and Allie. For all three of us to be summoned, wonder what kind of mess we will be tasked to handle? A rare occasion indeed,” with mane-like yellow hair and a small yellow beard below his chin, he bore a wild appearance.

The black-haired girl remained unmoved; she seemed to be the quiet type.

The young man with the ponytail chuckled. He waited till the three hover cars had converged and entered the wide corridor in front of them before speaking again.

“I heard there was trouble at the borders. Heard anything?”

“Oh.. trouble? What kind of trouble? I’ve been spending most of my time on the battlenet lately,” Borus took out a piece of chocolate out of nowhere and popped it into his mouth.

“A rather irksome one. There’s a military camp in the outer plains, and all of its members are former elite students. If they can’t even handle this, then it’s obvious as to why we’re all summoned here,” Matthew nodded. “Enough chatter, we’re almost there.”

Their hover cars soon entered a ring-shaped, silver grand hall.

A halo of yellow light glowed above them and crimson crystal lining was spread across the floor, resembling a vast completed circuitry.

The halo directly lit up the ring region below, which consisted of three hovering seats levitating high above the ground. A thin layer of light from a white screen surrounded it. A seated person could be seen through the screens.

“You’ve arrived?” an aged voice sounded from beyond the screen. “Please be seated.”

The way to the corridors around the grand hall was automatically sealed shut and replaced by sturdy metallic silver walls.

Boom!

After the walls had descended, the surfaces of the grand hall pulsed with a vibrant layer of silver light, disappearing as quickly as it appeared.

“To have urgently summoned you all this time around, the purpose is to address the attack from unidentified forces in the outer plains,” the old man spoke in a lowered voice.

Matthew looked at the three hovering seats before him. The three seats were positioned ten meters away from one another in a circular formation, yet they only took up a tenth of the grand hall’s entirety. Located in the central area of the grand hall, it had a vast and chilling atmosphere.

“Unidentified forces in the outer plains? Is there any updated intel?” he adjusted himself and answered.

“Although I’m aware it’s not good to bother any of you on your days off, only the three of you are the closest to that point,” the old man sighed.

As the meeting started, the entire flooring of the grand hall had lit up unexpectedly, emitting a slightly dazzling light which shone through the circuit-like crimson linings.

A moment of hissing sounds passed before the entire flooring then transfigured into a huge display screen. A view of towering mountains and rivers was revealed before the three people.

Between the intertwining lush ravines, two human-shaped mechs, one red with white and one red, soared in a high-speed pursuit to kill. Gauss rounds and red laser beams were fired all around the area. A gigantic ax weaponry and wings lined with chainsaw blades on the red mech continuously clashed with the opponent, inducing piercing sounds upon impact.

Boom!!

A grenade was lobbed from the person below the engagement, leading to a sudden explosion. It engulfed a large, ten-meter area in a sea of flames.

Matthew instantly recognized the red-winged mech.

“Fiery Kaizen Zabrook, a graduate from the previous batch. Who could possibly be a match for him at this level?”

“That’s Phantom Steps, alright,” the yellow-haired brute at the side rubbed his small beard and said. A glint of interest in his eyes. “Just as I couldn’t find a worthy opponent, then this fellow came along? How convenient….”

“Your mission is to stop this assault mech which has entered my borders. They all share the same red and white distinction in appearance,” the old man’s voice resounded through the screen.

“If possible, ascertain their origins,” another old lady answered from beyond the lit up screens, carrying a note of concern in her voice.

“I have no problems with killing, but I’ll be leaving the fuss of gathering intel to Allie,” the yellow-haired brute plucked a strand from his beard and fidgeted with it.

“Not a problem,” the black-haired girl finally voiced out.

Matthew remained silent. He continued to spectate the combat between Kaizen and the opposition with his head lowered.

“Did you just say the opposing ‘squad’? How many people are there overall?”

“For strengths of this caliber, there should be three people at least.”

“Three, eh? Should be around four or five if that’s the case. I can have some fun this time around. Hehe…” the yellow-haired brute snickered.

“From the looks of things, they still have an ace leader in their ranks. I’ve already dispatched Medero.”

“Huh? Medero…”

As the three of them heard this name, the yellow-haired brute reacted the most strongly.

“Not to worry, Shadi. The opposition is fairly strong. The three of you alone wouldn’t necessarily be enough to handle them,” the old man assured them.

“Booooooriiiiing! There’s no need for us now with Medero sent out!” the brute, Shadi, clutched at his hair in frustration. “Damn it, I might as well return to the battlenet!”

“There will be opportunities for us, I’m sure,” Matthew gazed at the intense battle visualized below and spoke in a lowered voice. “The opposition is no ordinary force…”

“Do not underestimate your enemies. Go now,” the old man ordered. “The mission points amount to fifteen million, following level three protocols.”

“Aww yeah! This I like!” Shadi shouted aloud.

Matthew couldn’t help but whistle in response. Allie, however, lowered her head in silence with fists clenched.

Rumble!!

In that instant, in the screen below, Fiery Kaizen in his red mech had finally found an opening and fired a merciless strike at the red and white mech. It directly struck the red and white mech at the chest region.

In the end, it was a tie with both suffered severe damage. The two mechs fell from the sky, thick clouds of smoke following their descent.

This instant suddenly caught everyone’s attention. The three individuals within the grand hall were astonished at what had transpired.

“What happened!? Wasn’t that last hit supposed to be Senior Kaizen’s opportune strike!?” Matthew said in a lowered voice.

“This is where I’m asking you all to be wary of.” The old man answered in a lowered voice, “Best if you could salvage the wreckage of their mechs. This can be considered a training for all of you. It can’t be helped, but your instructors are needed to be dispatched.”

“Understood.”

**********************

“It’s a pleasure meeting you, I am Carlos Raymundo Bojack Mishka. This is my full name, and as you can see, I am noblemen from the Angela Kingdom.”

In Garen’s watch terminal, the screen displayed a curly-haired man dressed in a golden-brown, extravagant garment. The man in his extravagant robe wore long socks of white. His head of curly golden hair gave off the impression of a golden retriever.

Even more cringe-worthy, however, was the immediately obvious, fake and distasteful smile on his face.

Such a distorted smile completely ruined his initially dashing appearance. He resembled a hilarious, comedic clown.

“Pleasure meeting you. I am Nonosiva, your current long-term contract business client,” Garen replied with the same manner of speaking, a calm smile on his face.

This must be a minor person of territorial nobility that took great lengths in establishing contact with him. The White Rainbow Stones production sites in his territory were conveniently much more profitable in terms of cost performance index and transport costs.

Earlier, Garen had looked him up through the information provided by Kendall for a clearer understanding of the man. He then immediately called the man’s number.

At first, he thought that this man would be the same as the graceful nobles in the Totem World. He didn’t expect to meet this sort of character.

Looking at the man’s appearance, it felt like he was trying to mimic someone’s composure, yet never quite managed to bring it into effect. In the end, the result was a look of giddiness and that of a complete fool.

Did all minor nobles of the Angela Kingdom act in this manner?

Garen had rated him very poorly in his mind. Judging by the man’s getup, he was most likely someone who thought highly of himself.

The Angela Kingdom was actually the Polar Region in the outer borders of Blackboard Region. Famously known for their aurora residue production, various Rainbow Stones were byproducts of aurora residue borders, similar to how soot was produced from burning fuel. Due to costly chemical production methods, their value of application was fairly low. As such, they were treated as mere trinkets and accessories by conventional businessmen.

Rather than a constitutional monarchy, the Polar Region still followed the imperial preference ruling system. The king belonged to the highest nobility with absolute command over the militia and the lands of the kingdom.

“Regarding the issues of White Rainbow Stones… could you lower the price on your side a little more…?” after affirming the man’s identity, he began to flex his silver tongue.

Carlos acted as such on the opposite end as well. The business deal this time around was different from past dealings. In one month, the interest rate within the entire territory would rise by fifty percent. The White Rainbow Stones were small stones scattered all around in their area. As they were in abundance, they had little to no value. From Carlos’s perspective, he would gain this pile of money in exchange for nothing from this deal.

Chapter 816: Woven Web 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The negotiation price between the two individuals fluctuated up and down as the duo began their long-winded battle between silver tongues. Both listed out various reasons and the difficulties they had to face, trying their best to steer towards the most beneficial outcome for themselves.

Half an hour soon passed. The terminal on Garen’s watch chimed; the first batch of highly potent fuel powders had been sold. A total of ten bottles were in this shipment, and each bottle weighed around a thousand grams. They were sold not in accordance with market value, but through a channel found by Blue Narcissus. As it was a test batch and sold in small quantities, Garen released the first batch. Costing ten million Units per kilogram of highly potent fuel powders, as he expected, did not have many transactions.

He used his hacking skills to scour for the value differences on the internet. He ran simulations in comparing prices to ensure that both sides would gain profits without suffering too much loss on his end.

As he glanced at the figures displayed on his watch, he’d obtained a hundred million units of profit in total. Forty million Units were transferred to his account, and more than thirty million remained after tax deduction.

“Money sure does flow around quick….”

With more than enough leverage, Garen’s foundation suddenly became more than enough for his means.

“For the first batch, we need five hundred pieces. Shouldn’t be a problem, yes? All of them must adhere to the previous large sizes with no inferior qualities,” Garen straight up demanded five hundred pieces. “This will only be the initial quantity. May our partnership be a successful one, as we may increase our orders in the future.”

“Five hundred pieces….” Carlos gulped. These stones would at most cost additional labor fees, and the rest would purely be profit since these stones were everywhere. He was so broke to the point of being unable to sustain himself. Previously, he’d taken the initiative to seek out Kendall. Setting aside his dignity to act truly produced a different outcome.

“I’ll give you a rounded up price. In accordance with our previously negotiated price, it will be three Units per piece. The total amount will be a thousand and five hundred Units, including labor fees,” Garen happily transferred a thousand and five hundred Units over. “This is just the initial order. If our partnership goes well, we may increase the quantity in future orders.”

This amount of money was nothing to him. With more than thirty million just transferred into his account, a little over a thousand Units was mere rain droplets in his eyes.

“You are simply too generous,” Carlos was excited beyond words. He was actually a minor noble that had declared bankruptcy. Although the territory he’d inherited from his family was quite vast, there wasn’t an abundance of valuable resources. With the White Rainbow Stones, he could still manage to profit off them a little. In the past, he’d barely scraped by each day. Each shipment would only be around ten pieces or more, and it would take a long time to sell them all out before a second batch was needed to restock.

After living life with a tightened belt until recently, the only servant left in his family was an old butler. Not a single residence remained on his land, as no one was willing to stay long-term in a godforsaken area. Even hiring people to gather rocks required him to travel a long distance to another small town.

The garment that he had on him now was the only one he could get his hands on. It was a garment for the leader of the household passed down from his grandfather. The long periods of dire lifestyle had left him breathless, but now he’d finally seen a turning point!

“Sir Carlos, from what I gathered from my assistant, Kendall, I understand your predicament. Our previous partnership had led to great success for both of us, and this following deal will solidify the foundation of our partnership. If we can reach a long-term direction in our partnership, I believe it will be a huge help to the development of your kingdom,” Garen answered through the terminal.

“Long-term partnership…” Carlos gulped.

The two further discussed the overall details of the shipment, ascertaining the deal.

Carlos requested for three days; he’d definitely be able to successfully deliver the goods in three days’ time. After hearing that Garen was a Blackboard Academy student, he was especially confident that things would work out. Most of the students in Blackboard Academy were extremely wealthy, and a little over a thousand Units wouldn’t even bother them. Perhaps a single meal for them would cost as much. A big spender client like this needed to be kept close!

Upon resolving the issue of resources, although it was only a spoken agreement, Garen felt quite assured as he was aware that sources of White Rainbow Stones could be found everywhere. However, this particular family was more willing to deal than most. His partner’s attitude was great to work with as well. He considered the man as the most suitable business partner for this.

Moreover, it was better to provide help to someone in dire need of it as compared to going extra lengths to sweeten the deal. If he could find an even more reliable business partner in the Polar Region, it would be much more favorable for him.

Garen decided to get some rest in his dormitory since he had continually managed matters one after another. He was mildly fatigued too. He sat on his bed and practiced on his training methods but as always, there was little to no effects for him. It seemed that this method truly didn’t match with his traits.

“Guess I can only hope that absorbing high-grade White Peacock Stones will increase my Willpower,” Garen heaved a sigh as he laid down.

“Next, I’ll test out the power of absorption, Devour.”

Concerned that the hospital staff would find out his secret, he had no chance to use this power as his body condition was constantly monitored during his stay in the hospital. Now that he had returned to his dorm, he didn’t need to worry as much anymore.

“How do I activate Devour? What should I devour in order to produce effects?”

Garen picked up a glossy red apple from the table, which emitted a mild fragrance. With it in his grasps, he felt a minor chill seeping into his palm.

“Devour!”

Garen gently lifted up the apple as his inner body activated the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

In that instant, countless thin, blue lines emitted from his palms without a sound. The lines acted as if they were piercing a balloon, surging into the apple’s core. Garen’s Attribute Pane blurred slightly before it returned to normal with no obvious changes. It was clear that an apple provided too little help to his body.

However, his stomach oddly felt full.

Garen’s eyes gleamed as he recalled the message implied in a secret technique from his past life.

He then picked up the alloy pen stand from his study table. The pen stand was entirely coated in silver and molded into a statue of the world’s most brilliant physicist, Larz. Now in Garen’s hand, however, it was gradually enveloped by the same blue lines which were as thin as hairs, slowly reforming it into a blue firefly.

Minutes and seconds passed as the blue firefly slowly shrunk and became thinner.

As Garen held the blue firefly, he felt a thin stream of sticky residue seeping into his palm. The countless blue lines then spread throughout his body, and the wounds on his body seemed to be recovering slightly.

After another half an hour had passed, the blue firefly finally ceased shrinking, and remained still.

“It’s still being devoured, only at an extremely slow pace…” Garen furrowed his brows. “Based on the speed of devouring, it would take a few months to finish the process. Perhaps it was true that nothing can’t be devoured, only the rate of the process would differ.”

A thought came to his mind. He relaxed his grasp on the blue firefly, revealing the unrecognizable pen stand. The pen stand looked as if it had been melted at high temperatures and transformed into an unidentifiable metal object. Its surface was unusually smooth to the touch.

Next, he dug out rubber, pure copper, pure steel, water, cotton, and various other materials to test out the technique.

“This devouring power produces different effects with different materials. It’s likely that ninety percent of materials provide nothing more than effects of sustenance and healing. These alone are impressive enough though, as I’m only at the most basic level of using it. If I raise it to higher levels, I may produce even greater effects.”

As he’d imagined, the Hellfrost Peacock could devour a variety of things to recover from any damage taken in an instant. From here, he knew that this would be complicated to figure out.

“Metals provided healing to wounds, food can provide sustenance, while cotton had no effects. For objects of too little density, I could barely supplement my body structure with essential elements. What about highly potent fuel powders then?”

Garen suddenly thought of the wastes produced by White Peacock Stones, this stuff was a fuel that would produce a large amount of heat upon burning.

He quickly found some leftovers of the powder in his dorm cupboard.

With the powder in his palm, Garen activated Devour once more.

Once again, a large number of blue lines stem from his palm. As if they were countless tentacles, they vigorously enveloped the pouch of powder.

Sizzle….

The reaction was different from the other objects. When highly potent fuel powder was devoured, noises of crackling explosives were produced.

A reenergizing heat wave surged into Garen’s body. This heat wave produced no effects. But after encircling his body, it quickly converged in front of his abdominal area, forming a spherical object.

Garen gave a mystified look at it. He felt as if it formed into a ball of meat, slightly moving about.

“This is…” a thought suddenly came to mind. “This thing, could it be a contaminated power waste produced by Hellfrost Peacock? A Distorted Seed?”

A Distorted Seed was radiation material naturally produced by the Hellfrost Peacock. This radiation would distort the state of surrounding beings, corrupting them into bizarre, non-sentient battle machines. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique mimicked this power and produced this kind of radiation, which was able to converge into Distorted Seeds. When planted in an enemy’s heart, it would turn them into a mindless and formidable killing machine. Body quality stats and other characteristics would be multiplied by 1.5 times of their base power through the radiation.

“Not entirely. This is probably the partial product of Distorted Seeds,” Garen determined. “To think that highly potent fuel powders could churn out Distorted Seeds. This seems to be normal though. The Hellfrost Peacock is categorized as an ice lifeform, so naturally, it would not need heat energy. Instead, it would transform heat energy into Distorted Seeds, able to harm others while expelling waste formed in its body.”

“Perhaps I can find a chance to test out the effects of the Distorted Seeds. If this thing can be modified according to my will, rather than a mindless killing machine, it can be used as a quick buff and provide power to others. That would be great,” Garen was getting excited at the thought.

Even if a Hellfrost Peacock couldn’t control the Distorted Seeds, with its highly rigid blood veins capable of suppressing the Distorted Seed parasites and its potential threat intimidation, it wouldn’t rule out the possibility of it being a way to buff the Hellfrost Peacock’s powers. If he could retain his will and be able to control the unsheathing of its fangs, then…

An idea struck Garen’s mind.

The scientific technology in this world was too advanced. The research and development of human willpower rivaled to that of divine spirits. A grand scale war could even wipe out entire planets. As for the development of strengths of the human body, however, it had not been developed to the same degree of advancement.

Chapter 817: Advance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The southern region of Blackboard City.

City outskirts.

By a vast and mighty river, at a remote spot by the riverside.

A black-haired young man, slightly over ten years of age, kicked away pebbles with each step, casually walking around along the riverside. He didn’t seem to be over the age of sixteen appearance-wise. The young boy’s face was filled with helplessness.

He saw there was no one in his immediate surroundings, and couldn’t help but speak out.

“Master Red Moon, did you find the thing you were looking for?”

“Hush now! What’s the rush?” an irritated voice scolded next to his ear.

“But we’ve been walking around for half an hour. What about returning home? We’re definitely going to be late again,” the young boy felt even more helpless now. He looked at the bakery uniform he was still wearing, “I heard in recent news that many thugs run amok here. It would be troublesome if we encountered them!”

“What’s there to fear? You have me around!” Red Moon flared up. “Hush now, I’ll strangle you if you make any more noise! F*ck, you made what I’d sensed just now disappear!”

The young boy quivered and immediately went quiet.

This young boy was the junior manager of One For All Bakery, Clint. In a white servant attire, him treading along the riverside was an odd sight.

A surge of river water stirred by strong gusts of wind vigorously splashed against the muddy riverside in waves.

Suddenly a rushing wave rose up and collided with the riverside.

Splash!

Large sprays of water were abruptly stirred up, soaking Clint entirely. He couldn’t react in time when it happened. His entire uniform was soaked in an instant, drenching his person as well.

“Ah!!! My uniform!” ae shouted out loud. He miserably patted down his wet uniform. A gust blew by, and he sneezed immediately after.

“How can I be so unlucky!!”

“I told you to not scream! Or else I’ll give you a beating!” Red Moon scolded harshly.

The young man felt helpless. He could only scan left and right. Luckily, no one had appeared to see this sorry sight, otherwise, he would’ve been very embarrassed.

“You can’t even withstand a small issue? Then wouldn’t you go crazy if you encounter that bunch of people?” Red Moon commented in a contemptuous manner.

“I’m just an ordinary guy, I have nothing to with any mech wars or whatever. That would be a job for the police,” the young man, Clint, wrung out some water from his clothes. He felt that he was having the worst luck today.

“Even if you were an ordinary person before, the moment you picked me up, you were no longer normal. Do you understand this?” Red Moon calmly spoke in a much warmer tone than usual.

“But the Blackboard City military is tremendously strong. There’s no need for us to worry about that group you mentioned,” Clint helplessly replied.

“You sure do enjoy relying on others, huh? Always deciding on letting others handle the troubles? Have you never thought of turning it all around and becoming someone others can rely upon?” Red Moon asked in return.

Clint fell silent. Although his core personality was weak, it didn’t mean that he couldn’t differentiate between good and bad. He desired to repay and take care of his sister, as well as finding his biological parents while helping his close friends.

“Did you forget about Darby?” his dream was to become a dashing mech pilot. Did you forget about Baylon? His dream was to no longer be a burden to his family and brother. And your sister, her biggest dream was for you to become truly independent, to become a mature man! Not someone who only knows to cower behind others’ protection, and shrink yourself away into your own pathetic shell the moment trouble arises.”

Red Moon had never properly lectured anyone before; this was his first time doing so.

Clint remained quiet. He was well aware of his family’s wishes and the dreams of his friends, and so he, too, had aspired to contribute to making them a reality. However, wanting to act and really starting to make them come true were two entirely different matters.

“Tell me, are you a selfish person?” Red Moon asked in a loud voice, “If your answer is yes, then I will just look for another compatible person, just so I won’t waste any more time on you. You should just live the rest of your life as a good-for-nothing coward.”

Clint lowered his head and continued to remain silent, took him awhile before he voiced out.

“But… but…”

“But what!?”

Sizzle!

Abruptly, an arc of blue electricity lit up on Clint’s body. After the crackling of a few electrical sparks, Clint knelt down on the ground as small wisps of smoke wafted from his body. His body then began twitching.

His pupils dilated and his eyes widened without blinking.

“This painful sensation stems from abdominal injuries,” Red Moon’s voice ringed in the boy’s ears. “Aren’t you scared of pain? Then allow me to have you get a feel for it.”

Sssss…!

After another wave of electric current sounds, Clint dropped down onto the floor. His body went through spasms, resembling an out-of-water shrimp.

“This is the sensation of mutilation, have a taste of it.”

Sssss…

“This is the pain of ruptured organs.”

“Aaarghh…” Clint uncontrollably drooled and it dripped onto his clothes and the ground. He wanted to close his mouth, but the agonizing pain going through his body had left his mind went blank and his body unresponsive.

Clack!!

“This is the pain of having your neck snapped,” Red Moon’s cold voice rang in the boy’s ears. “Had enough?”

Clint had no way of replying anymore. All he wanted to do was just lay down on the ground. Sweat poured out from all over his body, soaking his clothes and leaving a person-shaped wet spot on the ground.

He felt something lodged in his throat, preventing him from making any form of sound. He could only make unintelligible sounds.

“Can you feel it? These are the possible pains you can feel in war,” Red Moon laughed coldly, “Whatever you’re terrified of or have a fear of are all of these things. Can you feel it?”

Clint had no idea what went wrong with him. Once he’d truly experienced these pains, he suddenly stopped being afraid of them in his mind.

A feeling of “what I was afraid of was just that?” washed over him.

“How about now? Are you still scared!?” Red Moon continued to ask.

Clint felt surprised when all of the pain disappeared from his body like flowing water.

He straightened up his body, knelt, then quietly stood up from the ground. A feeling of rebirth washed over him.

“This was what you feared of all along, terrified of even,” Red Moon giggled. “Don’t you have the feeling of ‘that’s all there’s to it’?”

Clint wiped away the sweat and tears from his face and nodded slightly.

“A little…”

“Damn you, you idiot! Don’t you know how to fight back?” this was not what Red Moon expected to see, but instead, a rebellious spirit awakened by the torture the boy had received! A person without bloodlust would have no way of going against the various endeavors and enemies he would face in the future. He had intentionally tortured Clint, hopefully ridding him of his fears, and another goal was to hopefully trigger his rage and wrath, producing a will to fight back.

“I know you’re doing this for my sake, Master Red Moon,” Clint answered seriously.

“You imbecile!” Red Moon flared up in response. “Is your brain full of dog turds? You’re not even the least bit enraged at me torturing you? Can you even consider yourself a man? Dog turd! Idiot, imbecile! Buffoon!! …Forget it, I’m done with you. Today’s objective was partially achieved. Next time when you get into a fight or whatever and you feel these kinds of pain, surely you won’t be afraid of them anymore, right?”

“Ma…maybe…” Clint scratched his head, unsure of himself.

“The next time someone decides to bully you, punch him!” Red Moon replied straightforwardly.

“Why? I don’t like to fight,” Clint replied honestly.

“Forget it, forget it. Let’s no speak of it any further. Looking at you infuriates me!” Red Moon was irritated once more.

Under Red Moon’s guidance, Clint continued to tread along the river bay. Before he could walk far, he was already ordered to stop.

“Right here!” Red Moon shouted, “Pay attention, it’s right here. Stay back a little, be careful! I’m going to make my move!”

“Huh?” Clint carelessly didn’t react in time.

Suddenly, he saw a humongous shadow slowly rising from within the river. The shadow was about two to three meters in diameter and length, and rapidly rising from the bottom of the river.

Splash!!

Amidst torrential splashing, a black, metallic wreckage broke through the river surface. It hovered in the air and then soared directly towards Clint’s direction.

“Woah, woah…!” Clint couldn’t resist shouting out loud.

“Enough gawking!” Red Moon flared up, “Hurry and get out of the way, I need to put this thing down! I’m tired as hell!”

Clint then snapped back to his senses and hurriedly dodged to the right.

The giant metallic wreckage slowly descended from where it positioned itself. The wreckage was entirely pitch black, and a partially intact black disc logo still remained on its surface.

“What is this?” Clint walked over and encircled it for inspection.

“Blackboard manufactured mech wreckage.”

“Why are you bothering with this, master? What’s the use of a wrecked junk?”

“I did this for you, you imbecile!” Red Moon flared up once again.

“Oh…”

Red Moon’s voice had carried a note of fatigue.

“Alright, you should return home for today. That’s it for now. People normally wouldn’t bother taking this away once it’s dumped here. We’ll come back tomorrow.”

“Oh…”

“Fortunately, the Blackboard Region had no areas for selling salvage. Otherwise, this thing would’ve been lifted away to one for sure,” Red Moon seemed really tired. “Move on now, go back and rest. We need to accelerate progress, or else it will really be futile to fight back when that group comes along.”

“With Blackboard Academy around, they definitely won’t come. You can relax, master,” Clint attempted to comforted Red Moon.

“Don’t tell me to relax, you idiot!” Red Moon felt that this pig-like companion really deserved a beating. If there were two opponents, it might as well be a ‘one against three’ scenario!

No one was fully aware of how powerful that group was. Through the intel obtained from documents, he was quite aware of what they’re capable of.

Their ordinary pilots were all at the standard of level four willpower, the stronger ones being level five, and to reach that degree… Furthermore, their mechs seemed to be of the odd variant. He recalled the last sound phenomenon produced by the mechs.

“Great Light Mech… damn it all… If not for the fact that my mechanical body was utterly destroyed, you small fries wouldn’t even stand a chance against me!”

“What Great Light Mech?” Clint said in confusion.

“That is the opponent we’ll be facing soon. Be sure to remember this name.”

“Oh… relax, the Blackboard army is really impressive.”

“I want to beat you up again!” Looking at Clint’s face, Red Moon was infuriated once more.

Chapter 818: Advance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“At 4 am yesterday, the remains of a white mech were discovered in the South Plains area. According to investigations, it was probably a wandering mech that entered our borders without permission, and was therefore shot down by our pilots stationed there. Now, three of the militaries Black-Clothed Generals have already moved out, and are practicing military drills, while they completely eliminate threats and search through the area. Would unrelated personnel please evacuate the area as soon as possible…”

Garen stood in the bathroom, allowing the hot water to wash down his head, wiping the sweat stains off his body as he listened to the news being broadcasted in the living room.

The whooshing sound of water mingled with the sound of the news, and gave off a strangely peaceful feeling.

“Black-Clothed Generals?” His expression changed slightly. Others might not be so aware of it, but he had recently been using his hacker skills to search up information regarding pilots, so he was particularly sensitive towards these sorts of information.

“The Black-Clothed Generals are another name for the Academy’s Black Light Squad, in other words, it’s an umbrella term for the elite students. Some of the elite students are stationed outside, so they’re called the Black-Clothed Generals outside, they all have the military title of major general. Here are at least fifteen powerful pilots under the command of every Black-Clothed General, and these pilots are not your average pilots. To think they brought out three teams at once this time…”

Garen turned off the water, yanked down a dry towel hanging beside him, and covered his head with it, rubbing his hair dry.

Wiping the water off his body, he walked out of the bathroom and put on his clean underwear that was warmed in the dryer. Then, he walked straight into the living room and sat down in front of the computer.

“Did something happen again? How troublesome…”

He glanced at the images on the news nonchalantly, pressing Previous and Pause. The picture of the white-and-red mech remains was especially eye-catching.

Turning off the news, he picked up his Watch Terminal and looked at the time.

“It’s almost time.

Ding… ding…

There was the sound of the bell from the door.

“Please enter.”

Garen pressed a button on the computer, and the house door opened automatically, making a crisp smacking sound.

The door was pushed open, and a large, tall boy walked in. His skin was dark and his hair short, his aura giving off a sharp and stormy feeling.

“You are Nonosiva? I’m Mondo, from the second year. I’ll spare the long introductions, let’s get straight to business.”

“Sure,” Garen nodded and stood up. “Please sit, do you want some tea?”

“No. This is your proof of membership card, please keep it carefully.” The boy Mondo evidently had a decent impression of Garen, he did not seem to look down on Garen because of his family background at all. Instead, he spoke to Garen as though they were complete equals.

“Also, because of your excellent performance at the finals, the management team has decided to give you full Level Two support. As for what that entails, you can use the card to check the website, it’s stated there.

“Understood.” Garen accepted the silver-white card. There was a black V on it, and some delicate patterns like vines on the sides. It looked very intricate and extravagant.

“Also, if there’s anything urgent, you can call this number directly. He’s Lady Britney’s direct disciple, he can easily settle any normal problems, such as that kid you offended.” Mondo pressed around his Terminal, and sent Garen the contact of a third-year boy called Gurs.

Mondo gave Garen a friendly smile.

“Lady Britney really likes you, and she told us to take special care of you. Otherwise I wouldn’t be the one here today, it would be a regular worker instead.”

“Then I owe my thanks to Lady Britney,” Garen smiled as well, his Terminal moving slightly.

“As long as you understand,” said Mondo with a satisfied smile. Seeing the more than ten thousand units that had suddenly appeared on his watch, he was in an extremely good mood.

He patted Garen’s shoulder.

“If you have any problems from now on, you can come look for me. There’s no need to bother Lady Britney and Gurs with everything. As a senior, it’s expected of me take care of my juniors.”

“I won’t forget you, senior.” Garen nodded, in a good mood as well.

“I won’t forget such a generous and direct new member either!” Mondo had a very good impression of this Nonosiva.

The two of them quickly exchanged their contact methods, as a third-year student, Mondo had evidently started to dabble in society, so he was pretty familiar with haggling. The two of them exchanged their respective limits, so Garen knew what kind of problems he could go to Mondo with, and which problems he should not trouble him with.

99% of the members in Blue Narcissus were rich and powerful, but there was no such thing as too much money. And Mondo’s family was very strict, so he did not have much allowance. That was why he placed more emphasis on this money-making method, constantly telling Garen to come to him in case of trouble. His grandfather, who was in charge of the family, was a boss of the Blackboard Region army, and was also one of the academy’s lecturers, so it was easy for him to mobilize of the city’s defense corps. It was even possible for him to hire one of the elite students, the Black-Clothed Generals.

This was the part that really shocked Garen.

The title of Black-Clothed General was a military position that the elite students had to reach Level Five at least to obtain, and this inconspicuous boy in front of him could actually reach such a level. He had to appreciate the power of the members of Blue Narcissus here. It was no wonder that even though so many new students joined the academy every year, the number of Blue Narcissus members had always been maintained at several thousand members. This was more than one in a hundred, it was one in a thousand, or even ten thousand. Because many of the Blue Narcissus’ higher-ups were actually students who had graduated, and they had fifty- or sixty-year-olds in key positions as well. With a web of connections like that, they represented what was basically ultimate power.

After Mondo left, Garen closed the door, and arranged his connections in his heart.

“Now that Department Head Britney’s side is slightly more stable now, as long as it was not too troublesome, it would be easy for me to borrow some influence now. In that case, the Blue Narcissus’ Department Head Britney, Mondo, Gurs. On Celine’s side, there’s Vivienne, Wade. The Blue Narcissus has more influence on department checks, as well as the backgrounds and powers inside the Blackboard Region, they can also influence some small-scale military mobilizations. From the results of my investigations, I should be able to mobilize a team of about ten Level One pilots. In other words, my connections with the Blue Narcissus are mostly to help increase my actual power in the Blackboard Region.”

He balanced the weight of the favors he had bought with the money this time.

“And then there’s Celine and Vivienne, they mostly lean towards a wide reach of influence. Celine’s family business spans the different regions, so they can get news and intel quite easily, plus it’s easy for them to buy all sorts of supplies as well. They have a certain amount of influence in the other regions, and Vivienne’s family seems to be involved with the black market and high-interest loans as well, so I should be able to get some forbidden items as well. For example, high-level training methods that even the Blue Narcissus would not dare to sell out in the open… as well as hiring outside mercenary groups for jobs. They’re a lot more complicated than the Blue Narcissus’ side.”

He analyzed the meaning of each side’s relationship with him, and how to borrow power. Now, when he was at his weakest, it was key that he borrow power and influence so that he could develop quickly.

“But the foundation and core of all these connections is still my own strength and development.”

Garen released a breath. He was going to reach the peak of his training method very soon, the Blackboard training method could only reach Level One, and after that the academy would not provide any more higher-level training methods for free. At the most, they would only provide the right to train with higher-level training methods, after all most people were not allowed to obtain Level Three or above training methods without a certain background. But if he wanted to get the actual content, he would need to work for the school, or simply use money to buy it, or he could sign a contract to become a lifetime worker for the academy. Only then could he get the training method to continue training.

“Without a training method, no matter how much stronger the Peacock Technique makes me, I still wouldn’t know which direction to go. I need to find a training method that fits my Willpower ASAP.”

The Peacock Technique’s strengthening as it levels up was actually a forceful push as he advanced down the path with his training methods. If the path ahead was unclear, it would also naturally appropriate that power for some other uses, and not to strengthen his Willpower.

“I don’t know enough about Willpower right now, if I had enough information and intel, maybe I could try to invent a Willpower training method of my own, but unfortunately I need money and position to get a higher-level one.”

He brought out the website that led to a market selling training methods again.

Each training method was shockingly expensive, and they only sold a maximum of Level Three ones on the market. If you wanted anything higher, you needed a proof of identity. Unless you were from the military or a core member of some faction, you were not allowed to buy it, no matter how much money you offered.

Garen’s ambition went way further than Level Three, the way he saw it, many of these training methods were all just abridged versions, if he wanted to create his own complete version, it would take too much time and energy, so it was not worth it.

“Looks like I still need to settle with the connections from Vivienne and Celine. A slightly higher-level training method… can’t be cheap.” He looked at the prices on the site that started by the ten thousands, and these were just the Level Three ones. The higher level ones were not allowed to be sold, so their prices should be a lot more astronomical than these ones.

“Forget it, I’ll slowly accumulate money, and get a Level Three one first.”

He began to browse the site.

It was not quite the same as what he saw last time, and the prices had changed as well. Many of the training methods were different too, some had evidently sold many copies, so the prices were lower. Some were on a limited-time sale too, with signs indicating that it was recommended by the website, or endorsed by some XXX famous pilot, some XXX famous training method, the fastest training method, and so on.

Glancing through it, Garen set his gaze on four training methods.

‘Herculean Warhammer — increases the power of Will-powered mechs, the degree with which increases by level. At Level Three, the increase is at 200%. This training method has a special effect with regards to Willpower defense, it has very effective defense against Willpower techniques of Level Three and below… Each level is sold at 380000 Universal Units.’

‘Wind Words — increases the speed of Willpower control, allowing you to play with your opponents like the wind, and grasp victory in your hands easily. At Level Three, the mech’s speed will be increased by 35%. At the same time, it also speeds up Willpower manipulation to a certain extent. Suitable for speed-type pilots. Each level is sold at 400000 Universal Units.’

‘Galaxy Glow — training method that allows control of several mechs, allowing your Will to split up, and carefully control several units at once to attack. The number of splits depends on the level, Level One allows one split, Level Two allows two, Level Three allows three. Suitable for fortification-type pilots. Each level is sold at 260000 Universal Units.’

‘Sword of the Sun — training method that adds on an effect, it adds a layer of high heat to the mech’s fists, allowing it to burn and melt the enemy’s outer shell, thus increasing destructive power. At the same time it produced high radiation, and has a certain negative effect on the opponent. Suitable for close combat pilots, each level is sold at 190000 Universal Units. Be warned that this method is very hard to learn, please consider carefully.’

These four training methods were all top quality to Garen, they were very suitable for his fighting style. And most importantly, these four methods seemed to hide the potential to grow, as though they were the abridged versions of some high-level techniques. There was a chance they could be perfected later, and there were many other training methods that looked impressive or cheap, and seemed more worth it, but in truth there was no other chance to advance after that.

Chapter 819: Ripples 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So which training method should I use for now?”

Garen glanced at the four training methods in front of him, each had their own pros and cons.

“Since I was going the long-range shooter route before, then I might as well go for long-range.”

Eventually, he still decided to continue as a long-range shooter, this was a path he had never taken before. Perhaps this might lead to new discoveries in his martial arts away, because he had always specialized in close combat before.

After making his choice, he moved his cursor to Galaxy Glow, and pressed confirm to buy the first level.

Smack.

‘Ding-dong, you have successfully purchased Galaxy Glow, a note from the seller: this training method is slightly harder to level up, if you need a higher-level training method, please go to Thousand Star Region’s Thousand Star Academy for further study.’

Garen soon saw the ‘Download Complete’ notification on his Watch Terminal.

That was a yellow-covered book that looked like a traditional tome. It appeared on the screen of his Watch Terminal, and he pressed it lightly, flipping the pages inside. It was all covered in small and compact letters.

‘The Way of the Thousand Gods, begins with earnestness.’

The first line of the opening was a condensed sentence that seemed like Mandarin.

‘Every part of the human body had its own hidden consciousness, that is the instinctual will in the deepest recesses of the body. Fighting, eating, defending, attacking! Its most direct expression can be seen in the immune system and the natural reflexes. Any cell or tissue in the human body has its own independent and primal will, before they specialize and gather into the other organs, tissues, or cells, they are each the most primal living cell. And what we are trying to do, is to reactivate the instinctual will of these cells once more.’

“Interesting.” Garen glanced at it, and seemed to find this theory somewhat possible. So he continued reading.

‘The cell’s natural reflexes are to absorb, attack, defend, or escape, but all of these have a complete theme, and that is survival. The human body, and other living creatures, are made of countless such cells. Therefore, the most basic instinct at the core of the human body, the strongest instinct, is also survival. The desire to survive is the source of all motivation, it’s the basic reason why people fight, in order to live, in order to have better lives. Everything humans do is so that they can reach this aim. Because this is the collective will of countless cells, the deepest will at the very core of every cell in the human body.’

‘The Way of the Thousand Gods intends to activate this deepest level of consciousness, activating the cells in every part and allowing them to have their own battle instinct. Theoretically, according to the structure of the different cells, many of our prodigious predecessors have experimented and discovered that the most the human body can achieve is…’ And the remainder was wiped away, just plain white with nothing else. Evidently, the person who leaked it out did not want outsiders to see that.

Garen was growing more fascinated, this theory was rather deep, huh. It definitely was not something a mere Level Three training method could cover. He understood that this thing was definitely the abridged version of a higher-level training method, looks like this training method had some history behind its roots.

After the part that was obscured, there was just a tiny bit of the remaining training method left. It only had three levels and three grades. Two of the levels were empty, he could only see them once he bought them.

And now all he could see what the first grade, or the Level One training method. There were also many training videos, lectures, live battle demonstration, and practical applications attached.

Garen looked at it briefly.

He was already at the Advanced Basic Level, and he was this close to properly achieving Level One. When he reached that, he would no longer have to rely on the Moonfang to disguise himself. To him, this was something he had been looking forward to for a long time. He just needed to get through this period steadily.

He immediately practiced once according to the training method he had just obtained. As expected, a slightly higher-level training method was different, he could instantly feel that his rate of progress was unspeakably better than the previous Blackboard training method, where he could not feel anything at all.

If he continued at this pace, he would just need four or five months, and if all went well, he would have reached Level One. But even these four or five months were too long.

“Now I wait for the white Rainbow Stones.”

Garen looked at the light outside the window, it was especially bright at eight or nine o’clock.

“It’s been a while since I left the house, maybe I should go for a walk.”

There was something happening outside the academy, because he could hear a constant stream of soothing music, it seemed to be something like a dance tune.

Garen walked up to the window and opened it to look outside first. Through the cracks in the 槐树的, he could see a man-made grassy slope beside the alloy floor. There was a radio on the lawn, and they were having a friendly dance event out in the open, or rather, it was a friendly dance training session.

Some of the students were not very talented, and some did not try very hard either. They came to the academy to meet people and make connections, so there were countless such events.

The person organizing this open-air dance hall was an elegant man with long green hair, he wore the third years’ uniform, and stood beside the floor with a smile, holding a glass of jade-green wine as he chatted occasionally with the students around him.

There was a band playing softly in the middle of the dance floor, composed fully of good-looking men and women who would occasionally flirt with the other students.

Garen had also begun to understand the habits of the students here, as long as they fancied each other, the culture here did not really place much importance on virginity. If someone caught your eye, it was common to just rent a room at night and have a one-off thing. And it was very hard to determine if a woman was a virgin or not too, because it was too easy to fix that membrane. And thanks to their Willpower training, there were also many women who resembled young girls in terms of their bodies, looks, and aura, even if they had already slept with many men.

The training of Willpower had improved humanity’s genes, so there were more and more good-looking men and women. Even if they were not handsome or beautiful, they could make up for it with their presence, so it was not surprising that things were so open here.

He drew the curtains completely, opening the windows, and allowing air to enter the room.

Only then did Garen wash up, put on his clothes, and walk to the door.

Just as he had opened the door with a clack.

“Hey, Nonosiva, are you going to get breakfast?” Apparently, a girl had moved into the opposite dorm at some point. She looked cute and sweet, with shoulder-length curly light brown hair. She wore a small tight white skirt with a black pattern, it was very short, and nearly revealed the roots of her thighs. Her legs were very long and round, though, and she wore a thin black silk hose around them, which showed how much thought she put into them.

The girl smiled sweetly at Garen, and she was even holding a pale yellow straw hat in her hands, dotted with small white flowers.

“How do you know my name?” Garen was slightly surprised.

“Over there.” The girl pointed at the wall to Garen’s right with a smile.

Garen turned around to look, and saw his name and classroom hanging on the wall.

“Do you want to go together?” She winked at him. “I just moved here two days ago, do you mind showing me around?”

Garen looked at his watch, closed the training method book, and set up a password on it.

“You’re Lucianne-Kell?” He looked at the sign on her door. “Sure, I can show you around, come with me.”

“I just entered the school recently, so I’m not very familiar with the surroundings, I hope you’ll take care of me, Nono.” Kell was very friendly from the start, she did not seem scared of strangers at all.

“It’s very nice to meet you,” Garen smiled and nodded politely. “What about the person who was staying there before?”

“Left the school, they were advised to drop out because their results didn’t make the mark. What to do, we can’t relax for a moment, even if we’ve managed to enter the school.” Lucianne-Kell shrugged helplessly, holding her palms up, and then she turned her gaze. “I heard that Nono’s in second year now, and you’re one of the Academy’s few First Seats, could you help tutor me when you have time? I’m always kinda scared when it comes to controlling mechs… I never know what to do.”

“If I have time, I’ll consider.”

Garen smiled.

As the two of them continued walking, many people greeted Garen as though it was natural. Most of them were people he had met before but never spoken to, and now they were all acting familiar with him, waving and greeting him naturally.

“You’ve finally come out, it’s good for you to come out for a walk when you got time, y’know.” Two boys from his class met Garen and Kell, and smiled at them **ly(1).

“Yeah, it’s really boring to stay in the dorm all day too. I saw them having a ball outside, so I came out to admire it for a bit, and relax.” Garen was not very close to these boys, but at least he knew them a lot better than the others, so his smile was a lot more natural as well.

“I hear Mondo went to your place a few days back, is that for real?” one of the boys came up to him and asked quietly.

“Mondo?” Garen was taken by surprise, he had not thought it would be that guy’s influence.

“Yeah, Mondo is one of the military’s big heirs, he’s pretty powerful in the academy too, and he went to your place personally. Everyone’s talking about that now,” the boy said in a very small voice.

“It’s not much, just about me joining the Blue Narcissus. He just happened to be coming over to give me the membership card, it was on his way.” Garen knew that the fact that he had joined the Blue Narcissus would get out really soon. After all, the other Thousand Year Trees and Black Roses were not going to keep it a secret for him, and besides, it was not that big a deal.

“Blue Narcissus…!” But as soon as he said it, the two boys’ mouths turned O-shaped, and even the pupils of a girl who just happened to be passing by dilated.

As for Lucianne-Kell, who was beside him, her face gave a huge jolt.

The three of them instantly fell silent, they evidently needed time to digest the weight of that news.

Garen felt as though he had underestimated the importance of the Blue Narcissus organization, or rather, its position in the hearts of regular students.

“You mean that extremely mysterious Blue Narcissus, whose members are all heirs and heiresses?” the other boy could not help but ask.

“Is there a problem?” Garen asked in confusion.

“Throughout the whole school, do you have any idea how many people can join the Blue Narcissus every year? It’s less than five per grade! Oh my god!” the boy instantly lost it, looking at how calm Garen seemed, it was as though a stampede had run through his heart. This was such incredibly good news, and this guy did not act like it at all! He was wandering out here like it was nothing!

“Whatever, I’m gonna go get breakfast.”

Looking at the two boys wordlessly, Garen went past them by himself.

Lucianne-Kell stared for a moment, and then hurried to catch up.

Translator’s Notes:

No idea why this was censored?

Chapter 820: Ripples 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the way to the canteen, more and more people greeted Garen enthusiastically, and most of them were people he had seen just once, yet they were greeting him automatically like they were the best of friends. Most of these came from families that were not particularly well-off, but not too bad either. In fact, the students with really bad backgrounds did not approach him at all.

When he reached the canteen, he grabbed some food and drink before sitting down. Lucianne-Kell sat down opposite Garen of her own initiative, and within half a minute, some students approached them, greeted Garen, and sat down beside him.

This situation was exactly the same as when those heirs and heiresses showed up. Some of the students sat down as though in awe of the great weather, and then began to talk among themselves. They would occasionally pull Garen into the topic, teasing him. These conversations looked very natural, but in truth all of them were instinctively observing Garen’s reactions.

Before he knew it, there were five or six other students sitting around him with Garen in the center, and they had formed a small social circle. This also allowed them to subtly block off the other students who wanted to approach him, so several students who had arrived late left quietly and rather regrettably.

Inwardly, Garen understood the reason.

He had demonstrated his potential, and then joined a powerful group such as the Blue Narcissus. Plus there were rumors that he was connected to Mondo, so of course his future was full of potential. He would definitely become a Field Level Officer or even Major General. To the normal students around him, someone like him should be approached before he fully developed, that was the best time to try and get in his good books.

Most of the students believed that opportunity came to those who knocked on its door, if you did nothing at all for yourself, even the biggest opportunity would eventually come to nothing. Sometimes you had to be slightly more shameless, and then maybe you would obtain a chance that others would need to work for years to reach.

These people truly chased after power, going where the tide did. They were shameless enough to be nothing more than grass by the wall, you could give them some small jobs, but Garen knew that they would be the first to run if anything serious happened.

Still, he could not act too independent in the academy, plus many of these people were also good-looking young men and women. At the very least they were eye candy, so Garen just let them be.

He sat in his seat and ate his mushroom braised chicken at his own pace. The way Garen ate was very strange, he would dip his bread and buns into the chicken soup and eat them like that. He would usually finish one fist-sized bun in three bites, and he never stopped. Within ten minutes, he had stuffed three peoples’ worth of food into his stomach.

After that, he picked up the napkin and wiped his mouth elegantly. When he was reincarnated into the Totem World, the combination of his lifelong aristocracy training and huge appetite gave him some strange eating habits. It looked very classical and gentle, but he ate a terrifying amount.

By the time the people around him noticed something amiss, they saw that nothing was left of the pile of things on the table in front of Garen.

“Did you always eat so much, Nono? No wonder you’re so good at Mech battles!” Kell, who was sitting opposite, was evidently there to purposely get closer to Garen, and now she asked in a small, tender voice.

“It’s not that much,” Garen replied calmly. He held up his watch to check the time. “It’s getting late, I plan to attend Professor Ser’s class on interference.”

“I’ll go too, I’ve nothing else to do anyway,” Kell said, taking the initiative.

“Me too! You don’t mind, do you, Nono?” The one who spoke was a pretty girl from Nonosiva’s class, her results were completely average, and her Willpower was only at Middle Basic Level as well, but her looks and her figure were very decent. She had a proper Eastern girl’s features, her black hair tied up, her skin fair and smooth. Her large eyes were black and bright, with the textbook almond-shaped eyes and cherry lips. She gave off an impression of a jade-white china doll, and when she sat quietly, she had the aura of a young girl in the spring of youth.

The girl was called Vera, she looked pure and innocent, but she was a well-known bootlicker in the class. Apparently, she was often seen going in and out of entertainment with the rich boys.

“If you won’t find it boring, sure.” Garen smiled and stood.

As soon as he got up, he saw Mina and Aier sitting not far away. Both of them looked at him slightly worriedly, and just happened to meet his gaze.

“If you’re here, why didn’t you come say hi?” Garen walked up to them, smiling. Only friends in need were friends indeed. He split the crowd, and walked straight up to them.

“Well, we saw you were surrounded by so many people, including some pretty girls, so we didn’t want to disturb you.” Mina was slightly unhappy, but seeing that Nono still greeted them the same way he always did, she heaved a sigh of relief inwardly.

“Isn’t that Aier? You guys are here too, sorry I didn’t notice you just now,” Vera said with a smile, walking out from beside Garen. She knew Aier, the little boy who had once written her love letters. He was very pure and innocent, but she had not thought that he would be this close to Nono, so that was a possible breakthrough.

“Vera…” Aier saw Vera standing next to Garen, and dejection flashed across his eyes. He had always had a crush on Vera.

Garen was lazy to bother with these soap dramas, the class was going to start soon. He had nothing to do anyway, studying more would never go wrong. The classes in the academy were all free to join, if you wanted to attend then go, as long as you pass the final test, nobody really cared how you studied anyway.

After becoming famous, a situation like this would also be very normal. There were many people who wanted to approach the powerful, and some students with good connections would surely also have found out that he was praised by the Blue Narcissus’ Britney. That was why this was happening.

After chatting with Aier and Mina for some time, Garen was practically pushed by the group into the students’ lecture area.

Kell and Vera had completely taken over the positions on his left and right. Garen did not really care right now anyway, this way he was no different from the other rich and powerful heirs, so he could use that to disguise himself.

The days passed by.

Soon, the second batch of white Rainbow Stones would be arriving as well, and the teaching time he agreed on with Celine was fast approaching as well.

Garen made some slight preparations, and then he went with Perry, the representative from Blue Narcissus, as well as Celine’s representative, Wade, to receive the cargo. This was the first time, so all three sides needed to familiarize themselves with the process. The car sending the cargo was a normal cargo vehicle from Celine’s family. There were five hundred pieces in this first batch, they were the first primary materials.

Garen used the several tens of thousands of units he had left after buying the training method to rent a small factory for distillation for a month. There was a fully automated production line to increase the purity of the flammable powders, to achieve the market’s minimal requirements.

But this was all beside the point, the main reason for his helplessness was how, after absorbing all of the more than five hundred White Rainbow Stones in this batch, he still showed no signs of leveling up. The progress of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s fourth grade rose from 11% to 78%, and it did not go any further than that. Evidently, that little bit was no longer enough for it to use up, and he needed more.

On the other hand, the high-energy fuel powder created from these five hundred or more stones was enough to fill twenty or thirty bottles. He had invested 1500 units, and 500 more units went to safe transport of the materials, so his main cost was 2000 units. In return, he obtained 25 bottles of powder, each 25kg in weight. Each kilogram cost ten thousand units at the very least. So his final profit would be about 2.5 million, and considering the split in profits, Garen would obtain 40% for himself, so that would be a million units.

Looking at the number of Universal Units in his watch, Garen finally relaxed as well.

He still owed Instructor Hamm more than a million in surgical fees, so now he finally felt like there was some hope for him to return it all. He would also need a lot of money for the training methods after this, but he needed to be wary of the speed and regularity every month.

Earning money too fast was not a good thing, it would be easy to invite the greed and envy of others.

Garen tried his best to control the speed with which he produced the powder, partly because he was afraid of attracting attention, but also because he wanted to control the demands of the market. As soon he tossed out the refined powders, there were already military factories and research centers taking them, they practically fought for it. This situation made Garen secretly glad that his plan was correct, if he had not first connected with the two powers and had them cover for him, then those waves of commercial spies would already be enough for him to lose big. Just looking at how thirsty those buying powers seemed to be, no one would believe him if he said he did not have any forces suppressing them.

He set his pace at buying five hundred pieces twice a month, it was not too much, and this way he would earn about 5 million each time. 10% of that was 500 thousand units. Celine was not interested in 100 thousand or so, but he had to perk up and pay attention if it was 500 thousand. If he was already like that, as someone from a family of merchants, Vivienne and Wade would be even more so. 500 thousand units in profits every month got their hearts palpitating slightly, then they would think about the 40% Nonosiva had, and both would feel even weaker.

In June, as their first time cooperating, Garen had a total profit of five million. Taking away the change, he paid 20% or one fifth in taxes. Of the remaining four million, he took 40% in profits, and ended up with 1.6 million more units in his account.

He used most of this 1.6 million to pay back his debt to Instructor Hamm, and then he used the remaining 200 thousand or so to pay for the factory’s rental and overhead, and he also gave some away as salaries for the people who had safely navigated the purchase and delivery of the White Rainbow Stones. He gave Kendall ten thousand as a bonus so he could send it back to his family, and then he gathered up the remaining hundred thousand units into a whole number.

These hundred thousand units were his true modal for him to set his foundations.

At the same time, as Nonosiva, he had officially entered the second year of university, becoming a second-year student at the academy.

As for his Willpower, as long as he could absorb the White Peacock Stone again next month, he should be able to reach the fourth grade. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s basics were divided into five grades, the first five grades were just setting the foundations. There were three more grades after that, and that was where its power could really be displayed. Garen had already vaguely noticed that the Peacock Technique was not very beneficial to his body in itself, it mainly increased his special abilities. This also made him look forward to the upcoming fourth grade, because that was a fundamental shift. Once he reached it, his Willpower would be forced to increase, and he would then properly be in Level One, so he would no longer have to rely on the Moonfang. He could be a mech pilot all on his own.

And just then, ripples finally began to spread through the Blackboard Region as well. Some rumors about the White Light terrorist organization began to spread through the region, apparently the White Light Organization’s Great Light Mech had already entered the Blackboard Region, breaking past the defense army and Black-Clothed General’s barricades.

So the three large states, more than ten provinces, several dozen cities of different sizes, as well as the several hundred villages and towns in the Blackboard Region all began to up their security at the same time. Thankfully, they did not overdo it, they just activated many more surveillance cameras and increased the number of mechs on patrol. Normal people would just find security slightly tighter, only the professionals could sense the subtle undercurrent of chaos in the Blackfield Region.

Nobody knew that the Black-Clothed General had actually already completely lost track of the White Light Mech, and it was already hidden somewhere in the Blackboard Region.

Chapter 821: Fair 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Evening, in the second largest town in the Blackboard Region, Nocto City

The many tall buildings were like pencil blades stuck into the ground, straight as an arrow. The buildings would occasionally sparkle with white or green, yellow lights, and there was the vaguely of music as well.

Between the buildings, there were many suspended bridges connecting them, and these flowed with a constant stream of levitating cars. The car lights were like a river of neon lights, from afar, it looked like a sparkling string of pearls.

A row of wild geese lined up in a row neatly, slowly flying through the gap between buildings. Crossing over the bridges, flying over the cars, they flew slowly over a few patrolling white mechs.

Whoosh.

A humanoid white mech raised its head and glanced at the geese.

“What is it? Cady,” another mech beside it asked.

“Nothing. I just saw some wild geese, and that always reminds me of the situation back home. I wonder what it’s like back there now,” the white mech replied softly.

“Go see it if you have time, after all, once this martial law period is over, the higher-ups have said we get a week off,” his companion said with a laugh.

“True, I do plan to go back for real this time,” the white mech laughed as well.

Whoosh!

Suddenly a spot of white light flew across the sky above the city.

“What’s that?” The two of them looked up and noticed the white light.

“Don’t know, a signal glare?”

“Scan it.”

“It seems to be a firework that was reflected back.”

“A firework? Is it one of those new types? It’s so bright.”

“Forget it, let’s keep walking, once we complete our mission today we can go back and have a feast.”

The two mechs slowly continued to fly towards their determined destination.

Meanwhile, the white dot landed in a very normal pitch-black alley somewhere in the city.

The white light floated in the air lightly for a while, and then it landed onto the ground slowly. With a whoosh, the air twisted and turned transparent, then somehow a whole man’s body began to appear above the white dot.

He wore a white skin-tight suit, and there was a red line of light that kept flowing on his body, from his head down his back, blinking and twinkling continuously.

“I have arrived safely,” he smiled, the corners of his lips curving. Glancing around his surroundings, he found that the alley was completely void of people, and there was only a stray dog sprawled on top of some rubbish cans.

“Is everything okay? Ace,” a woman’s icy-cold voice came from the man’s collar.

“No problem, everything’s going swell. This degree of security is no threat at all, their scanning is too lame!” the man replied relaxedly. Unzipping the skin-tight suit he wore, he revealed a T-shirt and black leather pants. He pressed the suit lightly, and it instantly and automatically shrunk, turning into an ornate thick silver belt. Wearing it casually around his waist, the man instantly became a normal young person living in the city. He gave off a fashionable and wild feeling.

“I have to say, these clothes are pretty good, Six Flowers.”

“Thank you for the praise. That is an affirmation of my taste,” the icy lady replied. “I graduated from fashion design, after all.”

“Now that’s a surprise.” The man smoothened his hair, spiking up all of his short deep blue hair, so that it looked like a burning blaze reaching upwards. He also completely revealed his face, so handsome it was slightly devilish.

“Alright, I’d better explore this place properly, it looks like this Blackboard Region is doing pretty well for itself.”

“I hope you have fun, sir, but please don’t forget your mission.”

“Of course.”

“We will handle the search for the Black-Clothed General, please don’t worry about that.”

Turning off his communicator, the blue-haired man chuckled and strode out of the alley. As he passed, that sprawled stray dog suddenly had a fit, and fell down sideways, its whole body shaking. Blood flowed out of its eyes, and with two popping sounds, the wild dog’s eyeballs exploded.

“The optical nerves will also retain some information…” the man murmured, as he quickly melded into the crowd down the street.

**********************

The Blackboard Academy, in a large lecture room

A white-haired lecturer in a black suit was talking his tongue off in the front, never once stopping. Most of the several hundred students at the bottom were seriously writing notes, while others were simply recording video and audio.

Only the lecturer’s voice echoed through the classroom.

The seventy-eight-year-old lecturer, Andre was one of the few people in the Academy who fully supported the Deadlight Cannon Crossfire Web, he believed that once the Deadlight Cannon Fire crossed enough times, and was concentrated enough, then even the strongest close combat mech would be helpless when fighting in a small area.

“As for the claims that close combat mechs will be countered by the large battleships, right now, close combat mechs are countered by the large battleships, whereas large battleships are countered by long-range shooting mechs. And long-range mechs are countered by close combat mechs. They are all interconnected, this is the fixed rule that we concluded from many wars.”

In a corner of the classroom.

Garen held his notebook and was very seriously doing his notes. Somehow a bunch of rich and powerful heirs had gathered around as though it was natural, quite a few of them had decent backgrounds, and were top of the grade as well. They were all sitting next to him, some were taking notes and listening to class properly, and some were talking and joking with the only girl in the group.

The rumors about Britney’s praise of Garen had finally completely come out. As the person who held the true power in Blue Narcissus, Britney was already the Head of the academy’s Logistics Department, and she was also in charge of Blue Narcissus’ finances. The power of her family was terrifying, and although she had never met Garen officially, she was already very obviously on his side.

Vera and Kell also sat beside Garen, both of them looking very close to and reliant on him. They could also feel the contemptuous and jealous gazes from around them, so they felt slightly cocky. After all, the early bird caught the worm.

“Nono, that guy’s here too?” a boy beside Vera, called Monty, said suddenly.

“What?” Garen paused slightly, and looked at him for a moment before following his gaze to find a somewhat familiar figure.

Short blue hair, earrings, a tall figure. That boy was currently noting something down, his head lowered.

“It’s the young brother of that Cor who put you in the hospital last time. Last time he brought people over and wanted to teach you a lesson, remember that?” chuckled Monty.

“That incident, huh…” Garen frowned.

“It was not just that, this guy came looking for trouble during the finals as well, trying to trip you up. I heard that he spread the rumor saying that your weakness was your Willpower wasn’t strong enough,” said Monty with a cold laugh. He was Mondo’s younger brother, and his older brother had specifically told him to approach Nonosiva, so this was the best opportunity to show up. Others were afraid of those siblings, but Monty’s family was not intimidated by Cor and Caus. Even if they had the Thousand Year Tree and Black Rose behind them, he had the Blue Narcissus behind him too, so he was not scared of their background. Besides, they were more than a level beneath him in the organization, why would there be anyone willing to cross him for their sake.

“What do you want me to do? We’re bros, so just say the word and I’ll get them on it.”

Garen spun the pen in his fingers.

“It’s all in the past, this way the grudges will never end, so just forget it.”

“You sure are generous,” said Monty with a laugh.

“Nono was never a calculative person,” Vera said softly, as though she was part of the family.

“Fine, fine, fine.” Monty threw two boys a glance, and the two boys sitting behind Garen stood up with a smile, walking out of the classroom. One of the larger guys was working his fists, making loud cracking sounds.

Garen sensed it, but he pretended not to, and he lowered his head and continued to write notes.

Monty laughed.

“I’m going to the loo.”

“Mm-hmm.”

Bam!!!

In a dark corner of the corridor outside, a red-haired boy was hit by a ferocious knee jab, crashing into the wall as blood leaked out the corner of his mouth. His whole face was white, and he was in so much pain he could not even straighten up.

The two large boys pulled him up hard.

“Isn’t he a tough guy, that Caus? He dares to play tricks on my friend, hehe… I wanna see if he would dare to leave the room for his friend.”

Monty crossed his arms over his chest, leaning at the exit and he stared at the red-haired boy, laughing coldly.

“You’re one of Cor’s best friends, and you’re pretty close to Caus too recently. I’ve informed that guy, let’s see if he dares to show his face.”

“Monty… We never provoked you!” said the red-haired boy, his voice muffled.

“You provoked me, alright.” Monty spat on the ground and rubbed it with his foot. “Caus still hasn’t come out? It’s only a dozen seconds by foot from the class, looks like he’s forsaken you and ran off on his own.”

“What are you trying to do? This has nothing to do with me…” The red-haired boy’s heart was growing cold, he knew that these people were so domineering in their grade that even the lecturers could not control them. Their backgrounds were so powerful that no one would say anything even if they permanently disfigured a student or two. To them, it was just a matter of money.

“You’re looking for me, right?” Caus suddenly walked out from a corner and stood behind Monty. Looking at the red-haired student’s blood-covered face, his expression darkened. “Monty, what on earth are you trying to do?”

“Yo, yo… If it isn’t Caus, our newly promoted elite student? That won’t do~~ Elite students are impressive, what are we normal students to do from now on? Master Caus is a future star… Smack!!”

There was suddenly a loud and crisp sound.

Everyone was frozen, no one had thought that Monty would suddenly lash out without warning. Monty was also an expert in fighting, especially in close combat. For him to lash out suddenly, even Caus could not react in time.

He slapped Caus straight in the face, and laughed brutally.

“How is it? Mr. Elite? Fight me?”

Smack!

There was another slap, and the other side of Caus’ face began to swell.

“Why aren’t you fighting back? Aren’t you the inner school’s powerful elite student, why aren’t you resisting?” Monty said eerily. “What do you mean by not fighting back?”

Smack!

Smack! Smack! Smack! …

The slaps landed on Caus’ face one after the other. He continued to stand there quietly, not making a move to fight back, but his previously handsome face was already completed swollen.

In the classroom, Garen raised his watch, and looked at the video sent to it. Seeing that Caus had no intention of fighting back, he remained expressionless, turning off the connection, and continued to listen to the class.

Chapter 822: Fair 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In some pale yellow plains on the outskirts of Nocto

Three black mechs landed slowly on the wild plains, covered with wilted wild grass.

“According to our sources, the signal first showed up around here,” the first black mech with bull horns on its head spoke first.

“With the intel department’s outdated techniques? I bet they were played with again,” another mech, this one holding a huge scythe, said grumpily. “Do you have any real info or not, Matthew? Running around like this all day is tiring too.”

“That depends on Allie.” Matthew sat in his mech, looking as gentlemanly as ever. ” Boris, how did you feel about that mech you finished off last time?”

“How did I feel?” The mech with the giant scythe paused. “Should be Level Five Willpower, I might not be able to finish ’em off myself. But with Allie’s interference, and your long-range shooting, it was still very easy. One hit K.O.! Hehe!”

“According to the latest intel, that guy was just someone who had fell behind the pack, you better pray that we don’t meet the main team before that big sister arrives here,” Matthew said helplessly. “Level Five, huh… I wonder how long it’ll take for me to get in there.”

“We’re still young, what are you so worried about?” Boris tsked. “As long as we get into Level Five, we get to become Black-Clothed Generals, and then we can enjoy a life of luxury, hehe…”

“Someone’s coming! Watch out!” Allie, who had been the only one keeping silent, spoke suddenly.

“Which direction?”

“North-east, the actual location is unknown, it’s coming fast, very fast!” Allie said hurriedly, and then she suddenly jumped back, retreating. “Standard dodge!”

The three mechs were like birds caught by surprise, they instantly bounced more than ten meters away.

Boom!!!

A white meteor crashed in the distance. The meteor showed itself, and it was actually a huge white-and-red mech, crouching in the middle of the deep crater in the ground, sharp thorns forming a shell like that of a tortoise on its back.

“Go! Kill him!” Matthew yelled abruptly, turning around and running.

Boris and Allie split up suddenly, the two of them dashing at the white-and-red fiercely.

“Dammit! I fricking found the big fishes as soon as I landed!” the white-and-red mech cursed, splaying open both of his palms and revealing the pitch-black cannon barrels on them.

Hah!

Intense electricity spewed out of the cannons.

Without them noticing, a large group of countless white mechs had rapidly appeared in the distant sky, all of them marked with the logo of the Blackboard Region, and then they began to fly towards the area of the conflict.

*********************

“Oh… oh… Just like that! Just like that!! Oh~~~~!! It’s coming out!!”

Clint Beza looked on speechlessly as a large piece of metal shrapnel flew out of the river in front of him, landing slowly beside the riverbank. All he could hear was Red Moon’s disgusting shouting.

“It’s so wonderful, how many years has it been? How many years have I not felt what it’s like to have a body… Tsk-tsk,” Red Moon’s voice was full of joy. “This alloy sure is good, I never thought we could find such wonder alloy material in this trash region, looks like it’s not good for nothing after all.”

“Are you happy, Master?” Clint watched as the metal corpses piled up behind him.

“Sure I am, after fishing for more than ten days, I only managed to gather these few things, guess I gotta be happy for now,” Red Moon replied quickly. “Hurry up, hurry up, don’t dally around, you gotta get ready to combine this!”

“Put it together? You want me to put it together?!” Clint’s mouth fell open. “How am I going to combine it? I have no idea!”

“What are you afraid of, I’m right here!” Red Moon said with disdain. “Combine them and then we can go look for more resources!”

“But how do I do that!” Clint was finally at the end of his rope, grabbing his hair hard.

“You still don’t feel it?” Red Moon’s voice took a rare, serious turn.

“What?”

“Your body, your body’s hidden Willpower, it’s finally been activated.”

“Hah?” Clint did not understand, “Willpower? Since when did I have Willpower?”

“You idiot! If you didn’t have Willpower, how would you be able to carry out so many things?!” Red Moon howled, as though wishing he would grow up. “Your Willpower’s attribute is moving material things! Idiot!”

“Hah?”

“Hah, your ass!! Now get moving!” Red Moon was utterly incensed.

“But this is so big… Could I go back and get someone to help…” Clint scratched his hair in frustration, saying in a small voice.

“Go and move it! The heck ’bout getting anyone else!” Red Moon was even more pissed now, “You got me, the universe’s number one Forbidden Mech core, helping you, so what the hell are scared of! Get moving!”

Clint was completely helpless, if he did not go help, he would surely be electrocuted again. He was sick and tired of that seizure-like feeling, so he had to go up obediently, and look for the lightest piece to carry.

Aiming for the black shard the size of a face basin, he rubbed his hands and went up to grab the edges, pulling it up fiercely.

Whoosh!

The shard was surprisingly light.

“Eh?” Clint was stunned, weighing the metal shard in his hand. “It’s so light…”

“Light, my ass! It’s because you got stronger!” Red Moon continued to scold him. “Do you fricking think that I’ve been electrocuting you and wasting my energy all this time? Grow some wits, won’t you!” Now that they were closer, this guy’s real personality was completely revealed. At first he still pretended slightly, but now that he was sure of Clint’s weak personality, he could not even be bothered to pretend anymore.

“But why would Willpower be like this?” Clint may be dumb, but that did not mean he had no general knowledge at all. Willpower would not be this strong as soon as it was activated. “Shouldn’t Willpower be very weak in the beginning, and it can’t be used on material things and people, right?”

“Do I look normal to you? Let me tell you, I’m so great that even my piss smells good, what’s more the secret techniques I taught you!” Red Moon was slightly full of himself now.

“If it was just normal middle- or low-level Willpower activation, it might end up like what you said, but if I’m the one doing things, do you really think it would be that sort of garbage?” he chuckled. “The Nine Mega Cannon training method trains up Willpower to match my electric healing, so the effect is really impressive! Tripling your strength is a small matter!”

“If your talent wasn’t so trashy, if you could learn my Milky Way Extinction, I guarantee you could become Superman in a second!” Sensing the shock on Clint’s expression, Red Moon got even cockier.

“So cool….!”

“Of course, who do you think I am? Back then, all on my own I swept through… Uh, let’s forget about that, hurry up and combine them! This is the combination blueprint! Remember it closely!” Red Moon changed the topic, and sent him a blueprint straight through his brain.

“In accordance with your wishes, you can choose your support members, so the first one you decided on is Darby, and the last one is Baylon?”

“Yeah,” Clint nodded solemnly. “I’ll ask him last.”

“Why the heck woulda ask!”

But this time, Clint actually decided to ignore Red Moon for once. Seeing how quickly and resolutely he turned on his Watch Terminal, Red Moon also did not scold him for once.

Soon enough, the call to Baylon went through, and on the opposite side, Baylon’s handsome smiling face appeared on the screen.

“Where’d you go, Clint? It’s really busy in the shop, how could you not come help?”

“Lon. There’s something I want to ask you.” The more time Clint spent with Red Moon, the more mysterious and complicated he felt to Clint. He did not know if it was right for him to bring Lon into this either, but he had a feeling that once he went down this road, perhaps he really might not be able to turn back later.”

“What’s the matter? Tell me.” Seeing Clint look so serious, the smile on Baylon’s face froze slightly as well.

“If you have a chance so that you could become a true pilot, and drive your ideal mech into battle, but in return you need to face many dangerous and troublesome things, would you choose to take that chance?” asked Clint carefully, choosing his words with caution.

“I would!” Lon paused for a moment, and then replied with determination. He lowered his head, but from behind his hair, his eyes shone with the light of desire for his dreams. “I want to catch up to my brother… I… Becoming a pilot… has always been my biggest dream. Isn’t it natural to face danger in battle?” His voice weakened, but his eyes grew brighter. “But this is all just a hypothesis, alright, forget it and come back to help. Owner’s getting angry,” he laughed again.

“I understand.” Clint severed the connection suddenly. “I’ve decided, the last person is Lon.”

“You sure?”

“Positive!”

“Although that guy’s no good, he’s much more talented than you, hmm… The confirmation imprint I gave him includes the Bright King Jisaiya’s training method. Since you’re positive, I’ll activate it now, got it!?” Red Moon asked again.

“What do you mean by activating the imprint?”

“That means I’ll send the training method into his mind, and at the same time I need to activate his body’s potential using the electricity I gave him last time, so his Willpower will reach Level One. That’s the thing you guys call Level One Willpower,” Red Moon explained.

“We can reach Level One that easily?” Clint was completely dazed. “Then what about me?”

“You’re already Level One.” Red Moon was at a loss for words. “Of course, without my activation, if you had gotten a normal training method, you could be training for several dozens of years before you could enter Level One.”

“But I’ll warn you in advance, that kid Baylon? Something’s odd about his body, so there might be some strange changes after his imprint is activated, you better be mentally prepared for that.”

“What changes?”

“I don’t know for sure either. After this, you had still better continue practicing the training method properly every day, just like I taught you before. Find some heavy things and carry them around, that training method is the one with the lowest requirements for talent, all you need to do is work hard. If all goes well, you can definitely reach seven or eight levels.”

“Got it… It’s just… isn’t this unfair to those people who had to train so many years just to reach Level One Willpower…” Clint said as scratched his head.

“Unfair?” Of course they’re different from you,” Red Moon explained, his tone turning gentler. Your Willpower was upgraded and activated with the help of my imprint, unlike them, your Willpower has one large flaw.”

“Flaw? What flaw?” Clint was starting to get worried.

“Half of your Willpower comes from you guys, and the other half belongs to me, so when you use it, if I don’t agree, you won’t be able to control your mech as freely as they can. Also, after leaving the mech, your Willpower will be halved. In other words, no matter what you do, you must make sure your opponents don’t find out who you are. If they catch you when you don’t have your mech, your Willpower will only be half of what it usually is, and the result, hehe, you know what will happen.”

“Is that it? I can deal with that, is there any way to savage it?”

“No, you should be glad you have Willpower at all, now go do your work.”

“Okay…”

Seeing Clint start to carry and transport the shards obediently, Red Moon pressed the activation switch for an imprint in his own core. That was the switch to the imprint hidden in Lon’s body beforehand.

In an instant, a few invisible signals crossed a large distance and landed in Lon’s body, just as he was busying about in the bakery so far away.

Lon placed the plate on the table, turned around and walked towards the counter. Suddenly, his whole body stiffened abruptly, and in an instant, he froze on the spot, not moving at all, as a mysterious numbing feeling spread from somewhere inside his body. He vaguely felt as though there was something new in his brain, something that looked very complicated and very high-class.

Chapter 823: Training 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

Caus crashed against the wall violently. His nose was bruised and his face was swollen while his body was covered in dirt from the floor. He pushed himself up off the ground and looked at Monty and the others, who were sneering at him coldly.

“How is it? Does it feel good?” Monty stepped forward and pinched his cheek.

“Frankly, I’ve been annoyed at you for a long time. First Seat of the first grade, you’re truly something.”

“Are you done?” Caus lowered his head and spat out blood and saliva while his face remained expressionless.

When Monty noticed Caus’ persistent cold gaze, his heart trembled slightly for unknown reasons. “Still holding up?”

He furiously kicked his foot outwards again.

Bang!

The pointed end of his shoe struck Caus’ lower abdomen and caused him to bend over even further. The pain forced him to curl up like a dried shrimp before he fell onto the ground sideways.

Caus remained silent and held his head quietly without even sighing. His behavior made Monty feel extremely uncomfortable. Meanwhile, the red-haired male student who stood on the side had become dazed long ago after witnessing everything, as he’d never expected Monty to act so harshly.

“That’s enough, Monty. This is pretty extreme,” suddenly, the voice of a young man echoed from the corner.

Monty turned around and looked before noticing a tall but otherwise normal looking male student standing in the doorway suddenly. This fellow had tanned skin and looked extremely simple and plain. Furthermore, there were no prominent features on his square face. However, he gave off a composed and resolute air when he spoke.

“Hey~ It’s Nicholas, the Elite Student,” said Monty cynically.

“Show me some respect,” Nicholas calmly glanced at Caus who was still lying on the ground.

“Show you some respect?” Monty sneered but did not refuse him immediately. Although he did not fear Nicholas, he was still wondering whether it would be worth offending a strong individual with a good future just for Nonosiva’s sake. Therefore, he was merely judging if his actions were worth the repercussions.

After hesitating for a moment.

“Alright, this matter ends here because of my respect for you,” he waved his hand so that his other friends would release Caus and the red-haired male student.

“Many thanks,” in reality, Nicholas had been somewhat anxious earlier. Monty had a lot of support from the other Elite Students who were also advanced, highly-skilled Mech Pilots. Therefore, he was usually arrogant. Nicholas had never expected that Monty would actually respect him. Clearly, the person who was receiving his blows earlier was not very significant.

He walked over and helped Caus. Once he saw Monty and his group of people leaving slowly, Nicholas could finally feel his heart relaxing slightly.

Inside the classroom

Garen lifted his watch and observed the situation above him while remaining expressionless. However, Vera and Kell, who were beside him, were somewhat displeased.

“You’re just going to let him off lightly? Aren’t you making it too convenient for him?” Vera could not help but say.

“It’s no big deal, just pay attention in class,” Garen did not express it openly, but the animosity between Caus and himself had been settled completely at this moment. However, this was probably Monty’s main goal, forcing him to rely on the other party’s background strength even more.

This matter was settled just like that. After a full day of class, Garen did not see Caus return to the classroom either.

When he returned to the dorm, another student who was walking with him informed him that Caus had been taken away by his older brother. There was nothing else after that, as his older brother Cor did not express anything. It was clear that he merely planned to endure everything.

The stormy winds calmed down.

Garen’s life became a series of daily routines. He would spend a few hours practicing his Training Methods daily before spending some time with Monty, Vera, and the others, especially Vera and Kell. Due to their personal conditions, both of them came into contact with more people and had a wider source of information. Furthermore, their figurative short-sightedness made them a suitable and definite source for Garen to receive information. Meanwhile, Monty and the others seemed rough but were actually more pessimistic individuals who were unsuitable for intimate friendships. Most of the time, their information was not timely either. However, Garen continued to maintain good ties with Monty. Of course, these people were not useless either. With the help of Monty and the others, Garen was gradually able to become one of the main tyrants in his grade that no one dared to mess with, despite not having this intention at all.

The second-grade course was really dull.

Theory classes took up a large portion of their days while practical classes were mainly focused on experiments of accelerated gravitational forces. Therefore, they would need to sit inside the narrow Mech simulations and practice continuously to adapt themselves to higher levels of accelerated gravitational forces and inertia. They were training the adaptive abilities of their bodies to get used to more intense Mech Piloting in order to prepare themselves for actual practice. In order to become a true Level One Mech Pilot, one would need to be equipped with comprehensive fighting abilities. Therefore, subjecting themselves to intense acceleration and inertia was a vital part of their training.

After the acceleration adapting training, it was rumored that there was a simulated battle environment to help them adapt to radiation and a tactic simulation experiment to develop different areas of their brains, besides other actual combat courses. These things were mainly determined by the different levels and types of Willpower that humans used to adapt to different environments.

Most of the time, Garen would cut class right after grasping these things quickly. He would either practice his Training Methods in his dorm room or go and discuss sales with Celine and the others.

Each day, time passed slowly until more than half a month went by in the blink of an eye.

*************

Katak.

The pale green pool ball was hit by the white cue ball lightly before it rolled slowly towards the hole at the corner after the collision.

Beside the pool table, Celine got up and used a cloth to wipe the cue while happily watching the green ball roll into the hole.

She was dressed in a white shirt and a little black vest over trousers and shiny leather shoes, which gave off a fine and mature air. At first glance, it was uncertain if people would be able to notice that she was actually a girl. Moreover, she was only a young female student who was not even twenty years old.

Garen stood on the side while dressed in a black shirt. Both of his hands were twirling the cue unenthusiastically while looking on as Celine continued to hit the balls.

The bright but soothing light cascaded downwards from above. There was a black ‘L’ shaped bar counter on the side while soft slow music played. Meanwhile, a female bartender was dazzling them with her techniques before she finished shaking the cocktail quickly. The colorful alcoholic drink formed bubbles of various pale shades when the rays of light reflected against it.

Both of them were currently inside one of the underground cellars that Celine’s family owned. This place was located within a short distance from the academy and was used as a temporary residence when Celine made special purchases.

“How are the recent business sales?” asked Garen simply in a bored manner when he noticed that Celine was about to clear the table in one go.

“Still alright. With your blessings, everything is going smoothly except that the sales operations are far too relaxed. I feel guilty every time I get one-tenth of the profits,” Celine looked at her own results happily and smiled while getting up.

“It doesn’t matter. Without your support, more money would be depleted because of many other things. You should rest at ease,” Garen smiled.

“Actually, I did not have any sales at all. When news broke out at Vivienne’s side recently, a crowd of people flocked over immediately to inquire about the supply and quantity of goods. Dozens of bottles of powder were ordered at once,” Celine was extremely satisfied with their collaboration this time. After receiving two consecutive payments, she gradually began to look forward to these collaborations. She gradually warmed up to Garen as their relationship became closer as well. Besides their mutual support for each other, both of them had favorable opinions of each other as well, allowing them to naturally have a close friendship.

“I don’t have any problems in that aspect. However, the progress of your combat training is still really terrible,” said Garen while shaking his head. “I’ve used various methods to train and guide you but you’re still unable to meet my demands.”

“Don’t you think that your demands are too high?” Celine asked in a puzzled tone. “I couldn’t even meet your demands despite risking my own life.”

“Try again during today’s training in a little while.” Garen was getting impatient. As a high-level martial arts master, he had his own honor as well. If the students he taught merely turned out to be garbage, they would definitely affect his reputation when they went out into the world.

Although he took great precautions to only teach Celine certain unimportant combat theories and general knowledge and made sure that she followed these principles and knowledge to undergo her training, the effects and results were unsatisfactory. However, he had seen Celine’s vigor for training. She had an insane passion for it and dedicated almost all of her time in training.

“You really don’t see me as a woman…” whenever Celine mentioned training, her thoughts would become somewhat silent. When she thought of Garen’s state during training, she often felt that he was strange despite her being a maniac who was always striving to become stronger.

“I should do that,” Garen watched as the last ball on the table was finally hit into the hole before a female server walked over and arranged the balls properly again. He snapped his fingers before picking the white cue ball up and placing it in the right position.

“Actually, ball games like these are much simpler. If no one disturbs me, I can usually clear the table in one go. For instance…”

He moved the cue gently.

Pop.

When the crisp noise rang out, the pool balls that were arranged properly on the table dispersed immediately. Next, they rolled calmly and slowly towards all of the holes in the surroundings.

Plop plop plop plop…

Moments later, a series of noises that indicated that the balls were rolling into the holes lingered continuously.

Celine began clapping instantly while a defeated look appeared on her face.

“Despite already knowing that your level of abnormality is out of the ordinary, I still feel unhappy whenever I see things like this. I’ve been playing pool for more than a year but I’m still not as good as you even though you only learned it two hours ago.”

“This is the difference between geniuses and normal people,” it was rare for Garen to make jokes like these.

“Perhaps you’re right,” Celine did not laugh along but shook her head instead. “Let’s go back up.”

“Mmhmm.”

Both of them put away the cues and climbed up the steps that led to the surface from the underground cellar. There was a large majestic hall at the entrance that led to the surface. The large hall was completely golden while various oil paintings depicting happy scenes were hung on the surrounding walls. Some of the paintings depicted countryside life while others depicted either metropolis scenes or portraits of prominent figures. Most of them were oil paintings of various Mech models.

A few maids attended to them and took them to wash their hands. Next, they drank some natural water before changing into a set of bandage style clothing that was especially worn during training.

One of Celine’s main habits during training was her love of wearing different types of bandage style clothing. White bandages could be wound around her chest and other more cumbersome and voluptuous parts of her body to reduce air resistance while increasing the speed of her combat movements. She was a paranoid person who would always notice the slightest bit of inefficiency.

Meanwhile, Garen was different. He changed into bandaged style clothing as well because Celine strongly suggested it but wore special protective tight clothing on top. The white protective clothing resembled a somewhat tighter white windbreaker that was both beautiful and practical.

Once both of them had changed into a new set of clothes, they entered the actual combat hall that they normally used. It was a square hall that was more than one hundred square meters wide. The surrounding walls, ceiling, and floors were covered with a thick layer of black alloy walls. This type of alloy that was known as Issim had a high level of toughness and strong spontaneous recovery abilities. It was mostly used to build the outer shell of Mechs. The true affluence of Celine’s family could clearly be seen from their usage of this material to build this room.

Almost seven to eight hundred thousand Units were spent to build a room like this.

Chapter 824: Training 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Celine had short light green hair. Although there were a few scars on her face, she still possessed a seductive figure and fair, smooth skin. In spite of the bandages wrapped around her chest as a binder, both of her ample peaks continued to protrude distinctively, exposing two extremely eye-catching buds. Long periods of training had streamlined her slender figure and caused her previously round but proportionally long limbs to tighten firmly without a single gap. Meanwhile, her hips and buttocks were merely covered by bandages that were wrapped into trouser-like shapes that only reached her knees while the other parts of her legs were completely bare. From afar, she gave off a wild charm.

However, Garen had seen all kinds of beautiful women. Naturally, his emotions would not be aroused by such a sight. There was only an extremely determined student standing in front of him now.

“After going through so many consecutive classes, your endurance test is finally over. Today’s task is acute awareness train…”

“Hold on,” Celine interrupted him suddenly. “You’ve been training me all this while but I can finally feel that my progress has increased recently. We haven’t personally engaged in actual combat yet, so why don’t we try it properly today?”

“Try it?” Garen pondered for a moment. “That’s fine too. However, are you sure that you want actual trial training?”

“What’s wrong? Is that not okay?” Celine raised her eyebrows and asked determinedly.

“It’s fine, of course. I had this plan in mind earlier as well. I’m merely bringing it forward somewhat now,” said Garen casually.

“So we’re going to do it?” Celine laughed twice and bounced on the spot lightly.

“Pay attention, I’m going to start now!”

Garen raised his hand and looked at his watch, “One minute.”

He then casually told her, “I’ll destroy you in one minute.”

“Wanna try?” suddenly, Celine felt unconvinced.

Pfoo!

She had barely finished speaking and before Garen could even raise his head fully, Celine had charged over spontaneously. She kicked her leg upwards towards Garen’s chin violently while her slender leg caused a strong gust to roll up and whistle.

If she had managed to land this kick on a regular person, her victim would already have been admitted to the hospital for serious injuries such as fractured bones.

However, this was not the case for Garen.

He deflected her move with one hand.

Bang!

When the instep of her long leg collided and intertwined with the back of his hand, Garen swayed on the spot lightly while Celine stumbled a few steps backward before making great efforts to stand steadily.

“Use all of your strength. You’re too weak,” said Garen simply.

“Easy for you to say!” Celine had fought to the point where she was provoked now. She grasped the daggers on the weapons rack beside her quickly before taking a sudden big stride forward and charging over again.

Three whooshing noises could be heard as three knives streaked across, leaving faint gleams of dazzling light. However, none of the knives hit their target as all of them were gingerly evaded by Garen without requiring him to move his footsteps at all.

“Useless,” Garen slapped his right hand downwards. He hit Celine’s arm lightly before releasing an extremely dull but loud noise that sent the daggers flying.

A banging noise could be heard before the bandages on Celine’s arms tore open and dispersed suddenly. A large bloody mess appeared on her arms immediately.

“That was really strong! Again!” Celine did not show any signs of anger but laughed instead. She took large strides and approached while preparing herself for close combat. Her elbows and one of her knees attacked in three different directions simultaneously. She formed a strange pose while the strong winds stirred around her. In her current state, she resembled a fearsome tiger that was about to pounce.

A whooshing noise could be heard suddenly when she leaped directly into the air. However, she had overexerted herself and was struck downwards by the back of Garen’s hand. A tearing noise sounded through the air immediately before the bandages that covered her entire back fell apart and tore completely. The bandages around her chest tore open at once as well while a pair of white jade-like rabbits bounced out immediately in an extremely seductive manner.

“Such quick speed!” Celine did not seem to care at all. She had truly practiced to the point of madness and was completely unconcerned that her modesty had been exposed. Instead, she pounced over immediately. She had placed her hands together closely and interlocked them before stepping forward and closing in on Garen. Her hands were ready to seize the key fibers and muscles at Garen’s weakest points.

Garen had many experiences that would help him counter close combat like this. Moreover, the current qualities of his physical body were greater than those of the average person on all fronts. This allowed him to achieve almost twice the level of a regular strong man. Even though Celine was strong enough, she was still just a woman at the end of the day. Currently, she was still at a young age and had yet to mature fully. Therefore, her strength and speed were still somewhat slower.

Both of them engaged in hand-to-hand combat while facing each other as the shadows of their fists and legs intertwined continuously.

“Spiralling Leg!” suddenly, Celine rolled on the ground before moving her legs in a looping motion towards Garen’s thighs. She was using extremely great force that would cause an average person’s bones to break immediately if they were hit. The continuous sweeping motions of her legs formed a series of circular arcs that approached Garen relentlessly.

Garen lightly jumped vertically, only dodging the hit at the most critical moment.

“Are you just going to dodge?!” roared Celine.

“Dodge?” Garen smiled and swiped his right leg down steadily while immediately kicking his left leg forward swiftly without any other fancy movements.

Bang!

When both of their legs clashed, the bandages around her legs tore open and flew away at the same time.

Garen was lucky. The tremendous force had caused Celine’s tight bandages to tear open at once. Furthermore, all the white bandages on her upper thighs had scattered completely. Her upper body was naked now while the lower part of her body could almost be seen as well.

“Still want to fight?” asked Garen, smiling.

“Of course!” Celine did not have the slightest hint of hesitation. Instead, she charged forward and continued approaching. “I haven’t lost yet!”

Their fists collided constantly with each other’s before the occasional sweeping movements of their legs were added into the mix as well.

Shh!

The fists and legs of both people intertwined immediately again before the last bandage on Celine’s body tore and flew away.

“Stop creating trouble,” Garen stretched out both of his arms slowly before increasing the pace and performing a chain of hammering punches several moments later. Both of his hands formed a large hammer that struck Celine’s right arm so quickly that it was impossible for her to react in time.

Bang!

She took two steps backward.

The second punch slammed against the top of her breasts immediately, causing her to become slightly dazed.

The third punch.

Garen stepped in a circular motion and moved behind Celine before landed three consecutive punches on her. Every punch landed on the back of her waist, releasing dull thunderous quakes.

After the loud bang, Celine was sent flying at once. She hit the ground painfully and stopped moving completely.

“That was ruthless!” she could still speak and even giggle. “This is finally strong enough!”

“Still coming?” Garen looked down at her.

“I haven’t lost yet!” for unknown reasons, Celine’s face was redder now while pink and red flushes appeared on her neck as well. “Keep going!” she had managed to support herself and stand up again after taking great pains to do it.

“This is the continuous Twelve Flying Dragon Fist that I wanted to pass on to you,” Garen tapped both of his fists together gently and made a noise that sounded like two blocks of wood colliding against each other. “Observe carefully.”

Instantly, he dashed forwards like a slender arrow and appeared like a ghost in front of Celine who had just gotten up.

Bang bang bang bang bang!!

His fists rained down upon Celine, bringing countless fragmented shadows with them. His punches landed on her chest and abdomen and when Garen turned, his punches became even stronger immediately when they landed on Celine’s back. The powerful shocks across her front and back mutually canceled each other out, forcing Celine’s body to remain on the spot without moving.

For the final punch, Garen pushed both of his hands forward and clapped downwards.

Boom!

Celine’s entire body collapsed, starting from her shoulder. She rolled forwards painfully for more than ten meters while nearly crashing into the wall.

She coughed and spat out a mouthful of blood.

“Haha! That was fun!! Again!!” her voice had become strange.

“Enough. You don’t even have enough strength to fight back anymore,” said Garen indifferently. He could vaguely smell a strange scent that he could not place. It resembled the bodily odor of a virgin faintly. He glanced over at Celine before noticing that the area between her legs was wet. Apparently, this fight had aroused her…

“Eh? It obviously hurt when you hit me earlier, so why does it feel nice instead now?” Celine could feel a strange sensation just by lying on the ground.

“This person… Don’t tell me she’s a masochist…” Garen could feel the annoyance forming black lines across his head faintly. He turned his head and looked away to avoid being rude.

“What’s wrong with being a little wet? There’s nothing to be embarrassed about, it’s just a bodily instinct. Isn’t this just an orgasm that they talk about in the books? How strange,” Celine sat on the ground casually and pointed at Garen while teasing him. “We’re just individuals who are pursuing ultimate strength, we don’t need to care about insignificant things like our flesh bodies.”

Once she had finished speaking, she stretched her legs open without a care and began to inspect the condition of her lower body right in front of Garen without covering herself at all.

This rendered Garen completely speechless. Despite experiencing three different worlds, this was the first time he had encountered such a strange specimen. If this accident had not occurred, he would not have discovered Celine’s masochistic nature and her endearingly silly personality.

“I’m going to leave first. This is about basic politeness,” Garen was helpless and could only turn around and walk towards the doorway.

“Do as you please. If you can’t even free yourself from these worldly bindings, how are you going to pursue the ultimate sources of power?” Celine’s taunts echoed behind him. “I never thought of you as someone who cared about worldly customs initially, but now I see that you can’t even let go of such things. How unfortunate.”

“This strange person…” Garen stumbled. It was truly impossible for him to understand the type of environment that this person had been brought up in.

“Remember to bring me some tissues back if you’re going out. It’s really uncomfortable to be wet down here.”

The moment he opened the door, Garen heard some noises behind him immediately.

The maids who were standing in the doorway had heard as well while dazed expressions appeared on their faces suddenly.

“You… Both of you…”

“Go get tissues!” Garen’s head was filled with unexpected rage and slight exhaustion. Perverts like Celine had no sense of shame. If this was the true meaning of being free of all moral bindings, then he would rather…

“Oh… Under… Understood…” the little maid had suffered a great shock. Her face turned as red as an apple at once but she sneaked a quick glance into the room before running away and leaving hurriedly.

Garen saw that there were other maids inside the hall whose faces were also flushed. They were other students from the academy who were hired as help. Most of them were young girls who had yet to experience real life. Therefore, their faces turned completely red at once when they heard people speaking about such topics.

Moments later, the maid who had dashed away earlier returned and lowered her blushing face before speaking softly.

“Would… Would you… need this as well?” she took out a transparent little sheath shyly and passed it towards Garen who stood in front of her.

“I just need some tissue…” Garen scratched his head and said softly. “Frankly, there’s nothing between Celine and I. You must understand, an accident happened during training. You know what I mean…”

He explained patiently but it seemed as if the maid had misunderstood something as a look of comprehension flashed across her face suddenly.

“Oh… I understand. It’s that thing, is it…”

Just then…

“What are you doing?! You haven’t brought it yet and you’ve caused it to drip across the entire floor!” Celine’s loud yells echoed from within the room again. Her voice was extremely loud, allowing the entire hall to hear her words clearly…

Garen felt an impulse to raise his hands towards the sky and utter a long cry. As he looked on at the hall full of shocked faces, he knew that it would be impossible for him to get rid of their suspicions no matter what he did.

He took the tissue paper for Celine quickly. When he saw the mischievous look on the girl’s face, he knew immediately that she had done everything on purpose.

“This is the power of worldly customs. Watch, hehe,” she sat on the ground and laughed. Frankly, this girl was not bad looking and was actually quite pretty. She had a good figure and face despite her fierce personality. She liked fighting and was crude. If she had not undergone the latest scar restoration surgery, it would not be a problem for her to pass off as a man who had more than seven scars on his chest.

When Garen remembered the cartoon that he had once watched on earth, the same black lines of annoyance formed on his head again.

“Keep sitting down if you want to die!”

“I’m just sitting here and you’re already threatening to hit me~~” Celine’s face deserved to be slapped. “Lucky for you, I haven’t had enough fun yet.”

“I…!” Garen was speechless.

Chapter 825: Destiny 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After leaving the room with Celine and changing their clothes, the girl continued to smack her lips while relishing the feeling from earlier.

Both of them sat in a separate room in the little restaurant and were personally served cups of hot tea. They lifted the cups and drank from them slowly.

“The new batch of goods has almost arrived. Should I get the convoy to send it directly to your factory or should they be sent somewhere else?” Celine took a big gulp of her tea before placing the cup down slowly and asking her question.

“Sending it to the factory will be fine. I’m taking the blended solution there to solve the issues,” Garen nodded and said. He had taken the effort to look for an experimental solution that seemed mysterious but was actually just a normal mediator to conceal the process of his Peacock Technique absorbing the compositions of the Peacock Stones.

Fortunately, the absorption process of his Peacock Technique could not be seen by most obstructed auras. The numerous blue lines that seemed extremely distinct could not actually be seen by most people. This applied to those with strong Willpowers as well. Garen had secretly looked for one of Celine’s bodyguards once to test this out. This man had Level 3 Willpower and although he was supposedly just a bodyguard, he was actually an individual that Celine really respected as those who possessed Level 3 Willpower were considered as high-level individuals. Even though he could not surpass the Level 3’s in the army who were skilled in actual combat, those in his level could not simply be hired easily.

After testing it out with him, Garen discovered that the blue lines could not be discovered by most people.

“That will be fine too,” Celine raised her arm and looked down at her watch. The convoy would arrive soon.

“That’s good. I’ll go get the goods. Will they be at the same place?” Garen stood up.

“Of course. Should I just add today’s tally to your account directly?” Celine asked casually; she was too lazy to get up and send him off.

“Up to you. Or you could just deduct it from my account. Frankly, we don’t have to be so concerned about this sum of money,” Garen waved his hand and turned around before exiting the little hall. He passed the teacup in his hand to the maid outside the doorway.

After leaving Celine’s villa and walking out of the main door of the white flower garden, Garen saw two young girls walking into the villa from the side door coincidentally. They looked like Celine’s friends.

“That girl has normal female friends too? How weird.”

He rearranged the collar of his shirt and walked out of the main door of the garden. The car that Celine had arranged for him earlier was waiting outside now. It was a fully black streamline Casipa sedan car that he liked. It looked like small-scale flying fish model interstellar airship. Surveillance cameras and lights were installed all over the body of the black car while the exhaust opening at the back resembled numerous cannons.

He pulled the car door open and sat inside. The driver looked like an earnest middle-aged man.

“Same place?” he asked in a low voice.

“Yeah, sorry for troubling you again, Uncle Carway.”

“What are you talking about?” the driver laughed as the car started moving slowly.

He sat inside the car and watched the scenery outside the car disappearing past. The pedestrians on the side of the road moved past the car window occasionally while his car sped past a few Hover Cars as unhappy drivers honked at him from behind.

They traveled from the academy, which was also where they’d left Celine’s residence. They went down the road around Blackboard Region and passed through a long stretch of student residential areas. Students who did not wish to stay in the academy would either buy or rent houses in this residential area. Next, they passed through the Commercial District where the number of cars and people had gradually increased greatly.

There were many traffic lights in the Commercial District. They had to wait for five or six traffic lights consecutively. Although more than half an hour had passed, they had barely passed through the Commercial District to enter the actual ring road that bordered the city.

There were fewer cars on the ring road and Garen was soon overcome by boredom. He decided to send a few text messages to Nono’s family to ask about their recent situation.

Nono’s parents’ new work positions suited them very well and they put all their energy into adapting to their work. They had spent many years working at the lower levels before being promoted to new positions that were neither too high nor too low. These positions were just right for them and allowed them to develop themselves to their fullest potentials.

After gradually communicating with each other more frequently, their tone of speaking became more confident and cheerful, unlike their previously silent manners. Frankly, they were unaware that everything was due to Garen’s efforts. Instead, they assumed that their quiet contributions were finally properly noticed by their company which had decided to promote them to their new positions.

After knowing the gist of his family’s situation, Garen was satisfied and decided to ask about the circumstances of his younger siblings.

“Your younger sister has gotten herself into a bad society with a scoundrel named Ansel. She won’t listen to us no matter how we urge her! She starts smashing things and throwing temper tantrums for the most trivial reasons…” when she spoke of her youngest daughter, his mother spat out all of her bottled-up grievances and feelings of helplessness. As she lamented, her previously cheerful tone disappeared at once.

“The last time she came home was a week ago. We nearly made a police report because we thought that she had gone missing. In the end, she ran home suddenly and we only realized that nothing was wrong when we found her asleep at home. I’m too afraid to even ask about her personal matters now. There was even an instance where more than ten scoundrels came to our doorstep to invite her out to dinner…”

His mother sighed heavily,”It’s fortunate that your younger brother is still very obedient. He’s working at that bakery while attending night classes. According to him, all of his coworkers are gentle and he likes working there. He won’t leave that job even though our circumstances at home have improved slightly.”

“I offered to let him attend a regular school once. What did he say about that?” Garen raised his eyebrows slightly and asked.

“He felt that he wouldn’t be able to catch up in a regular school or integrate into it properly after delaying it for such a long time. He’s fine with attending night school because he can just take regular exams later,” replied his mother.

“It’s good that he made his own decisions,” Garen nodded.

“Recently, however, your father and I have discovered that something is not quite right with your brother,” said his mother after hesitating for a while.

“What’s wrong?”

“I feel like he’s always hiding something. I don’t know what he’s doing and his voice has become extremely quiet. His entire body seems paler while his chin has become sharper. If I didn’t see him daily, I would have assumed that he was someone else,” said his mother with an uncertain look on her face while speaking on the Terminal screen. “He won’t say anything even when I ask him and I’ve started to stop worrying just like I have with that girl.”

“Is that so…? I’ll go and look for him to chat when I’m free. Perhaps there is something that’s bothering him but he’s just too uncomfortable to talk about it,” Garen smiled faintly. “Don’t worry, it shouldn’t be a serious matter.”

“Yes, it’s fortunate that you’ve grown up, Nono. You’ve become wise…” said his mother while looking at him with a relieved expression on her face.

Unconsciously, during this short period of time, Garen had gradually become the backbone of this family. He was also their main pillar of support.

He turned off the Terminal and stroked the screen on his watch gently while feeling its cool smooth surface. He remained silent and merely sat there quietly while pondering something.

The driver Uncle Carway glanced at him through the rearview mirror but remained quiet to avoid disturbing him.

The car drove across the ring road quickly. They finally reached the delivery location, an old abandoned factory, after ten minutes.

Their surroundings were completely devoid of people. Only stray cats and dogs could be seen passing through the area occasionally before vanishing into the nearby undergrowth here.

Two little white trucks were already waiting at the entrance of the factory. A young man in white clothes stood beside the vehicle and walked over automatically when he saw Garen get down from the car on the other side.

“I apologize for troubling you with having to personally check the goods this time.”

He shook hands with Garen while smiling enthusiastically. This fellow had sunken cheeks and the air of a soldier around him. He had actually served in the military service before.

“I wanted the goods, so it’s only right that I come over and take a look at them,” Garen nodded without wasting time on unnecessary chatter. He walked over to the back of the truck and pulled the trunk door open with a ‘clang’ before looking inside.

A large wooden box was placed inside the dark boot of the vehicle. After jumping on top of the car, Garen opened the box quickly. The box was filled to the brim with white Rainbow Stones that were the size of a fist and were clearly of good quality.

“Don’t worry. All of these are fine objects that we picked out carefully. None of them are unsatisfactory!” said the skinny man outside the car.

Garen picked up two random stones. It looked as if he was rubbing the white Rainbow Stones together and checking their quality. However, he was actually using his Peacock Technique to test the stones secretly.

“They’re truly not bad,” after checking them for awhile and confirming that these stones were of sufficient weight, Garen put the stones in his hand back down and closed the box before jumping off the truck again.

“You can send them to the Factory Number One directly. We’ve taken over the goods so you can return and report on your task now.”

The skinny man nodded and smiled. He was not one of Celine’s people. Instead, he and the other person who had driven were Vivienne’s people who were also members of Blue Narcissus. Garen had hired them over as temporary workers just to perform minor tasks.

After receiving the goods successfully, Garen sat inside a truck with a new driver and returned on the same road.

The road was not as congested this time, allowing them to return to Blackboard Academy within twenty minutes.

Without any delay, he jumped out of the car and returned to his dorm room to take the solution that he had prepared earlier before entering the truck alone and getting the driver to take him to the factory immediately. He stayed in the car alone without allowing anyone else to enter.

Inside the dark car, Garen could vaguely feel some swaying movements from the car. He ignored them and raised his head to look at the surveillance cameras inside the car. He reached his hand outwards and covered it directly until the corners. Next, he placed a little hat on it that he had specially prepared earlier to cover the range of its line of sight.

Once all of his preparations were completed, Garen sat down and crossed his legs while looking at the whole box of white Rainbow Stones in front of him.

“This is a critical moment that will impact my absorption…” he murmured quietly while looking at the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his vision. There was only a distance of approximately twenty percent before his Peacock Technique could reach Level 4. This box of white Rainbow Stones would definitely help him surpass his limitations to truly reach the first grade of Level 1 Willpower.

“Begin… Truly break off the little Moonfang now and enter Level 1 Willpower… Obtain the true strength that belongs to you…”

He took a deep breath and outstretched his hand to open the lid on the box.

******************

Beside Blackboard River

Pfoo… Pfoo… Pfoo…

Clint’s forehead was beaded with sweat. He bent his waist and panted while supporting himself with his hands on his knees.

While looking at the large pile of black Mech pieces in front of him, a strange sense of accomplishment stirred in his head suddenly.

“How… How is it…? I went through great pains to piece together a complete… system…” as he looked on at the pile of odds and ends, although they looked extremely miserable, he knew that these items were sufficient as the basis of the first step to establishing the detection abilities that would allow them to distinguish and determine enemies.

“What ‘how’? You’re just using your basic physical body to live, so what’s the big deal?” said Red Moon impatiently. “Don’t disturb me. I’m still investigating the original documents regarding the links of the interior circuits.”

“Sigh…” Clint felt slightly discouraged as he’d initially expected that he would receive Red Moon’s praise instead. “What are we going to do next?”

“Keep assembling the parts. Follow the blueprints the same way I taught you earlier and link the parts to form the shape I want,” Red Moon explained. He sounded somewhat distracted when he spoke and it was obvious that he was busy with something else.

“Understood…”

Clint’s hair was constantly blown backward by the river breeze, making him seem like a child’s shaggy toy.

When he walked over to check some parts that he had picked up, Clint was about to move his hand to shift a piece when he suddenly saw a person walking towards him slowly from the far end of the river bank. This person’s figure was very familiar but also slightly strange. They were dressed from head to toe in black clothing and had covered themselves up fully even on a hot sunny day like this. They even wore a baseball cap and large sunglasses that shielded more than half of their face.

Chapter 826: Destiny 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Lon?” Clint pursued him and yelled loudly.

The other person was looking around initially as Clint had been blocked by the pile of parts here. Once he heard the shouts, he noticed Clint there immediately and ran towards him.

“Is it really you, Lon?!” once the other person had approached him, a surprised look appeared on Clint’s face when he finally recognized the figure in black clothing. “Why are you dressed like this when you’re not even a big celebrity? You look like you’re afraid of meeting someone you know.”

Baylon stopped walking and rested while panting lightly.

“Clint, do you know what happened to my body? After you spoke to me that day, I felt as if my mind was suddenly filled with many unknown things while my body seems to have become weird and different.”

He couldn’t explain it but Clint had always felt that Lon was somewhat strange, as if something was not quite right with him.

“It’s not a big deal actually, hehe… I met with a minor accident and I need your help… One of my friends…” Before he could finish speaking, his eyes widened suddenly while his gaze drifted behind Baylon towards the further end of the river bank. “What’s that?”

He had barely finished speaking before the little white dot in the sky above the river bank flew towards them suddenly.

It was actually a large pure white blood-sucking mosquito that was as smooth as a mirror on the surface. He could tell that it was a technologically advanced object at the first glance. Its most prominent features were its blood red eyes and sharp blood sucking mouthpart that was a meter long. It looked abnormally fierce.

The mosquito noticed Clint and Baylon instantly.

‘Suspicious targets have been discovered. Preliminary steps to approach them are in progress. Willpower force field sampling…’

This mosquito was at least two meters long and two meters wide. It looked like a normal blood-sucker that had been enlarged numerous times. Its wings were currently vibrating and making buzzing noises as it flew towards Clint and the other boy.

‘Target is being verified… One of the pieces has been determined. It has not been expanded yet. Will begin attacking and attempting to retrieve it,” a cold mechanical noise echoed from within the mosquito’s body.

Moments later, its cold blood red eyes glared at Clint and Baylon instantly.

“Eh… This is…? Damn! It’s a colony of drones!!!” said Red Moon suddenly when he recognized them and was shaken from his thoughts in a flustered manner. “Someone has discovered me! Escape quickly!!”

“Eh?” Clint stood on the spot in a daze without reacting.

Hiss…

Two noises that sounded like air jets could be heard as two of the white mosquito’s sharp skinny legs broke off suddenly. It spurted towards Clint and Baylon instantly and flew towards them.

Both of its fine legs carefully sprayed murky red flames outwards. Shockingly, both of them were actually two disguised targeting missiles!

Clint and Baylon were both shocked and could not react to their current situation at all.

“It’s a condensed missile!” Red Moon’s voice rang out suddenly.

Instantly, Clint understood.

It seemed as if everything that Red Moon had said was true. The supposed Forbidden Mech and unknown forces that were pursuing him and the potential dangers he would encounter in the future… Everything was true.

Regarding these matters, he’d initially assumed that the other person was just joking, teasing, kidding! Things like this only occurred in novels and would not happen to him for no reason. Although he had always done things according to Red Moon’s instructions, he had never believed any of these things deep inside his heart.

However, while looking at the two condensed missiles that were flying quickly towards him now, Clint suddenly understood everything at once.

At this point, the missiles had only been flying here for less than two seconds after they were launched. Despite the short span of time, Clint had already thought about many things within these two seconds.

As the missile approached closer, everything seemed as if it was being shot in slow motion. His mind became completely empty as he’d never encountered a situation like this before. What was he supposed to do? Hide? Where would he go to hide? What kind of place would he hide in? How would he hide? What would he do? He did not know anything. Unfamiliar feelings of helplessness flooded his mind.

“That’s right! Lon is still here!!” suddenly, he thought of Baylon who was in front of him. “I can drag him into this too!!”

“You can’t involve him!!”

Clint felt a strange strength stirring in the depths of his heart suddenly.

He reached his hand out and used his mightiest strength and fastest speed to push himself in front of Baylon’s body in one quick movement.

“You should stay out of the way! Why do you care whether other people live or die??!!” scolded Red Moon loudly while hiding inside his mind. When he noticed suddenly that something was not quite right with the directions of Clint’s movements, he made some quick calculations before his mind nearly exploded with anger.

“You idiot! Go left! Left!!!! My God!!! For God’s sake, why are you so stupid?!!”

They could have definitely have evaded the dangers easily if Clint had not made it into a fatal situation. Coincidentally, the direction in which he threw himself towards and later pushed Baylon was where the missile was actually headed…

“Forget about it, I’ll take matters into my own hands…” desperate times called for desperate measures, and Red Moon had no choice but to take action and interfere with the flying missile’s tracking to deflect it towards two other sides.

Sure enough, once the interference signal was released, both of the missiles instantly flew towards two separate sides. After two explosions rang out, everything became peaceful again.

“Pfoo…” Red Moon exhaled heavily. “You’re going to scare me to death sooner or later if this continues.”

‘Target discovered. Self-destruction sequence in progress…’ suddenly, a beeping mechanical noise could be heard from one of the white mosquitos on the other side.

“What?” Red Moon was dumbfounded.

Clint who had just breathed a sigh of relief was stunned as well.

They watched the mosquito shrink its body into a ball before deconstructing and assembling itself into a silvery white sphere. There was a glimmering pale red layer shining off its surface.

“Damn! It’s a freaking Fuel Air Explosive!!” Red Moon could not help but curse.

It was a weapon of mass destruction with a range of two hundred meters! The Fuel Air Explosive was so powerful that people who were hiding underground would suffer the repercussions and die as well. It could remove all the air and oxygen in the area within moments too.

“To hell with your…!!”

He could not even finish cursing in time. The only thing they could hear was thunderous…

Boom!!

At that moment, a white light shined brightly and exploded within seconds. It turned into a thin white cloud that dispersed in every direction.

A white mushroom-like cloud rose from the side of the river bank and reached ten meters above it. It covered more than two to three hundred meters of the grounds in the surroundings.

The Mech pieces were blown away by the explosion, causing most of them to fly away. There were only a few sharp pieces that remained in their original locations because they had been stabbed in the ground earlier.

The intense cloud explosion blew all of the bits and pieces in their surroundings away. The terrifying impact force tore the steel to shreds and lifted the muddy water from the river bank. The force crashed into the ground, exposing the black mud that was hidden many meters below.

At the center of the white clouds, fiery red flames had begun to burn, covering a range of over two hundred square meters within moments.

At this moment, a dark red dot lit up where Clint was located suddenly. Its redness was as deep and dark as blood. It was also dense and sticky like a liquid droplet that coagulated after puddles of blood had evaporated.

“Red King…” a low voice that could be heard indistinctly echoed from the sky.

Pfoo!!

Numerous blood-red clouds floated out of the blood droplets suddenly. The bloody clouds formed a large sphere that contained wandering nebulae, a glimmering Milky Way, and countless twinkling stars.

Within the endless galaxy, an unimaginably large scarlet Mech floated above the center of the nebula quietly.

The humanlike red Mech had an extremely long tail that was coiled around its body like a snake.

Ka…

The Mech raised its head slowly as if it was looking at something in the sky or the universe.

Boom!!

The blood clouds exploded suddenly and formed a red circular ripple. The exploded red cloud immediately canceled out the impact of the flames of the Fuel Air Explosive that were sweeping over.

Simultaneously, a strange vibration passed through their surroundings in that moment… It traveled further and further away…

*************************

At the bottom of an abyss

A pure white Mech that was immersed in lava opened its eyes suddenly before the third golden eye on its forehead too opened.

“Forbidden… Hahahaha… I’ve finally found it!!” the sound of deep, strange male laughter echoed from inside the Mech.

The white Mech was more than sixty meters tall and beginning to float out of the lava slowly. It exposed its elegant and fine airframe before two large white pauldrons extended from its body sideways. From afar, they seemed like a second pair of arms.

A red glowing line of lava flowed downwards from the center of the Mech’s body while the numerous red lines formed a gigantic star symbol.

Within the surroundings of the abyss, two other white Mechs with the exact same symbol on their chests in glowing green lines stood upright. They were the Great Light Mechs that had trespassed into Blackboard Region.

*************************

Blackboard Academy

Hall of the Power Holders

The positions where the virtual images of the three head professors were located lit up clearly. The three figures appeared here one by one.

“These forces are…” the Dean gripped the armrest of the chair lightly.

“Forbidden…” Vice Principal Simis answered softly. “Finally… The legendary Forbidden Core has appeared here… Can you sense the hidden messages in the forces there?”

“Red King… Is this an opportunity… Or a catastrophe…?” the old woman’s eyes were downcast.

“In any case, we have to find the location of that item immediately! Holders! We may decide to either protect or capture them, but everything is still too early now,” said the Dean, making the final decision.

“We have no choice but to request for Black Star to return.”

“There’s no need for that, there aren’t many people who can detect these forces. Getting Medero to sort it out will be fine,” said Vice Principal Simis, shaking his head. “Black Star’s hasty return will only make people more suspicious. They may even focus their gazes over here.”

“Alright.” Dean Cruz von Shaw reached her hand out and tapped the area in front of her lightly before a virtual display floated out in front of her. “Fortunately, this force can only be sensed by those around us. If the other regions find out, the outcome will be inconceivable. We must set up an interference for the force immediately.”

*********************

Inside the car

Strangely, Garen felt as if some of his Willpower forces were scattering faintly. He was unable to sense these forces at first, and could not detect this strength as well if his soul was not much stronger than most and if he did not possess a few Soul Seeds.

“This is…”

He stretched his hand out and pressed it against a white Rainbow Stone. He was planning to absorb some of its Peacock Stone properties. He could sense the different types of information inside these subtle forces.

“It seems like some major changes have occurred…” Garen’s Soul Seeds could detect the general situation of the world. He had previously used this ability to determine where the protagonists in the worldly situations where located. Once again, his Soul Seeds were clearly experiencing these feelings again.

After hesitating for a while, he cast aside the distracting thoughts in his mind.

“No matter what changes have occurred, they are not something that my current self can grasp. Only by ensuring that I am strong enough will I have the right to gain benefits.”

He focused his mind and pressed one hand downwards with great force before closing his eyes.

Shh…

Numerous blue lines stretched out of his palm slowly before piercing through the white Rainbow Stones inside the box.

Chapter 827: Destiny 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The large pile of White Peacock Stone fragments was absorbed by the blue lines before flowing into Garen’s body continuously.

On the Attribute Pane inside his vision, the changes within the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had gradually occurred.

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, origins unknown. Level Two Heart Reformation uses the Hellfrost Peacock’s blood as the standard for the Heart Reformation to achieve the aim of strengthening the physique of the entire body progressively. Reformation time: completed.’

‘Level Three Stomach Reformation has been completed. Peacocks possess great swallowing abilities and their stomachs can digest almost any substance. Once it has been integrated with Heart Reformation, it will create the Devour ability.’

‘Natural ability obtained: Devour (The Queen of Peacocks’ basic but strongest talent). Produces Distorted Seeds.’

‘Completion rate of Level Four is at 78%.’

From 78%, it slowly crawled to 80%, and then jumped to 90%… 100%!

The moment it reached the one hundred percent mark, Garen suddenly felt a cold sensation surging out from his heart and flowing towards the various parts of his body. It felt as if he had suddenly jumped into an icy pond on a hot sunny day. It felt really nice at first until the temperature grew colder and caused his entire body to ache!

“Mmm…” Garen could not help but make a noise. However, he had yet to notice that many special changes had already occurred in his body while he sat cross-legged in the car.

It felt as if his entire body was pulsing like a beating heart. Meanwhile, a thin blue icy layer had covered the surface of his body. This icy layer was constantly extending itself towards his surroundings. It extended from the floor inside the car towards the other objects around it.

His hair was gradually turning somewhat blueish as well. It seemed as if his Secret Techniques were beginning to modify his physical body and its properties progressively. The color of his pupils was darkening to an extremely dark blue.

The icons on his Attribute Pane were currently transforming from blurry images to clearer ones, and changes had begun to appear throughout the information and messages regarding the initial Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, Level Four. Completion rate of Level Five is at 7%.’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Devour (Devours various living things to restore body)’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Distorted Seed (Creating chaos is the Hellfrost Peacock’s favorite pastime)’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Cold Chaos (Causes fluctuations in time and space naturally and releases cold air naturally within an area of ten meters to create a chaotic low-temperature area with the lowest point at ten degrees. Simultaneously, there is a low probability that it will trigger confusion within the minds of its enemies, causing them to attack randomly)’

“It seems like Cold Chaos is the ability that I gained after completing Level Four. I get new abilities even before completing new levels. This is pretty good,” Garen examined his abilities carefully. Strangely enough, each ability that was formed by the Living Secret Techniques had corresponded with his body completely like the Natural Abilities. When he used them, it felt the same as using his Attribute Abilities. It felt as if he had been born with these talents.

“They are truly mystical Living Secret Techniques,” he turned around and looked at his surroundings. Everything around him, including the floor of the car, was releasing gloomy cold air faintly. Moreover, the source of this cold air was his own body.

“The effects are not that great but they would probably be very useful in the Secret Technique World instead. Since this is a powerful world with Mechs that can destroy planets, these abilities are not as significant anymore.”

He studied the dispersing cold air carefully. It did not consume a large portion of his energy as it was almost the same temperature as his own body. He tried to suppress and restrain this cold air slowly.

“A range of ten meters. If I suppress it for some time before it’s released suddenly, perhaps it can be used to scare others. After engaging in a fierce battle for a long time, releasing it will probably affect my opponent’s bodily temperatures as well. This is not bad.”

Although there were temperature cycle systems inside the Mechs that would help them remain at constant temperatures, these objects require specific resources. Meanwhile, Garen’s chill could seemingly pass through the Mech’s materials. Moreover, there was a low probability that it could affect his opponent’s minds as well. Therefore, these abilities would have unimaginable uses during large scale battles if he developed and strengthened them properly.

Garen sucked the chills back into his body and investigated the other changes that he had undergone. The most important part was his Willpower.

‘Willpower — Lower Level One, (Obtained an additional level of strengthening and increasing abilities from the Living Secret Techniques)’

(Training Method: Blackboard Manipulation, Blackboard Academy’s free Training Method. Continuous training weakens its effects and its progression speed has been set at every twelve years for each level) The highest level is Level One.’

“Finally…” Garen was extremely emotional at this moment. He had been constantly anxious about relying on the Moonfang all this while because he was worried that someone might see through him. Moreover, he could not fight for extended periods of time because the Moonfang would collapse and stop working after exceeding a certain time frame.

Now, however, he had finally been able to achieve the true standard of Level One!

At this moment, he was truly standing on the same starting line as the other geniuses in the Academy. Although he had a late start and was slightly slower, it was still better than when he could only disguise himself and use the Moonfang previously.

Lower Level One was where most of the Elites in the classes of the Academy were located. The first three seats in each class would rightfully be placed in that position. The First Seat was not achievable right now, but he had definitely surpassed the standards and levels of most students already. If he needed to retake certain subjects to reach his standard, it was also possible for Garen to request for graduation exams now as well.

While looking at the box full of high-energy fuel powder, Garen poured the solution that he had brought with him inside and stirred it for a little while to conceal the traces of his absorption.

He had not reached the factory yet but Garen was not anxious at all. He continued to sit inside the car and began to check the upgrades that had occurred in his Peacock Technique this time and the changes to his physical body.

He had memorized the initial data clearly.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 1.7, Agility 1.5, Vitality 1.8, Intelligence 1.5, Potential 0%. Soul Limit 40.’

His gaze shifted to check his current data.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 2.1, Agility 2.0, Vitality 2.7, Intelligence 1.9, Potential 0%. Soul Limit 40.’

“Strength has increased by 0.4, Agility by 0.5, while my Vitality has increased by a maximum of 0.9. That’s certainly expected of a living creature that consumes Vitality. Finally, my Intelligence has increased by 0.4. My qualities seemed to have increased evenly except for the emphasis on Vitality.”

Garen stood up and felt the sensations throughout his vastly improved body.

His physical qualities had already reached his peak levels in the Secret Technique World. Most bullets and weapons would be ineffective towards his current self. However, it was different that time. The Secrets Techniques that he’d practiced previously were Golden Statue Techniques which were widely known as Defensive Secret Techniques that were used for guarding. Once he had entered the highest realm, he realized that they were completely different from the normal grade levels. Therefore, the current qualities of his physical body had not necessarily achieved the actual combat abilities that he had previously possessed in the Secret Technique World yet.

“In other words, my Living Secret Techniques do not have any specific combat or attacking experiences yet. Perhaps an inclination towards one of my body’s physical qualities during training or a certain aim is improving my Vitality levels,” Garen murmured when he’d suddenly thought of this point.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique continued to deepen and upgrade continuously because of his training, while some vague development towards reaching inhuman levels had also appeared. Garen had noticed this point as well.

After gathering his thoughts, he took care of the high-energy fuel powder quickly and closed the lid of the box. This thing was as precious as gold.

The car had begun to slow down as well. It was a sign that they had almost arrived at their destination.

After a short while, Garen felt the car jolt suddenly before finally rolling to a stop. He got up and took the cover off the monitor.

“We’ve arrived, Mr. Nono,” the driver’s voice echoed from the monitor.

“I know.”

Garen opened the car door and got down while carrying the box that weighed more than a hundred pounds and walking directly into the nearby factory.

This place was a desolate area that was surrounded by fields. There was not a soul in sight, and the lonely factory sat a short distance from him.

Four to five bodyguards got down and encircled Garen before accompanying him towards the factory.

It was important to note that the box that Garen was holding was worth millions of Universal Units. Therefore, extremely strict guarding measures were naturally important.

They had only taken a few steps before all of the guards inside the factory came out. There were more than ten of these men and each of them had laser guns and knives at their waists. Their bodies exuded powerful vibes.

They were obviously professionals who had previously seen blood.

There were no incidents during the handover as Celine and Vivienne’s subordinates were among these people, and people from Blue Narcissus were observing them as well. Their surroundings had seemed desolate but there were actually many hidden individuals who had been stationed there secretly.

After receiving profits of hundreds of thousands several times, all three parties had started to value this business because there was still a possibility for it to increase continuously.

The factory manager’s name was Geen and he was a young man with blonde hair. He was dressed in a suit and leather shoes when he walked out to greet Garen. He observed every single person around Garen carefully as if he was trying to discern something.

“Mr. Nono, although our personal relationship allows us to somewhat talk personally despite being strangers, as you are a major shareholder that controls four layers of profits, I think that you should look for bodyguards.”

“Where’s Kendall? I will consider this aspect,” Garen nodded. He had already thought of recruiting some subordinates to guard his personal safety. He had an income of over one million Units each month and a business that was constantly improving. It would mean bad news if he was targeted by others. The weapons in this world were not as simple as those in the previous worlds. Who could be sure that an unknown, extremely powerful weapon wouldn’t appear suddenly?

“Mr. Kendall had left for Sicalia earlier, but he should be on his way back now.”

“Yes, I was the one who asked him to go there. But since he hasn’t returned yet, could he have encountered some problems on the road?” Garen nodded.

“It seems that the garrison had cordoned the road off temporarily and delayed his return.”

“In regards to bodyguards, do you have any good suggestions?” Garen asked directly. He knew that this man was from foreign lands and previously had social connections to elite talents. This man had sought refuge with six different forces before finally leaving with his own. He was the type of person whose heart could not settle down. The most important aspect was that he was not one of the three main cooperative forces.

“Speaking of candidates, I actually have a few,” Geen smiled and walked into the factory while being guarded by a separate group of people just like Garen.

“The Giant Shark Mercenaries hail from the Maria Region. They have twenty members and are rumored to possess the strength of forty people in a terrifying net of firepower. There is also the Charm Mercenary Troop that is filled with only the finest and most beautiful mercenaries of a high standard. They have six members and if each of their beauties is worth their price… You should know what that means…” Geen cast a perverted gaze at Garen.

“I’m only looking at their strength and cost,” said Garen while his expression remained unchanged.

“In terms of strength, both of these groups are first-rate mercenaries. Their average strengths are at Level Two while their Commanders and Vice Commanders are at Level Three standards and possess their own unique skills. As for cost, it’s good timing that they’re off-duty now and living casual and relaxed lives. Therefore, they won’t be expensive to hire. The Giant Shark Mercenaries cost two hundred thousand each month excluding food and living expenses. Meanwhile, Charm costs one hundred and forty thousand each month,” Geen clearly had some connections with both of these mercenary groups.

Chapter 828: Fate 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I’ll pick Charm then. They’re cheap and I get to see some beautiful girls. I’ll have eye candies and the expenditure isn’t huge as well since I have to maintain their Mechs, right?” Garen did his research on this aspect.

“Indeed. The Mech’s maintenance cost is within the tens of thousands per month bracket and that isn’t considered expensive at all. I knew that you would have chosen Charm. This is a newly formed mercenary group and they’re cheaper because they aren’t that well known. Furthermore, they are willing to do their best to get their name out there,” Geen started smirking.

“Hey, didn’t you just say that they’re on vacation here? And now they’re a newly formed group?” Garen felt that he was being cheated.

“Don’t worry about it. They definitely have the quality and you’ll get to see the pretty girls. Isn’t it a win-win situation? The Charm mercenary group consists of pure, charming enchanting, busty girls. There’s a variety of them~~” Geen said enticingly.

“This…” Garen acted as if he was in a dilemma as this was the kind of his reaction that he should possess for his puberty age.

“Believe in me. It’ll be fine!” Geen held onto Garen’s shoulder as he said with a smile on his face. “What’s most important is that they’re seriously lacking male populations in the Maria Region. One of the main reason they came here is to find an outstanding male to leave his seeds for them. Do you know what I mean?” His smile became even more perverted as he continued.

Leaving his seeds…

Garen had heard of such a rumor where the population of male to female ratio in the Maria Region was one to nine. There were very few numbers of males in the region, so much so that the whole country was governed by females. There were also a lot of rumors in the Maria Region that the girls didn’t wish to be married and yet wished to enjoy life and give birth to offsprings. Hence such a behavior had sprung about.

Once they had found an outstanding male, they would spend some time with him and lead a ‘breeding’ lifestyle. Once they had obtained the seeds they would return back to their country.

“Are you saying that this mercenary group…” Garen’s eyelid started twitching.

“You’re correct. Their other motive is what you’re thinking right now…” Geen started smirking.

In order to maintain their population count of Maria Domain, the seeding phenomena were very common among the females from the Maria Domain. However, it was rare for a group of beautiful women to seek a breeder together.

Furthermore, rumor had it that the women from that region were very dominant and initiative. If they were to get married to a man, the man would be fated to stay at home and do the house chores, taking care of the kids and supporting the woman from behind…

There were even unrestrained women who liked prostitution where they would find handsome men from foreign countries to have a go with them…

However, it was for the best…

Frankly speaking, Garen wasn’t even interested in the strength of the mercenary group. These maids could only be used to run some errands at best. In case he encountered any trouble, he could push the blame to the mercenary group to avoid any unnecessary trouble as well.

With his current physical strength, he could kill everyone in the vicinity with ten steps or less, including the elites who possessed level three Willpower. Garen’s martial arts were so great that they wouldn’t even have the time to activate their Willpower before dying to Garen’s attack.

However, once there was a distance between them or he was fighting against a Mech, he would be powerless as he would be seriously threatened by just pure Willpower alone.

Furthermore, there were all sorts of protections on a Mech as well. Fortunately, there were very few people permitted to operate a mech in the Blackboard Region so it wasn’t much of a concern.

“I guess it’s decided then. I’ll rely on you to get them here when the time comes,” Garen had determined that money was just a number to him at this point. He had managed to purchase the level three training methods that he wanted within a short amount of time. Furthermore, money wasn’t required for him to train his Peacock Technique and the main purpose of him hiring mercenaries was to protect his family and cover himself up.

The mercenary group’s purpose wasn’t just as simple as accepting every protection mission, he would also need them to fight against that technique as well… He simply needed to react to the situation rather than having to protect himself against any ambushes.

“I’ll handle it!” Geen patted his own chest.

***************

Clang!

Clint dug himself out from the ruins with difficulty as he pushed aside the metal scraps above his head. Dust was floating about in the air and he couldn’t see his surroundings clearly.

“Lon!!”

He started shouting.

There was no reaction…

Clint was completely covered in dirt and had small wounds all over him. His shirt had been torn into scraps and it looked like a ragged cloth.

“Lon! Where are you?” he shouted as his face started to turn anxious.

“He… Here…” suddenly, a fragile-sounding voice came from behind.

Clint immediately turned around and saw a person whose face couldn’t be recognized and was as dirty as him under the ruins.

He recognized that it was Lon’s voice and immediately went forward and pushed the junk away from him.

“You alright?”

“I’m fine… Just some slight injuries,” it was a miracle that Lon hadn’t been seriously injured and was able to live from that explosion.

“That explosion earlier…” Clint recalled what had transpired just a moment ago.

“Was a fart! Run for your life!” Red Moon’s voice came from beside him.

“Master Red Moon!” Clint was very happy to see him. “Did you protect us?”

“Naturally! Pack up and let’s scram out of here! Your boss has just used all of his accumulated strength to protect you, but we’ll all be dead even if a mosquito decides to attack us!” although Red Moon spoke arrogantly, a faint note of fragility could be heard in his tone.

“The Mech Assembly is fine. Please take this,” as Red Moon finished speaking, Clint saw a red vortex suddenly appearing in front of him. Then an item flew out of the vortex and dropped into his hand.

This red item resembled a nail clipper yet at the same time, it looked like a clamp. It was the length of half a finger and there were numbers and symbols which was almost worn off as they looked very faint. It seemed to have existed for a very long time.

“What is this?”

Out of curiosity, Clint tried to figure out what it was.

“How can you be so dense! Do as I say, quickly! We need to gather up all the stuff that we have obtained. Take only the good ones and ignore the rest! Quick!! Trouble is just around the corner!” Red Moon scolded.

“DId… someone speak?” finally, Baylon who was standing at one side finally spoke up. “Is it a communication device?”

“You idiot. Help me this instant! You’re Baylon, right? I’ve sacrificed a lot for your level one Willpower. If you’re useless in this situation, how are you supposed to warm the bed up for Clint!” Red Moon didn’t care if Baylon had accepted any of this as he directed his anger towards him.

“Huh?” after hearing what he’d said, not just Baylon, even Clint was stunned.

“This guy is a fake. He’d returned back to his original form after his Willpower was modified. Stop acting as if it was a strange thing!” Red Moon replied unhappily.

“A fake… ” Clint then stared at Baylon with his eyes wide open. “Master Red Moon. Do you mean that… Lon… Lon is a girl!!” He increased his tone.

“Don’t worry about it. She’s a beauty,” Red Moon said with a perverted face. “It’s been a while I’ve watched an adult video. You guys should do the deed in front of me after this. Entertainment these days are truly boring!”

Both Clint and Baylon started blushing as they stood still in the ruins, not know what to do.

“You idiots. Start packing the stuff and run! Why the f*ck are you still standing there!” Red Moon couldn’t hold back and started spewing vulgarities once more.

“Okay… okay..” two of them replied immediately.

That small item was stupidly easy to use. One just had to aim at the item that one wanted to pack and gently press onto it. The items would then vanish as if it was swallowed into another dimension.

The packing was finished in a very short amount of time. After picking up the well-conditioned goods, both of them ran towards a deserted river bank and called Clint’s sister with the Watch Terminal at the same time so that she could send someone over with a new set of clean clothes.

************

Bam!!

A pair of white and black Mechs collided strongly against each other. Wielding a sword with only one of its arms, the Black Mech lightly gestured with its right hand and a black frisbee suddenly appeared in the sky, flying forth at high speed. It spun as it tried to cut through the White Mech. It formed a black line as it came down from the sky, but it was instantly sent away by the opponent’s attack.

Surrounding them was the wilderness of the Blackboard Doman’s outskirts. Not far away from here, there was another Black Mech aiming at the White Mech and attempting to snipe it. Both Black Mechs had a Blackboard emblem on them

“Matthew!” the Black Mech which was engaged in the battle shouted as it immediately backed off.

Boom!!

A clear laser cannon was shot and landed on the back of the White Mech, which made it stagger. However, it was very strange as there were no signs of injuries on the White Mech as if the cannon had been completely ineffective against it.

“With my Weakening Field activated, all long-range attacks will never be able to leave a scratch on my Mech. How can you still not get it after trying so many times?” The White Mech said as a green diamond-shaped crystal could be seen on its front. The crystal was faintly reflecting the sunlight, giving off an illusion that it was glowing.

“Even if it’s ineffective, at least it can exhaust your WIllpower and Mech’s Power Source,” the Black Mech which was in close combat replied.

“How foolish. Both of your strengths are level four at best. Even if you had perfect coordination, you could only delay me for that little bit. Can’t Blackboard send a stronger person than you to fight me?” the White Mech looked around. “Oh right. Where has that cute little girl run off to? I love my girls to be under eighteen heh. Furthermore, she’s pretty good looking too. If you’re willing to hand over her to me, I’ll consider letting you guys live.”

“Go to hell!”

Matthew fired off another cannon shot from afar and hit the White Mech’s head. However, there was no effect and only a small wisp of white smoke drifted from its head.

“What kind of monster is he!! Even the level five instructors in the academy aren’t this powerful!” Boris stared at the red white Mech as despair started to overwhelm him.

His close combat skills were overwhelmingly powerful and long-range attacks didn’t work on him as all incoming projectiles within an area of a hundred meters would be slowed down, decreasing its energy source and its potency.

Chapter 829: Lurk 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Did the instructor send us here so that he can humiliate us?” Boris cracked his occasional cold joke and it was obvious that his opponent didn’t appreciate it.

The Red-White Mech started chirping loudly as it immediately leaped forward while spinning its body at high speed. With swords in both of its hands, it looked like a top spinning at high speed.

Straight gouges were left in the ground as the sword slashed the surface.

“Quentin Slash! Hahaha! Go to hell!!!” a twisted laughter came from within the Red-White Mech.

The rotating slashes were moving towards Boris, who didn’t have the time to evade at all. He then grabbed the Blackboard Frisbee and stabbed it into the ground in front of him.

Clank!!

White sparks could be seen as the swords clashed against the frisbee.

Boris took a few steps back as half of his Mech was completely chopped off. It was fortunate that the Cockpit located at the chest was unharmed so he could still move.

On the other hand, a long dagger could be seen on the Red-White Mech. The dagger had been pierced deep into his back. It almost pierced through the cockpit and this made the pilot of the Red White Mech sweat coldly.

“Who’s there!! Show yourself!?” he turned around immediately as he knew that this person, who was able to overcome his Weakening Field, was definitely not the same guy who could only hide from afar and shoot at him.

Within the sands and dust that floated in the air, a pair of red eyes glowed faintly as a huge black object walked towards him slowly.

Bam.

The black object casually threw aside a red white Mech’s head as it slowly walked out from the sandstorm. There were still markings and electric arcs sparking from the bottom of the head. It was obvious that it had been ripped off from a Mech just a moment ago.

Hiss…

With the black Mech as the epicenter, the air blew in all directions and trembling could be felt in an area of several hundred meters.

“This is.. the Willpower Field… Hiss…!” the Red-White Mech inhaled deeply. “No! This doesn’t make sense! You… How can you gather a Willpower Field at such a young age!? How is that possible!?”

“It’s Sister Red-Eyed Medero!!” Boris finally recognized that person. “Big sister! How’s Allie?!”

“I’ve saved her so she’s fine. Originally I’m supposed to be here as an insurance but I didn’t expect the opponent to be this strong,” Medero responded calmly. “You guys can retreat now because I alone will be enough to handle him.”

“Understood!” Matthew and Boris had already given up on fighting this Red-White Mech monster a long time ago as long-ranged attacks were completely ineffective against him and he was overwhelmingly powerful in melee combat. He was obviously an opponent of a different class.

Two Mechs immediately flew back to where they came from.

They could see the remains of many Mechs along the way back, including those of the Red-White Mechs in small amounts. Some Mech soldiers that had, fortunately, survived the attack had gathered together and helped their allies as ambulances from the city swarmed to their location.

As both of them landed, they were immediately surrounded by multiple ambulances and were taken out of their Mechs.

Matthew was drenched in blood and sweat and these fluids had completely soaked his shirt. While he looked like he was seriously injured, it was just a phenomenon where his blood vessels had burst due to the immense stress from operating the Mech.

“What the current situation? What’s the death count?” it was the first thing he asked the moment he got out of the Mech.

Only one out of four Adjutants had managed to survive and she had survived because she had been shielded at the last moment. Her eyes were so swollen that it was unknown how many times she’d cried.

“It’s terrible… The opponent’s Mechs are too powerful… They could reflect everything we threw at them back to us and around thirty Pilots have died from this welcoming gift.”

“What about now…” Boris laid onto the stretcher. Both of his arms were broken and blood kept flowing out from his face. This was the results of fighting against a level five Pilot.

“Forty-two pilots out of two hundred are left,” the adjutant responded softly.

The surrounding medical officers couldn’t hold in their emotions and started crying, as most of the participants were their friends and relatives. They had volunteered to be here so that they could obtain the news firsthand as they were worried about the status of the war, but…

“Have we found out who our enemies are?” Matthew calmed down as an oxygen mask was strapped to his face.

“The enemies claimed to be the Shining Mech. Each of them possessed the strength of a level five and if it weren’t for lord Medero arriving in the nick of time…” the adjutant couldn’t speak further.

Level five!

Each and every one of them possessed the strength of a level five and they were fighting against these powerful people as their enemies…

Matthew couldn’t help but shiver at the thought of it.

What sort of concept did the level five represent? Within the Blackboard Academy, which was the most luxurious academy in the Blackboard Region, those who managed to achieve level five were all instructors and there were only a total of hundred plus of them. Furthermore, they were all aged thirty and above. Only these people were able to serve as teachers and guests everywhere and under any power. Their salaries were at the very top and they were very well treated. There was no need for them to go on the battlefield on their own to kill one another. Then, there were those enemies, whose weakest forces possessed level five strength…

“What kind of monsters are they?!” Boris couldn’t hold in his emotion.

“The White Light terrorist organization. Their Shining Mech was just a common grade Mech… They had an even stronger Mech called the Great Light Mech,” Matthew said quietly. “The situation is above what we are able to handle. There’s no point in dragging more people into the battle as it will only increase our death counts. We need the support of stronger Pilots!” Matthew stated calmly.

“Level Five pilots are the academy’s war preparation grade resources. They wouldn’t be mobilized if it wasn’t a battle between regions unless even big sister isn’t able to handle the situation,” Boris shook his head. “Once Black Star is back, all of them, including the Great Light Mech, shall die!”

“Yes, we still have lord Black Star!” Matthew nodded in agreement. Black Star, who was famed to be the strongest first seat in the academy, would definitely handle the situation the moment he returned.

****************

“Red Eye Medero! One of the most talented people in Blackboard.”

At this side of the battle, Medero’s Black Mech was surrounded by three Red-White Mechs. All three of them had a green crystal from the Shining Mech in the middle of their chests.

“Be careful. This woman is very hard to deal with! Although she’s not a level five, she’s still going to give us a hard time!” the Mech who had been fighting alone against Medero was trembling as half of his Mech was surrounded by a black electric current.

“It’s the Paralytic Power. Be careful and don’t let her get near to you!”

The three Mechs that were surrounding Medero started to fly up as they formed a triangular formation.

“If it wasn’t for me wanting to surpass Black Star, you typical level five fools wouldn’t dare fool around in front of me…” Medero sat inside the Mech, and her eyes were red to a point they were turning purple and were on the verge of bleeding. This was her unique Willpower Training Method — Red Eye. Its special effect was to be able to instantly see through her opponent Mech’s weak points. It was truly a terrifying unique Willpower.

“Thunderwhip!”

Medero attacked out of nowhere as both of her hands were now wielding a pair of purple electric whips.

Kashak!

The purple-red whips lashed out, forming a circle chain of electric arcs which landed around two of the Mechs in front of her.

Without any delayed action, an electric stream burst out from behind Medero and appeared in between the two Mechs instantly, and she swung her hands.

Boom boom!!

Two of the Red-White Mechs each had one of their arms torn off, dropping to the ground.

“It’s the Acceleration Field! Retreat! Her speed is too fast!” the only functioning Red-White Mech missed his shot as he shot at where Medero had originally been standing. By the time he reacted, two of his teammates had already been defeated. If he weren’t a pilot with a level five Willpower, he wouldn’t be able to react in time. If he were a slightly weaker pilot, he would’ve instantly exploded in that instant.

Medero’s Field Characteristic was speed, where she was able to increase her speed by up to a horrifying thirty percent in a short amount of time, which was about her Mech’s limit. A typical pilot wouldn’t be able to handle this technique, nor even these Shining Mech Pilots…

Without any word, these three Shining Mechs turned around and split up into three different directions.

“Don’t think you can run away from me!” Medero clapped her hand and formed a more intense purple-red arc.

With a sizzling noise, a purple light flashed and two of the Bright Mechs were split into halves at their waists and exploded in mid-air.

However, this short time frame had given the last Mech an opportunity to escape from her grasp.

Medero’s gaze was extremely focused as she formed another arc. Another purple light was shot up and landed on the back of the Bright Mech, which was a few thousand meters away from her.

Unfortunately, the distance was too great and her opponent was a level five pilot as well. At the most critical moment, he released a stream of white light and diverted the direction of the electric arc. However, this wasn’t without any cost as half of the Bright Mech was burnt. It looked like an empty can from afar as its waist sunk in.

The Bright Mech instantly disappeared as a series of black lightning balls appeared.

“Dimensional Jump?” Medero put away her electric whips and allowed it to move about freely in her hand.

“What a strong body for it to be able to escape safely after taking an attack from my Thunderwhip. No wonder even General Xin was unable to hold these people back. There are so many level five pilots… the White Light Group…”

Medero sat inside the Mech as she pondered.

The vibe she had from these level five pilots was that they weren’t nurtured in the traditional way, but were half-baked products from some sort of potential excitation. All of them were hysterical and she couldn’t sense any hope in them. However their Mechs’ characteristics were very powerful and it even had a unique Willpower ability, namely the Rebound.

To be able to rebound an attack of a certain caliber and also possess an even stronger ability to teleport about, these abilities would be very effective if used at the right moment.

“I need to investigate further.”

“Lord Medero,” a few Black Mechs slowly landed from the sky.

“Black Shirt General? How’s the other location?” Medero asked softly as she deactivated her fighting form, shrinking her Mech down a considerable size.

“There’s a total of 23 places that were ambushed in the whole region and all of them occurred within an hour. All of the opponents were just like those Red-White Bright Mechs. Including you, there were a total of twenty-three squads that moved to the front lines and the current situation should be under control now,” the other guy responded seriously.

“Are there any instructions from the teachers?”

“Principal Simis hopes that you can investigate the whereabouts of these Great Light Mechs that have infiltrated the Blackboard Region. The enemy was very powerful as he was able to escape under the attack of three squads.”

“Oh? Even three squads weren’t enough to stop him?” Medero’s tone turned heavy as even she would feel seriously threatened when fighting against a squad, never mind three. That was a squad consisting of ten Black Shirted Generals, and it was the strongest in the Blackboard Region excluding the military squad formed by the instructors! The weakest members were at least level three and the leader of these Black Shirted Generals were all elites of the academy who possessed the prestige of level five.

Chapter 830: Lurk 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“According to the latest intel, there are two stronger ones among the Bright Mechs which possess similar strengths to those of the Black-Clothed Generals. Furthermore, the Great Light Mechs possess a much stronger strength that could possibly be categorized in the realm of level six. Even the academy was considering mobilizing the Instructor Squad to attack them.”

“Level six…” Medero lowered her head. “Promoting from level five to level six has a very crucial threshold. It would be impossible to attain level six without inheriting a Mech, and if that were the case, the opponent’s body and Willpower definitely plays a huge role.”

“Indeed. We are currently taking steps to gather more intel. An Inherited Mech would have involved a lot of regions and it’s impossible for them to appear out of nowhere.”

“Update me as soon as you have any results.”

Even Medero had lost her cool as the Inherited Mech was involved, as that was a demarcation line for a Pilot. Any pilots who were level five and below were just Model Mechs where the Willpower and Pilots were separated. After attaining level six, the Pilots would merge with the Mech and fuse into a terrifying state, and the differences in strength would be drastically far apart.

“Even though it looks like it’s only one level apart, only people of our level are able to understand the difference in strength and the difficulty in attaining such strength. We’re lucky that the Great Light Mech decided to not go on a killing spree. Did he not show his full strength? What’s the point of that then? There’s definitely a huge motive for them to infiltrate into Blackboard Region!” Medero was lost in her deep thoughts.

**********

“Twelve Flying Dragon Fist!”

Garen punched with only one of his hands. Many afterimages of his fist landed on Celine’s elite bodyguard.

Twelve holes were punched through the bodyguard’s white suit by these densely packed punches, revealing his undershirt. He was able to render the bodyguard helpless with pure air pressure as he fell unconscious to the ground.

“Twelve Flying Dragon Fist!” a similar roar could be heard behind Garen. That was Celine. This girl didn’t seem to behave like a girl at all as she sprinted towards Garen in her high-strength alloy wire clothing as she mimicked Garen’s battle skills.

She took the opportunity to flank him while Garen was dealing with the bodyguard.

Garen turned around and countered the punches with his other hand.

“Too slow, and you lack strength!”

Boom boom boom boom…

The punches clashed against each other and Celine was pushed back, sliding on the ground as if she was a deflated ball…

“The essential of the Flying Dragon Fist is that it can react to the course of the battle at any given moment. Once the opponent has lost his momentum to any of the punches, you can turn these feint punches into actual punches. This same concept can be used on Mechs during battle as well, which is also the basis of my teaching to you.”

Garen walked towards Celine confidently and reached out his hands as he attempted to pick her up.

“An opening!!” Celine laughed as she released her Twelve Flying Dragon Fist, where all twelve punches were aiming at Garen’s weak point, the armpit.

“It’s pointless.”

Garen gently moved to the side as he easily avoided these afterimages. However, Celine unexpectedly changed her course of attack and slapped onto Garen’s waist.

Slap!

“Interesting,” Garen was stunned that he was touched by a beginner when he’d let his guard down. Although it was an ambush, it was a very rare event.

Although he wasn’t very adept in the arts of evading and quick reaction, he was still a top-class martial artist.

“Fuck! It’s so tough! It’s hurts!!!” Celine immediately felt that something was wrong when she hit Garen with all her might. Her palm was swollen and red immediately. “How do you even get this kind of tough body!”

“I’m your master. Don’t you think I should have something hidden under my sleeve?” Garen laughed. “According to our promise, I will only teach you the basics of martial arts and Twelve Flying Dragon Fist. How you develop in the future will depend entirely on you.”

Combining his physical attributes, which were twice as high as a typical person’s, and the simple theory of Qigong, he was able to harden his skin to a certain degree to easily counter against Celine’s futile attack.

“Skills under your sleeve? I like it! I want to learn!” Celine’s eyes were glowing. This person was a martial arts fanatic and would immediately hop up and down the moment she heard something that interested her. In an instant, she pounced to Garen’s side. “Teach me! Just let me know what you want in return!”

“These things are useless in Mechs. Why do you want to learn them?”Garen said hopelessly.

“That’s true…” Celine was disappointed. “Whatever. I think I’m more suited to the Willpower Martial Art.”

“Willpower Martial Art is the strongest battle skill for a pilot,” Garen nodded.

“However, the good bits are the abilities that are derived from the Willpower itself. If their martial arts are of equal level, then these abilities will decide the victor of the battle,” Celine shook his head.

“While Willpower Abilities are very powerful, you shouldn’t look down on martial arts,” Garen frowned as he felt that Celine’s concept was rather wrong.

“There are many strong pilots with powerful Willpower Abilities such as Frozen Wing, Fiery Storm, and even Phantom Superimpose, Prediction. Furthermore, rumor has it that there are even stronger ones, such as traveling through space and attacking or defending against their opponents with dimensional shards,” Celine looked in another direction.

“Travelling through space…” Garen was stunned as well. As Nonosiva’s level was too low, he didn’t have information regarding the scenarios above him. Now that Celine had told him about their prowess, he finally understood the true strength of the Willpower arts.

“These things are too far away from us so let’s not think about them. What else do you have that can be applied to Mechs. Teach me, teach me!” Celine was holding onto Garen’s hand as she kept shouting. Since she was in her tight body attire, her breast and slim waist were sticking tightly onto Garen’s body, as if she was a spoiled child.

Their positions looked rather sexual as Celine’s height was only slightly shorter than Garen. Even the bodyguard had quietly left the training room as he closed the door.

“My path is different than yours so there are very limited theories that I can teach you, and even fewer can be applied to Mechs,” after Garen had achieved level one Willpower, he was thinking if he should increase his absorption rate. However, this would naturally bring some trouble to him. There would definitely be someone who would try to pull him down once his techniques had further improved. On the other hand, Celine’s household would be a bridge to the outer world, where he could complete his breakthrough.

Celine herself didn’t place money as her first priority. When interacting with her, she seemed to be very interested in martial arts and this meant that there shouldn’t be any issue with cooperating with her.

Garen was considering if he should deepen his partnership with her.

“Celine, I have a feeling that I will have a breakthrough in Willpower so I feel like traveling about outside, but…”

“What’s wrong? If you want to go out, just go. There’s nothing to worry about,” Celine released Garen unhappily after realizing that he had changed the topic.

“Ever since there’s been a new breakthrough in my technique, I’ve felt that I’ve too many shares on my end. Hence… I plan to reduce the shares in my hand. Can you help me find a suitable candidate?” Garen said softly.

If he were to increase his production of this high energy powder, Garen knew that he would not be able to hold on to forty percent of his share.

“This might be a problem,” seeing that he’d decided to discuss an important matter, Celine had become serious as well. “We, the Veron Household, may be able to absorb this. How much more can you increase your production?”

Garen knew that the Veron Household had networked themselves to the upper levels without any issues as they held a considerable amount of authority. During this period of interaction with Celine, he’d suspected that the Veron Household might possess an Inherited Mech, which was a level six elite. It wouldn’t even be a problem for them to live well over hundreds of years. According to Celine, the pilot would fuse with the Mech once they reached level six. Their body would evolve together with the Mech and enter a completely different realm. Hence the stage a level six pilot stood upon was vastly different from those below, as their life, lifespan, physical attributes would all increase tremendously.

After calculating the production rate in detail mentally, Garen estimated the amount that he needed to exhaust. Now that he was able to stand firmly and could improve his strength at a faster pace, he made his decision.

“Approximately ten times or more than the current production rate!”

“Ten times!” Celine’s eyes were opened wide. “That nets you tens of millions per month! What the fuck!! That’s my annual expenditure!!!”

“Your expenditure is that huge!?” Garen was stunned as well.

“Yes. During this period of learning martial arts with you, I’ve returned last month and eliminated a branch household’s candidate so our ranking has increased. Heh.” Celine was very proud of herself.

“Your household has branches?” Garen couldn’t help but feel that the Veron Household was quite mysterious.

“To be precise, we are the branch household and the main household is one of the fifteen households of the Mother Planet Federation,” Celine said with a slight degree of arrogance. “This profit is too huge and I don’t dare to take up your offer as this involves a change in the market and will affect the original values of the share market. We alone would not be able to absorb such a huge amount.”

“Then who do you think is able to take up such an amount?” Garen asked softly.

“The Blackboard Region will definitely be affected, as this production rate would definitely catch the attention of the higher-ups. After all, these are military resources,” Celine had gradually calmed down. “I think… you’re not on the right path. Perhaps you can communicate with the higher-ups of the academy with this technology since you’re already on the academy’s radar. Someone has already caught wind of your technique.”

“Communicate with the higher-ups? Who should I contact? Minister Britney?” Garen wasn’t familiar with these people. After knowing how troublesome this issue was, he was considering if he should go to the rainbow stone’s production area alone to absorb everything at once to avoid all the complicated issues. However, this would attract everyone’s attention after leaving behind all the high energy powder. In addition, this was a good way to earn money as well, so he didn’t want to throw everything down the drain.

He didn’t need to force himself to improve drastically in such a short amount of time as it wasn’t bad for him to improve at a steady pace as well.

“I know of an honorable noble in the Polar Region. He has slightly more authority there and great influence as well. That person likes martial arts as much as I do too. However, I’ll give you a heads up that I’m not too close to him and I’m only in contact with him purely because of martial arts. We stand on equal footing and neither of us is better than the other,” Celine explained. “Their Mech’s strength is as good as ours. As long as you’re okay with it, I can introduce him to you.”

“Honorable noble…” typically in the Polar Region, only the nobles from the royal bloodline were able to be crowned as an honorable noble. These people often had strong backgrounds and shouldn’t be messed with. Naturally, they possessed tremendous power and would be ranked higher than Celine or even Britney. This person was indeed a big shot and those who were able to contact him were definitely very important people as well.

Naturally, there were very few of these people.

“I’ll wait for your good news then,” Garen decided after some thought. “I heard that if one has a good network, one can also become a noble in the Polar Region, right?”

“That’s true, but there’s an annual limit and you’ll be able to obtain a very small amount of land. The cost is very huge and there will be a rental period as well. Why do you ask? Do you have such an intention?” Celine questioned. “Well, you can just buy yourself into nobility once your income has increased.”

“It is my dream to have my own land…” Garen acted as if he was looking forward to it, but in actual fact, what he wanted was to find a land that could give him a huge number of Rainbow stones. This way, no one would be able to interrupt him as he absorbed all of them in peace. This was the reason why he wanted a plot of land!

Furthermore, there were a lot of things and experiments that he wanted to keep off the radar. He didn’t dare to fool around in the academy grounds as there were a lot of surveillance and powerful people around.